<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<!-- This is a WordPress eXtended RSS file generated by WordPress as an export of your site. -->
<!-- It contains information about your site's posts, pages, comments, categories, and other content. -->
<!-- You may use this file to transfer that content from one site to another. -->
<!-- This file is not intended to serve as a complete backup of your site. -->

<!-- To import this information into a WordPress site follow these steps: -->
<!-- 1. Log in to that site as an administrator. -->
<!-- 2. Go to Tools: Import in the WordPress admin panel. -->
<!-- 3. Install the "WordPress" importer from the list. -->
<!-- 4. Activate & Run Importer. -->
<!-- 5. Upload this file using the form provided on that page. -->
<!-- 6. You will first be asked to map the authors in this export file to users -->
<!--    on the site. For each author, you may choose to map to an -->
<!--    existing user on the site or to create a new user. -->
<!-- 7. WordPress will then import each of the posts, pages, comments, categories, etc. -->
<!--    contained in this file into your site. -->

<!-- generator="WordPress/4.1.1" created="2015-03-08 21:11" -->
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:excerpt="http://wordpress.org/export/1.2/excerpt/"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:wp="http://wordpress.org/export/1.2/"
>

<channel>
	<title>txGarage</title>
	<link>http://txgarage.com</link>
	<description>News. Reviews. Passion. for the Texas automotive consumer</description>
	<pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 21:11:33 +0000</pubDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<wp:wxr_version>1.2</wp:wxr_version>
	<wp:base_site_url>http://txgarage.com</wp:base_site_url>
	<wp:base_blog_url>http://txgarage.com</wp:base_blog_url>

	<wp:author><wp:author_id>1</wp:author_id><wp:author_login>admin</wp:author_login><wp:author_email>adamaoc@gmail.com</wp:author_email><wp:author_display_name><![CDATA[Adam Moore]]></wp:author_display_name><wp:author_first_name><![CDATA[Adam]]></wp:author_first_name><wp:author_last_name><![CDATA[Moore]]></wp:author_last_name></wp:author>
	<wp:author><wp:author_id>14</wp:author_id><wp:author_login>JustinWegner</wp:author_login><wp:author_email>justin.wegner@txgarage.com</wp:author_email><wp:author_display_name><![CDATA[Justin Wegner]]></wp:author_display_name><wp:author_first_name><![CDATA[Justin]]></wp:author_first_name><wp:author_last_name><![CDATA[Wegner]]></wp:author_last_name></wp:author>
	<wp:author><wp:author_id>8</wp:author_id><wp:author_login>News</wp:author_login><wp:author_email>adam-news@txgarage.com</wp:author_email><wp:author_display_name><![CDATA[News]]></wp:author_display_name><wp:author_first_name><![CDATA[News]]></wp:author_first_name><wp:author_last_name><![CDATA[Stories]]></wp:author_last_name></wp:author>
	<wp:author><wp:author_id>10</wp:author_id><wp:author_login>David_Boldt</wp:author_login><wp:author_email>david.boldt@txgarage.com</wp:author_email><wp:author_display_name><![CDATA[David Boldt]]></wp:author_display_name><wp:author_first_name><![CDATA[David]]></wp:author_first_name><wp:author_last_name><![CDATA[Boldt]]></wp:author_last_name></wp:author>


	<generator>http://wordpress.org/?v=4.1.1</generator>

	<item>
		<title>Full Review of the 2015 Corvette Stingray</title>
		<link>http://txgarage.com/2014/11/full-review-of-the-2015-corvette-stingray/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2014 12:48:47 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://txgarage.com/?p=11540</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[[caption id="attachment_11555" align="alignnone" width="400"]<a href="http://txgarage.com/2014/11/full-review-of-the-2015-corvette-stingray/2015-chevrolet-corvette-stingray-0015/" rel="attachment wp-att-11555"><img src="http://txgarage.com/images/2014/11/2015-Chevrolet-Corvette-Stingray-0015-400x300.jpg" alt="The 2015 Chevy Corvette Stingray" width="400" height="300" class="size-medium wp-image-11555" /></a> The 2015 Chevy Corvette Stingray[/caption]<p class="firstp">I should start off by saying that I’ve never been a huge Corvette fanboy. I’ve always had respect for the brand, and in my driving lifetime at least, it has always been a pretty amazing vehicle for the money. That being said, there’s no getting around the fact that the Corvette has never really be a car to lust after. As a boy, I never had a picture of a C4 hanging on my wall. Even coming to more modern times with the C6, as awesome as that vehicle has been, it’s not a design or a vehicle that is as lust-worthy as its competitors. I’ve been fortunate enough to have been able to get behind the wheel of almost every iteration since the C5. The only one I have yet to jump into would be the ZR1. I’ve even had the privilege to review a Lingenfelter C6 pushing out 630-horsepower.  The thing is, though, the more and more I drive them, the better and better they get. This new generation, the C7 built from the ground up, is no different in that regard. This car has been blowing me away as I make it my daily driver for a week and put it through the paces. </p>

Let’s take a look at what makes this car really stand out. The Corvette has always had a pretty basic shape. With a front-engine, rear-wheel-drive setup - despite rumors of a mid-engine model - there’s not too much you can do with its basic profile. You’re always going to have a long hood, tight cabin, and short rear-end. Although the profile remains basic, the styling has taken a drastic turn. Moving away from flowing, sensual lines into a more aggressive, sharp, and edgy design has given the C7 a new look. The new frame is made of lightweight aluminum instead of steel in an effort to save weight. Thanks to new build techniques, the chassis alone is 99-pounds lighter than last year’s model and 57-percent stiffer. They have also moved toward using more carbon-fiber for body panels like the hood to help save weight and keep the center of gravity as low as possible. All of these efforts round up to a curb weight of just 3,298-lbs for the C7 which is about the same as a similarly equipped C6, but it’s where they lost the weight and the nearly perfect 50/50 weight distribution that counts. The engineers have also stated that if they didn’t have to worry about fuel economy, the C7 could be even lighter.

What used to be the biggest point of ridicule for the Corvette is now one of its finer features. It’s no secret to any automotive shopper around the world, nor to the top brass at GM itself, that the interior of the Vette has never matched up to its competition or potential. This has all changed with the C7 as everything inside this cabin is covered in premium materials including soft rubbers, Napa leather, or even genuine carbon fiber. This interior feels very handcrafted and luxurious and it’s packed full of the technologies drivers have been asking for and have come to expect these days. Taking your first sit in the drivers seat is all it takes to realize that the fighter jet inspired cockpit focuses solely on the driver and driver engagement. This is even more apparent when you check out the passenger seat and see the climate controls placed to the right of the passenger vent so they don’t have to bother with reaching over into the driver's space. 

The driver’s information display is one big LCD screen in the middle of an analog speedometer on the left and a fuel tank and temperature gauges on the right. You can pick what you want displayed on the screen in the middle; anything from a large rpm tach, digital speedometer, or even tire heat or G’s you’re pulling. This is a great setup that’s useful, but the thing you really want to keep your eyes on is the full-color heads-up display. This allows you to never take your eyes off the road ahead and still know exactly what is happening with your vehicle.

<a href="http://txgarage.com/2014/11/full-review-of-the-2015-corvette-stingray/2015-chevrolet-corvette-stingray-0025/" rel="attachment wp-att-11565"><img src="http://txgarage.com/images/2014/11/2015-Chevrolet-Corvette-Stingray-0025-400x300.jpg" alt="2015-Chevrolet-Corvette-Stingray-0025" class="img-bytwo alignnone size-medium wp-image-11565" /></a><a href="http://txgarage.com/2014/11/full-review-of-the-2015-corvette-stingray/2015-chevrolet-corvette-stingray-0026/" rel="attachment wp-att-11566"><img src="http://txgarage.com/images/2014/11/2015-Chevrolet-Corvette-Stingray-0026-400x300.jpg" alt="2015-Chevrolet-Corvette-Stingray-0026" class="img-bytwo alignnone size-medium wp-image-11566" /></a>

To the right of the driver, nestled into the cockpit and angled toward the driver is an 8-inch infotainment display. This is a big area where the Corvette needed lots of love, and luckily, that love was given. The new system works great and looks great as well. All of the buttons are easy to reach and easy to figure out so you’re not constantly looking over trying to figure out what you’re doing. You also get controls on the steering wheel to make simple, everyday actions even easier. 

It’s not all great, though, as the two biggest gripes I have with this car both still come from the interior. One is the steering wheel itself; the thing you’re looking at and touching the most. The leather wrap is very nice and at 14.1-inch-diameter, I really like the small size. What I don’t like is the fact that the cheapest looking and feeling part of the whole interior is the middle part of the steering wheel. The other thing I’ll pick on is the paddle shifters. These are also plastic and feel pretty cheap. I could be fine with that if they worked halfway decent. Pulling back on the paddle, you don’t get a sense at all that you are doing anything even remotely mechanical. They really leave you with a dead feeling and it’s almost better just leaving it in automatic and letting this great transmission, which we’ll get into, do its thing. If I could describe the feeling, I would say it’s like closing a door in a house with foundation problems. You can push or pull it, but it inevitably gets stuck right before its ready to latch - you always have to give it that last little shove to get it to close all the way. Yes, that’s what these paddle shifters feel like but enough nitpicking, let’s move on.

Let’s look under the hood and see what the Corvette’s really about. Yes, this car still has a massive V8 and it lives up front sitting just behind the front wheels. This is the formula that’s worked for decades, and at least for the C7, this is how they’re still approaching it. That engine is a 6.2-liter V8 dubbed the LT1. It features an all-aluminum block with direct injection and continuously variable valve times and pushes out a healthy 455-horsepower and 460-lbs.ft. of torque. This is now the most powerful standard engine Chevrolet has ever offered on a Corvette. 

I eluded to the transmission matched up to this great engine earlier, but here comes the details. We’re talking an 8-speed automatic transmission, all new for 2015. This transmission was specifically designed for this car to enhance performance and efficiency. Yes, you can still get a 7-speed manual gearbox, but this big 8-speed has some really nice technological benefits. It also delivers shifts at a world-class speed that rivals the best dual-clutch transmissions out there.

<hr style="width: 100%; clear: both;">

<a href="http://txgarage.com/2014/11/full-review-of-the-2015-corvette-stingray/2015-chevrolet-corvette-stingray-0024/" rel="attachment wp-att-11564"><img src="http://txgarage.com/images/2014/11/2015-Chevrolet-Corvette-Stingray-0024-400x300.jpg" alt="2015-Chevrolet-Corvette-Stingray-0024" width="400" height="300" class="img-bythree alignnone size-medium wp-image-11564" /></a><a href="http://txgarage.com/2014/11/full-review-of-the-2015-corvette-stingray/2015-chevrolet-corvette-stingray-0019/" rel="attachment wp-att-11559"><img src="http://txgarage.com/images/2014/11/2015-Chevrolet-Corvette-Stingray-0019-400x300.jpg" alt="2015-Chevrolet-Corvette-Stingray-0019" width="400" height="300" class="img-bythree alignnone size-medium wp-image-11559" /></a><a href="http://txgarage.com/2014/11/full-review-of-the-2015-corvette-stingray/2015-chevrolet-corvette-stingray-0016/" rel="attachment wp-att-11556"><img src="http://txgarage.com/images/2014/11/2015-Chevrolet-Corvette-Stingray-0016-400x300.jpg" alt="2015-Chevrolet-Corvette-Stingray-0016" width="400" height="300" class="img-bythree alignnone size-medium wp-image-11556" /></a>

<hr style="width: 100%; clear: both;">

The GM engineers had to do some pretty fancy stuff to pack this 8-speed transmission into its tight packaging. The transmission sits over the rear axle and just fits into the space available. The engineers also say they developed this transmission to withstand a load of 650-hp and 650 lbs.ft of torque so we expect to see this in some higher power variants coming soon. 

 All of this adds up to a drive that is unlike any Corvette I’ve driven. This is easily the best driving Vette with a lighter, more precise feel than ever before. If you’re used to the front-heavy feel in generations past, you’ll be surprised when you hit a corner in the C7. 

The suspension has been significantly overhauled with hollow lower control arms and new aluminum rear tow-links that save almost 11-lbs over the previous design. The steering has also been upgraded with GM moving to an electric system for even more weight savings. They’ve made sure to keep as much feel as possible by stiffening the steering column by 150-percent and the torsion stiffness by 600-percent. This means the C7 is 5-times more rigid than the C6 before it, but now benefits in lighter weight, more economy, and driver modes available with the electronic steering. Most of the time, I would say I prefer the old hydraulic steering but they’ve really done it right in the C7 and the steering just feels spot-on. 

Looking at the field of competitors, the Corvettes sits with some serious names. It’s often put side-by-side on the track with the likes of the Viper, Ferrari’s, the GTR, and now the BMW M4. These are all incredible names and usually cost massive amounts more than the Corvette. Even with all that is new in the C7, you can pick one up starting at just $54,000. Our Stingray Coupe with the 8-speed auto and a few other performance and appearance packages topped out at $67,445, which is a great deal for how much car you get. That should be no surprise, though, considering that’s what the Corvette has always been about; bang for buck. 

Living with the C7 Stingray everyday isn’t that much different than living with any other vehicle. Although you can’t carry more than one extra person along with you, you can’t carry much luggage or groceries with you, you get noticed anywhere you go, and you have a massive V8 engine ready to propel you into warp speed at a moments notice. Other than these few details, it’s pretty much like driving any other vehicle. In all seriousness, though, the driving dynamics are not intimidating. You can cruise in this car all day long without ever feeling consumed by power. It’s also pretty comfortable for such a compact vehicle. The bucket seats are some of the best ever put into a Corvette and could be some of the best in anything in its price range. The steering is light and direct so maneuvering the car in a parking lot is easy. It doesn’t gulp fuel like other high-performance vehicles, you’ll actually average some pretty decent mpg if you’re not being hard on the throttle. This is easily the best Corvette I’ve ever driven, but it’s also just a great car; a great sports car in its own right. If you have the means and you’re looking for a car to rock your world, it’s hard to go wrong with the C7.

[gallery columns="5" ids="11541,11542,11543,11544,11545,11546,11547,11548,11549,11550,11551,11552,11553,11554,11555,11556,11557,11558,11559,11560,11561,11562,11563,11564,11565,11566,11567,11568,11569,11570,11571,11572,11573,11574,11575,11576,11577,11578,11579,11580,11581,11582,11583,11584,11585,11586"]]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>11540</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2014-11-07 07:48:47</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2014-11-07 12:48:47</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>full-review-of-the-2015-corvette-stingray</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="2015"><![CDATA[2015]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="8-speed"><![CDATA[8-speed]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="auto"><![CDATA[auto]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="car-reviews"><![CDATA[Car Reviews]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="chevrolet"><![CDATA[chevrolet]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="chevrolet-2"><![CDATA[Chevrolet]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="chevy"><![CDATA[chevy]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="corvette"><![CDATA[corvette]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="corvette-chevrolet-2"><![CDATA[Corvette]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="eight-speed"><![CDATA[eight speed]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="gm"><![CDATA[GM]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="horsepower"><![CDATA[horsepower]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="stingray"><![CDATA[stingray]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="super-car"><![CDATA[super car]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="transmission"><![CDATA[transmission]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_knews_automated</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[0]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_thumbnail_id</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[11554]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>good-bad-list</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[<div class="cci-press-card__wrap">
  <div class="cci-press-card card--front"> 
    <header class="press-card__header"></header>
    <section class="press-card__content">
      <div class="journalist-name animated fadeInLeft" data-journalist-name="Adam Moore"></div>
      <span class="journalist-title">
        <a href="http://twitter.com/adamaoc">
          @adamaoc
        </a>
      </span>
    </section>
    <footer class="press-card__footer">
      <div class="article-link">
        Web Dev for DealerTrack Tech - Writer and auto reviewer with @txGarage - Co-founder of @BensHeart Foundation - Family man first - love tech, cars, and politics
Dallas, TX 
      </div>
    </footer>
  </div>
</div>]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>postdata</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[2013|Chevrolet|Corvette]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_aioseop_description</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[txGarage - News. Reviews. Passion. - Texas Automotive Reviews :: Let’s take a look at what makes this car really stand out. The Corvette has always had a pretty basic shape. With a front-engine, rear-wheel-drive setup - despite rumors of a mid-engine model - there’s not too much you can do with its basic profile. You’re always going to have a long hood, tight cabin, and short rear-end. Although the profile remains basic, the styling has taken a drastic turn. Moving away from flowing, sensual lines into a more aggressive, sharp, and edgy design has given the C7 a new look.]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_aioseop_keywords</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[2015, chevrolet, corvette, stingray, auto, transmission, 8-speed, eight speed, gm, chevy, super car, horsepower, texas, dallas, dfw]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_ttscj_header_code</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[<style>
.post h1 {
  font-size: 27px;
}
.entry-content del { 
text-decoration: none;
font-size: 17px;
line-height: 26px;
}
.entry-content h2:first-child {
  text-align: center; 
  line-height: 1.8;
  font-size: 18px;
  letter-spacing: 1px;
  margin-bottom: 16px;
}
.img-bytwo {
  box-sizing: border-box;
width: 50% !important;
margin-bottom: 16px;
float: left;
padding-right: 1em;
padding-top: 1em;
padding-bottom: 1em;
}

.img-bythree {
  float: left;
  width: 33.33%;
  margin-bottom: 1em;
}

.entry-content .alignleft  {
  float: left;
}
.entry-content p {
font-size: 16px;
font-weight: 100;
letter-spacing: 1px;
line-height: 24px;
}
.entry-content  p:first-child {
font-size: 17px;
line-height: 26px;
}

body .entry-content p.firstp {
  font-size: 17px;
  line-height: 24px;
}

.entry-content .clear {
	clear: none;
}

/* === CCI Journalist Press Card === */
/* === CCI Journalist Press Card === */
.inner-gbl {
  overflow: hidden; 
}
.inner-gbl > h4 {
  display: none; 
}
.cci-press-card__wrap {
  position: relative;
  width: 260px;
  height: 410px;
  margin: 0 auto;
  -webkit-transform-style: preserve-3d;
  -moz-transform-style: preserve-3d;
  transform-style: preserve-3d;
  transition: transform 0.5s ease;
}
.card--front {
  z-index: 10;
} 

.padded {
  padding: 0 5px;
  font-size: 12px;
  text-align: center;
}
.cci-press-card {
  width: 260px; 
  height: 400px;
  margin: 0 auto;
  font-family: "Lucida Grande", sans-serif;
  background: #924b4e;
  border-radius: 8px;
  border-bottom: 3px solid #57060a;
  position: absolute;
  -webkit-backface-visibility: hidden;
  -moz-backface-visibility: hidden;
  backface-visibility: hidden;
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__header {
  height: 13px;
  padding: 20px;
  font-size: 20px;
  color: ghostwhite;
  line-height: 1;
  font-weight: 700;
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__header:before {
  content: "Author";
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__header:after {
  content: "Press Card";
  color: #652327;
  float: right;
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__content {
  height: 140px;
  padding: 20px;
  font-size: 20px;
  background: #444444 url('http://txgarage.com/images/2013/11/dallas-75-back.jpg') no-repeat;
  background-position-x: 0px;
  background-size: cover;
  transition: background-position-x 1s ease-out;
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__content .journalist-name:before {
  content: attr(data-journalist-name) "\A\A";
  color: ghostwhite;
  width: 100%;
  clear: both;
  display: block;
  font-weight: 700;
  text-shadow: 2px 2px 3px #333;
}
.cci-press-card .journalist-title a {
  display: block;
  font-size: 16px;
  color: ghostwhite;
  width: 100%;
  clear: both;
  text-decoration: none;
  text-shadow: 2px 2px 3px #333;
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__footer {
  padding: 0 20px; 
  color: white;
}
.press-card__footer h4 {
  font-weight: 100;
}
.press-card__footer h4 a {
  color: #fff;
  text-decoration: none;
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__footer .article-link {
  margin-bottom: 10px;
  padding-top: 10px;
  text-align: justify;
  color: #f1f1f1;
}
.rotate-3d {
  -webkit-transform: rotateY(180deg);
  -moz-transform: rotateY(180deg);
  transform: rotateY(180deg);
}
.z-up {
  z-index: 10;
}
.animated {
  -webkit-animation-fill-mode: both;
  -moz-animation-fill-mode: both;
  -ms-animation-fill-mode: both;
  -o-animation-fill-mode: both;
  animation-fill-mode: both;
  -webkit-animation-duration: 1s;
  -moz-animation-duration: 1s;
  -ms-animation-duration: 1s;
  -o-animation-duration: 1s;
  animation-duration: 1s;
}
@-webkit-keyframes fadeInLeft {
  0% {
    opacity: 0;
    -webkit-transform: translateX(-20px);
  }
  100% {
    opacity: 1;
    -webkit-transform: translateX(0);
  }
}
@-moz-keyframes fadeInLeft {
  0% {
    opacity: 0;
    -moz-transform: translateX(-20px);
  }
  100% {
    opacity: 1;
    -moz-transform: translateX(0);
  }
}
@-o-keyframes fadeInLeft {
  0% {
    opacity: 0;
    -o-transform: translateX(-20px);
  }
  100% {
    opacity: 1;
    -o-transform: translateX(0);
  }
}
@keyframes fadeInLeft {
  0% {
    opacity: 0;
    transform: translateX(-20px);
  }
  100% {
    opacity: 1;
    transform: translateX(0);
  }
}
.fadeInLeft {
  -webkit-animation-name: fadeInLeft;
  -moz-animation-name: fadeInLeft;
  -o-animation-name: fadeInLeft;
  animation-name: fadeInLeft;
}

@media screen and (max-width: 480px) {
 .inner-gbl { display: none; }
}
</style>
]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_aioseop_title</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[Full Review of the 2015 Corvette Stingray]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_wpas_done_all</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Could this Ram be an everyday driver and a workhorse?</title>
		<link>http://txgarage.com/2014/11/could-this-ram-be-an-everyday-driver-and-a-workhorse/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2014 12:20:54 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[JustinWegner]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://txgarage.com/?p=11594</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>The 2014 Ram 1500 Eco Diesel</h2>

[caption id="attachment_11599" align="alignnone" width="400"]<a href="http://txgarage.com/2014/11/could-this-ram-be-an-everyday-driver-and-a-workhorse/2014-ram-1500-lonestar-ecodiesel-001/" rel="attachment wp-att-11599"><img src="http://txgarage.com/images/2014/11/2014-Ram-1500-LoneStar-EcoDiesel-001-400x300.jpg" alt="2014 Ram 1500 Lone Star EcoDiesel" width="400" height="300" class="size-medium wp-image-11599" /></a> 2014 Ram 1500 Lone Star EcoDiesel[/caption]<p class="firstp">It’s not too often you can have a conversation while inspecting a diesel engine but that’s exactly what happened when I was looking under the hood of the 2014 Ram 1500 Eco Diesel. This review is to go over some points that I see worth noting if you’re looking at this eco diesel machine.</p>

<p class="firstp">Let’s talk exterior, what a great looking truck! With the 2014 Ram 1500 being the Motor Trend's 2014 Truck of the Year, I expected nothing less when inspecting everything about the exterior. This truck has that typical Ram Truck bold look from the front but has a square look that makes this truck very intriguing. They finally made the Rambox Cargo Management System functional with the keyless entry. So all valuables that are placed inside will be secure when you lock your truck. Another feature that also lends itself to the good looks for this Ram Truck is the very innovative Active Air Grille Shutters. Since technology has come so far on vehicles this one intrigues me the most as of late. The grilles automatically open and shut when the truck needs to be cooled. The grilles also shut at high speeds to reduce drag, which also helps gain more miles per gallon and saving money at the pump.</p>

<a href="http://txgarage.com/2014/11/could-this-ram-be-an-everyday-driver-and-a-workhorse/2014-ram-1500-lonestar-ecodiesel-0022/" rel="attachment wp-att-11621"><img src="http://txgarage.com/images/2014/11/2014-Ram-1500-LoneStar-EcoDiesel-0022-400x300.jpg" alt="2014-Ram-1500-LoneStar-EcoDiesel-0022" width="400" height="300" class="img-bytwo alignnone size-medium wp-image-11621" /></a><a href="http://txgarage.com/2014/11/could-this-ram-be-an-everyday-driver-and-a-workhorse/2014-ram-1500-lonestar-ecodiesel-0023/" rel="attachment wp-att-11622"><img src="http://txgarage.com/images/2014/11/2014-Ram-1500-LoneStar-EcoDiesel-0023-400x300.jpg" alt="2014-Ram-1500-LoneStar-EcoDiesel-0023" width="400" height="300" class="img-bytwo alignnone size-medium wp-image-11622" /></a>

I didn’t get any real time behind the wheel of this beast but it’s rated at 20 City MPG and 28 HWY MPG. I can certainly tell that all signs lead to a truck that fits the bill of finally getting some decent gas mileage. The towing capacity of the 3.0L Eco Diesel V6 is also very eye opening, rated at towing almost 10,000-lbs. I feel like there’s certainly some work this beast could put out. 

The interior of this truck was very much Ram as well. In one word, it felt like tough. Which is exactly that they tout. The dash seems like it had more technology than I have seen in previous models of Dodge Rams. The technology in the dash had some voice activation features that I also didn’t get a chance to mess wit. Luckily, Ram loves us here at txGarage so we’ll be getting more trucks soon and I’ll make sure to snatch one away from Adam for long enough to get some real time with the truck. 

There was one thing that seemed to stick out for me, and that was the small pockets of cargo space below a/c vents. I just don’t understand what goes there. If you were to keep change in there, just seems like it would fall out if you were going off road. This is ultra picky, I know, just feel like not having it there might serve a better purpose than an empty hole. 

Overall, my rating on this truck being and everyday driver and a workhorse depends on the situations and magnitude of the work, but overall, yes. With this being an Eco Diesel engine I feel like it’s got power, just not enough to be the workhorse that other trucks on the market have currently. The quietness in the cab allows you to be able to think without the loud annoyances as other loud diesel engines. This is one nice truck and I approve it for an everyday drive based on the time I got with it. Although, my opinion could change the more time I could get with it. I was very impressed at how far Ram has come and I look forward to many more years of their dependable and innovative trucks.

[gallery columns="5" ids="11599,11600,11601,11602,11603,11604,11605,11606,11607,11608,11609,11610,11611,11612,11613,11614,11615,11616,11617,11619,11620,11621,11622"]]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>11594</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2014-11-14 07:20:54</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2014-11-14 12:20:54</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>could-this-ram-be-an-everyday-driver-and-a-workhorse</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="1500-ecodiesel"><![CDATA[1500 EcoDiesel]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="2014"><![CDATA[2014]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="2014-ram-1500"><![CDATA[2014 Ram 1500]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="car-reviews"><![CDATA[Car Reviews]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="dodge"><![CDATA[dodge]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="ecodiesel"><![CDATA[ecodiesel]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="engine"><![CDATA[engine]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="interior"><![CDATA[interior]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="quick-drive-2"><![CDATA[Quick Drive]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="quick-drive"><![CDATA[quick drive]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="quick-look"><![CDATA[quick look]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="ram"><![CDATA[ram]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="ram-2"><![CDATA[Ram]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="ram-1500"><![CDATA[ram 1500]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="ram-eco-diesel"><![CDATA[ram eco diesel]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="review"><![CDATA[review]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="towing"><![CDATA[towing]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_knews_automated</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[0]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>good-bad-list</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[<div class="cci-press-card__wrap">
  <div class="cci-press-card card--front"> 
    <header class="press-card__header"></header>
    <section class="press-card__content">
      <div class="journalist-name animated fadeInLeft" data-journalist-name="Justin Wegner"></div>
      <span class="journalist-title">
        <a href="http://twitter.com/"></a>
      </span>
    </section>
    <footer class="press-card__footer">
      <div class="article-link">
        Justin is a Sr. Web Designer at Dealertrack Technologies with a true passion for family, anything outdoors and all things about vehicles. This gives him a great perspective on off-road vehicles although he's a big car enthusiast as well.
      </div>
    </footer>
  </div>
</div>]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>postdata</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[2014|Ram|1500]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_aioseop_description</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[txGarage - News. Reviews. Passion. - Texas Truck Reviews :: It’s not too often you can have a conversation while inspecting a diesel engine but that’s exactly what happened when I was looking under the hood of the 2014 Ram 1500 Eco Diesel. This review is to go over some points that I see worth noting if you’re looking at this eco diesel machine. ]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_aioseop_keywords</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[2014 Ram 1500, ram eco diesel, ecodiesel, ram 1500, 2014, ram, dodge, engine, towing, interior, quick drive, quick look, review, towing]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_aioseop_title</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[Could this Ram be an everyday driver and a workhorse? - The 2014 Ram 1500 Eco Diesel]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_ttscj_header_code</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[<style>
.post h1 {
  font-size: 27px;
  line-height: 1.3;
}
.entry-content del { 
text-decoration: none;
font-size: 17px;
line-height: 26px;
}
.entry-content h2:first-child {
  text-align: center; 
  line-height: 1.8;
  font-size: 18px;
  letter-spacing: 1px;
  margin-bottom: 16px;
}

.img-bytwo {
  box-sizing: border-box;
  width: 50% !important;
  margin-bottom: 16px;
  float: left;
  padding-right: 1em;
  padding-top: 1em;
  padding-bottom: 1em;
}

.img-bythree {
  float: left;
  width: 33.33%;
  margin-bottom: 1em;
}
.entry-content .alignleft  {
  float: left;
}
.entry-content p {
font-size: 16px;
font-weight: 100;
letter-spacing: 1px;
line-height: 24px;
}
.entry-content  p:first-child {
font-size: 17px;
line-height: 26px;
}

body .entry-content p.firstp {
  font-size: 17px;
  line-height: 24px;
}


/* === CCI Journalist Press Card === */
/* === CCI Journalist Press Card === */
.inner-gbl {
  overflow: hidden; 
}
.inner-gbl > h4 {
  display: none; 
}
.cci-press-card__wrap {
  position: relative;
  width: 260px;
  height: 410px;
  margin: 0 auto;
  -webkit-transform-style: preserve-3d;
  -moz-transform-style: preserve-3d;
  transform-style: preserve-3d;
  transition: transform 0.5s ease;
}
.card--front {
  z-index: 10;
} 

.padded {
  padding: 0 5px;
  font-size: 12px;
  text-align: center;
}
.cci-press-card {
  width: 260px; 
  height: 400px;
  margin: 0 auto;
  font-family: "Lucida Grande", sans-serif;
  background: #924b4e;
  border-radius: 8px;
  border-bottom: 3px solid #57060a;
  position: absolute;
  -webkit-backface-visibility: hidden;
  -moz-backface-visibility: hidden;
  backface-visibility: hidden;
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__header {
  height: 13px;
  padding: 20px;
  font-size: 20px;
  color: ghostwhite;
  line-height: 1;
  font-weight: 700;
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__header:before {
  content: "Author";
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__header:after {
  content: "Press Card";
  color: #652327;
  float: right;
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__content {
  height: 140px;
  padding: 20px;
  font-size: 20px;
  background: #444444 url('http://txgarage.com/images/2014/10/justin-wegner.jpg') no-repeat;
  background-position-x: 0px;
  background-size: cover;
  transition: background-position-x 1s ease-out;
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__content .journalist-name:before {
  content: attr(data-journalist-name) "\A\A";
  color: ghostwhite;
  width: 100%;
  clear: both;
  display: block;
  font-weight: 700;
  text-shadow: 2px 2px 3px #333;
}
.cci-press-card .journalist-title a {
  display: block;
  font-size: 16px;
  color: ghostwhite;
  width: 100%;
  clear: both;
  text-decoration: none;
  text-shadow: 2px 2px 3px #333;
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__footer {
  padding: 0 20px; 
  color: white;
}
.press-card__footer h4 {
  font-weight: 100;
}
.press-card__footer h4 a {
  color: #fff;
  text-decoration: none;
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__footer .article-link {
  margin-bottom: 10px;
  padding-top: 10px;
  text-align: justify;
  color: #f1f1f1;
}
.rotate-3d {
  -webkit-transform: rotateY(180deg);
  -moz-transform: rotateY(180deg);
  transform: rotateY(180deg);
}
.z-up {
  z-index: 10;
}
.animated {
  -webkit-animation-fill-mode: both;
  -moz-animation-fill-mode: both;
  -ms-animation-fill-mode: both;
  -o-animation-fill-mode: both;
  animation-fill-mode: both;
  -webkit-animation-duration: 1s;
  -moz-animation-duration: 1s;
  -ms-animation-duration: 1s;
  -o-animation-duration: 1s;
  animation-duration: 1s;
}
@-webkit-keyframes fadeInLeft {
  0% {
    opacity: 0;
    -webkit-transform: translateX(-20px);
  }
  100% {
    opacity: 1;
    -webkit-transform: translateX(0);
  }
}
@-moz-keyframes fadeInLeft {
  0% {
    opacity: 0;
    -moz-transform: translateX(-20px);
  }
  100% {
    opacity: 1;
    -moz-transform: translateX(0);
  }
}
@-o-keyframes fadeInLeft {
  0% {
    opacity: 0;
    -o-transform: translateX(-20px);
  }
  100% {
    opacity: 1;
    -o-transform: translateX(0);
  }
}
@keyframes fadeInLeft {
  0% {
    opacity: 0;
    transform: translateX(-20px);
  }
  100% {
    opacity: 1;
    transform: translateX(0);
  }
}
.fadeInLeft {
  -webkit-animation-name: fadeInLeft;
  -moz-animation-name: fadeInLeft;
  -o-animation-name: fadeInLeft;
  animation-name: fadeInLeft;
}

@media screen and (max-width: 480px) {
 .inner-gbl { display: none; }
}
</style>]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_thumbnail_id</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[11599]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_wpas_done_all</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Debut of the New 2016 Explorer - Platinum Edition</title>
		<link>http://txgarage.com/2014/11/debut-of-the-new-2016-explorer-platinum-edition/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2014 21:55:02 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[JustinWegner]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://txgarage.com/?p=11625</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[[caption id="attachment_11629" align="alignnone" width="400"]<a href="http://txgarage.com/2014/11/debut-of-the-new-2016-explorer-platinum-edition/16fordexplorer_02_hr/" rel="attachment wp-att-11629"><img src="http://txgarage.com/images/2014/11/16FordExplorer_02_HR-400x204.jpg" alt="The 2016 Ford Explorer" width="400" height="204" class="size-medium wp-image-11629" /></a> The 2016 Ford Explorer[/caption]<p class="firstp">Ever since the introduction of the new body style for the Ford Explorer back in 2011, we here at txGarage have been extremely impressed with the improvements Ford keeps advancing with. Well, on Tuesday, November 18th, 2014 Ford debuted the all-new 2016 Ford Explorer. Having watched and anticipated the news of this event from Ford for a while, I feel like I already have some great feedback for Ford with their innovations. They debuted the Platinum Edition which in it’s own right was one was you could tell Ford was listening to its consumer. Ford started to realize people were maximizing the options for this Explorer so, I think it was strategically and well played for them to debut with the Platinum Edition. And oh by the way Ford sells about 200,000 of these things every year, so you know they have the consumer base to get real-world examples on how to improve on an already dependable vehicle for off-road and everyday use.</p>
 
Let’s start with the visual appeal. Overall, this Explorer hasn’t changed too much in the aesthetically pleasing aspects. Still has that Land Rover look (which I am a huge fan of). With the bulky, broad front look paired with the hatchback-like backend, it’s an overall an exceptionally appealing vehicle. They cleaned up some of the edges taking away a few curves. They improved the grill to be more fuel efficient with the open closing technology. Even the base models look fantastic in my oh so humble opinion, but don't’ get me wrong, I would still love to get some time behind the Platinum Edition.
 
Now let’s talk power! The Explorer Sport and Platinum models both come with the 3.5L Ecoboost V-6. This engine on the frame of the Explorer is sure to put out enough power to do whatever normal job that is asked of it. The options for 4 wheel drive tells me this Explorer is going to be a serious contender in the SUV arena when it comes out for not only being luxurious but also versatile from concrete to trails.

<a href="http://txgarage.com/2014/11/debut-of-the-new-2016-explorer-platinum-edition/16fordexplorer_01_hr/" rel="attachment wp-att-11628" class="wp-att-11628"><img src="http://txgarage.com/images/2014/11/16FordExplorer_01_HR-400x270.jpg" alt="16FordExplorer_01_HR" width="400" height="270" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-11628" /></a>
 
The interior to this Platinum Edition for the Explorer is everything you would hoped it would be, and as they say, “so much more!” Inviting and luxurious all the while looking up for any challenge a family could have to throw at it. The automatic folding seats are what I feel is a great feature for everyone. Now even kids can fold seats down without having to hassle mom or dad. The views from the front (180° view) and back up cameras are also great on the display. Another feature that Ford installed in this model was the washer for the front and rear-facing cameras! This first of it’s kind feature was one that will become very useful when weather changes and you need either of the cameras. By simply hitting the wash button for cameras, you instantly start to notice a difference, all the while not having to leave the cab of the vehicle.
 
As with most Ford models coming out the past few years, they keep increasing safety. Being a new father, this is something I am becoming more aware of as the days pass. With adaptive cruise control, lane keeping, parallel and parking assist, the features on here are more than safe. I would feel more than comfortable packing up the family and luggage and going on a road trip, whether that be long or short.
 
So here’s the breakdown; this 2016 Explorer looks like it’s going to be a great contender for one of the greatest SUVs and we can’t wait to get our hands on the wheel and get some driving time. Weather your taking the kids to the ever cliched ‘Soccer Practice’ or you have an adventurous family that’s ready to take the road less traveled all over the nation, seems this 2016 Explorer is going to be one tough choice to pass up. The higher sticker price on the Platinum is a little bit of a turn off but if Ford has sold around 7 million of these things since ‘91, I would say they’re listening to their audience and making adjustments as so. This 2016 model sure incorporates some of those features with camera features and the smart charging system that charges your device at the highest possible rate. With all that said, I couldn’t wait to actually sit in one, drive one, and when they’re available spring/summer of 2015 drive that bad boy!

[gallery columns="4" ids="11628,11629,11630,11631,11632,11633,11634"]]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>11625</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2014-11-20 16:55:02</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2014-11-20 21:55:02</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>debut-of-the-new-2016-explorer-platinum-edition</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="2016"><![CDATA[2016]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="2016-ford-explorer"><![CDATA[2016 ford explorer]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="auto-show"><![CDATA[auto show]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="explorer-2"><![CDATA[explorer]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="ford"><![CDATA[ford]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="future-cars"><![CDATA[Future Cars]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="la"><![CDATA[la]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="la-auto-show"><![CDATA[la auto show]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="news"><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="suv"><![CDATA[suv]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_knews_automated</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[0]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_aioseop_description</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[txGarage - News. Reviews. Passion. - Texas Automotive News :: Ever since the introduction of the new body style for the Ford Explorer back in 2011, we here at txGarage have been extremely impressed with the improvements Ford keeps advancing with. Well, on Tuesday, November 18th, 2014 Ford debuted the all-new 2016 Ford Explorer. Having watched and anticipated the news of this event from Ford for a while, I feel like I already have some great feedback for Ford with their innovations. They debuted the Platinum Edition which in it’s own right was one was you could tell Ford was listening to its consumer. Ford started to realize people were maximizing the options for this Explorer so, I think it was strategically and well played for them to debut with the Platinum Edition. And oh by the way Ford sells about 200,000 of these things every year, so you know they have the consumer base to get real-world examples on how to improve on an already dependable vehicle for off-road and everyday use.]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_aioseop_title</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[Debut of the New 2016 Explorer - Platinum Edition]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_ttscj_header_code</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[<style>
.post h1 {
  font-size: 27px;
  line-height: 1.3;
}
.entry-content del { 
text-decoration: none;
font-size: 17px;
line-height: 26px;
}
.entry-content h2:first-child {
  text-align: center; 
  line-height: 1.8;
  font-size: 18px;
  letter-spacing: 1px;
  margin-bottom: 16px;
}

.img-bytwo {
  box-sizing: border-box;
  width: 50% !important;
  margin-bottom: 16px;
  float: left;
  padding-right: 1em;
  padding-top: 1em;
  padding-bottom: 1em;
}

.img-bythree {
  float: left;
  width: 33.33%;
  margin-bottom: 1em;
}
html .entry-content .wp-att-11628 {
display: block;
width: 100%;
}
html .entry-content .wp-att-11628 img {
float: none !important;
max-width: 100%;
width: 400px;
margin: 0 auto;
padding: 0;
display: block;
}
.entry-content .alignleft  {
  float: left;
}
.entry-content p {
font-size: 16px;
font-weight: 100;
letter-spacing: 1px;
line-height: 24px;
}
.entry-content  p:first-child {
font-size: 17px;
line-height: 26px;
}

body .entry-content p.firstp {
  font-size: 17px;
  line-height: 24px;
}


/* === CCI Journalist Press Card === */
/* === CCI Journalist Press Card === */
.inner-gbl {
  overflow: hidden; 
}
.inner-gbl > h4 {
  display: none; 
}
.cci-press-card__wrap {
  position: relative;
  width: 260px;
  height: 410px;
  margin: 0 auto;
  -webkit-transform-style: preserve-3d;
  -moz-transform-style: preserve-3d;
  transform-style: preserve-3d;
  transition: transform 0.5s ease;
}
.card--front {
  z-index: 10;
} 

.padded {
  padding: 0 5px;
  font-size: 12px;
  text-align: center;
}
.cci-press-card {
  width: 260px; 
  height: 400px;
  margin: 0 auto;
  font-family: "Lucida Grande", sans-serif;
  background: #924b4e;
  border-radius: 8px;
  border-bottom: 3px solid #57060a;
  position: absolute;
  -webkit-backface-visibility: hidden;
  -moz-backface-visibility: hidden;
  backface-visibility: hidden;
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__header {
  height: 13px;
  padding: 20px;
  font-size: 20px;
  color: ghostwhite;
  line-height: 1;
  font-weight: 700;
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__header:before {
  content: "Author";
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__header:after {
  content: "Press Card";
  color: #652327;
  float: right;
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__content {
  height: 140px;
  padding: 20px;
  font-size: 20px;
  background: #444444 url('http://txgarage.com/images/2014/10/justin-wegner.jpg') no-repeat;
  background-position-x: 0px;
  background-size: cover;
  transition: background-position-x 1s ease-out;
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__content .journalist-name:before {
  content: attr(data-journalist-name) "\A\A";
  color: ghostwhite;
  width: 100%;
  clear: both;
  display: block;
  font-weight: 700;
  text-shadow: 2px 2px 3px #333;
}
.cci-press-card .journalist-title a {
  display: block;
  font-size: 16px;
  color: ghostwhite;
  width: 100%;
  clear: both;
  text-decoration: none;
  text-shadow: 2px 2px 3px #333;
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__footer {
  padding: 0 20px; 
  color: white;
}
.press-card__footer h4 {
  font-weight: 100;
}
.press-card__footer h4 a {
  color: #fff;
  text-decoration: none;
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__footer .article-link {
  margin-bottom: 10px;
  padding-top: 10px;
  text-align: justify;
  color: #f1f1f1;
}
.rotate-3d {
  -webkit-transform: rotateY(180deg);
  -moz-transform: rotateY(180deg);
  transform: rotateY(180deg);
}
.z-up {
  z-index: 10;
}
.animated {
  -webkit-animation-fill-mode: both;
  -moz-animation-fill-mode: both;
  -ms-animation-fill-mode: both;
  -o-animation-fill-mode: both;
  animation-fill-mode: both;
  -webkit-animation-duration: 1s;
  -moz-animation-duration: 1s;
  -ms-animation-duration: 1s;
  -o-animation-duration: 1s;
  animation-duration: 1s;
}
@-webkit-keyframes fadeInLeft {
  0% {
    opacity: 0;
    -webkit-transform: translateX(-20px);
  }
  100% {
    opacity: 1;
    -webkit-transform: translateX(0);
  }
}
@-moz-keyframes fadeInLeft {
  0% {
    opacity: 0;
    -moz-transform: translateX(-20px);
  }
  100% {
    opacity: 1;
    -moz-transform: translateX(0);
  }
}
@-o-keyframes fadeInLeft {
  0% {
    opacity: 0;
    -o-transform: translateX(-20px);
  }
  100% {
    opacity: 1;
    -o-transform: translateX(0);
  }
}
@keyframes fadeInLeft {
  0% {
    opacity: 0;
    transform: translateX(-20px);
  }
  100% {
    opacity: 1;
    transform: translateX(0);
  }
}
.fadeInLeft {
  -webkit-animation-name: fadeInLeft;
  -moz-animation-name: fadeInLeft;
  -o-animation-name: fadeInLeft;
  animation-name: fadeInLeft;
}

@media screen and (max-width: 480px) {
 .inner-gbl { display: none; }
}
</style>]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>good-bad-list</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[<div class="cci-press-card__wrap">
  <div class="cci-press-card card--front"> 
    <header class="press-card__header"></header>
    <section class="press-card__content">
      <div class="journalist-name animated fadeInLeft" data-journalist-name="Justin Wegner"></div>
      <span class="journalist-title">
        <a href="http://twitter.com/"></a>
      </span>
    </section>
    <footer class="press-card__footer">
      <div class="article-link">
        Justin is a Sr. Web Designer at Dealertrack Technologies with a true passion for family, anything outdoors and all things about vehicles. This gives him a great perspective on off-road vehicles although he's a big car enthusiast as well.
      </div>
    </footer>
  </div>
</div>]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_thumbnail_id</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[11628]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_wpas_done_all</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_aioseop_keywords</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[2016 ford explorer, la auto show, la, auto show, 2016, ford, explorer, suv, ]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:comment>
			<wp:comment_id>13408</wp:comment_id>
			<wp:comment_author><![CDATA[Dustin]]></wp:comment_author>
			<wp:comment_author_email>dustywm@yahoo.ca</wp:comment_author_email>
			<wp:comment_author_url></wp:comment_author_url>
			<wp:comment_author_IP>70.72.88.26</wp:comment_author_IP>
			<wp:comment_date>2014-11-20 20:45:34</wp:comment_date>
			<wp:comment_date_gmt>2014-11-21 01:45:34</wp:comment_date_gmt>
			<wp:comment_content><![CDATA[Just too bad about the front end  those headlamps amd fog lamps look like they should be on a $15,000 car. Not on a $60,000 SUV. The grill is not designed well... and the new rear lamps look cheap and a last minute thought. This vehicle, though full of new and exciting features,  doesn't look much like a 2016 semi-luxury vehicle. Here's hoping 2017 will bring a much needed emergency face lift.]]></wp:comment_content>
			<wp:comment_approved>1</wp:comment_approved>
			<wp:comment_type></wp:comment_type>
			<wp:comment_parent>0</wp:comment_parent>
			<wp:comment_user_id>0</wp:comment_user_id>
			<wp:commentmeta>
				<wp:meta_key>akismet_result</wp:meta_key>
				<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[false]]></wp:meta_value>
			</wp:commentmeta>
			<wp:commentmeta>
				<wp:meta_key>akismet_history</wp:meta_key>
				<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:4:{s:4:"time";d:1416534335.5213499;s:7:"message";s:28:"Akismet cleared this comment";s:5:"event";s:9:"check-ham";s:4:"user";s:0:"";}]]></wp:meta_value>
			</wp:commentmeta>
			<wp:commentmeta>
				<wp:meta_key>akismet_history</wp:meta_key>
				<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:4:{s:4:"time";d:1416831178.629523;s:7:"message";s:44:"admin changed the comment status to approved";s:5:"event";s:15:"status-approved";s:4:"user";s:5:"admin";}]]></wp:meta_value>
			</wp:commentmeta>
		</wp:comment>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Full Review of the 2015 Subaru BRZ Series.Blue</title>
		<link>http://txgarage.com/2014/11/full-review-of-the-2015-subaru-brz-series-blue/</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2014 16:26:12 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://txgarage.com/?p=11638</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[[caption id="attachment_11668" align="alignnone" width="300"]<a href="http://txgarage.com/2014/11/full-review-of-the-2015-subaru-brz-series-blue/2015-subaru-brz-series-blue-0028/" rel="attachment wp-att-11668"><img src="http://txgarage.com/images/2014/11/2015-Subaru-BRZ-Series-Blue-0028-300x300.jpg" alt="The 2015 Subaru BRZ Series.Blue" width="300" height="300" class="size-medium wp-image-11668" /></a> The 2015 Subaru BRZ Series.Blue[/caption]<p class="firstp">We’ve been lucky here at txGarage and have had many opportunities to get behind the wheel of this driver-focused sports car. We were in <a href="http://txgarage.com/2012/05/video-2013-scion-fr-s-las-vegas-preview-and-quick-drive/" title="2013 Scion FR-S — Las Vegas Preview and Quick Drive" target="_blank">Las Vegas for the U.S. launch of the Scion FR-S</a>, and since then, we’ve driven the FR-S and BRZ on many different occasions. This is by far one of my favorite vehicles on sale today, so my biggest questions are: what has Subaru done for 2015 to enhance the experience and distinguish itself from the FRS, and what is this Series.Blue stuff? The BRZ is coming in 3 trim levels starting with a Premium, then Limited, and finally the Series.Blue that we’re driving.  This limited production model will only net 1000 vehicles, 500 of which will come in a Crystal White Pearl paint color – like the one we’re driving - and 500 will be painted WR Blue Pearl. So let’s jump into some more details and see what this is coupe is all about.</p>

Looking inside the BRZ, you’ll definitely not mistake it for a luxury vehicle. This is a no-frills sports car. You don’t get fancy controls on the steering wheel; you don’t get a fancy digital dashboard. What you do get is a large, center-mounted tach, amazing feeling from the steering wheel, and an uninterrupted driving experience.

You can get some luxuries, though. Every 2015 BRZ comes standard with a 6.1-inch LCD touchscreen display with navigation and Bluetooth connectivity. When you opt into the Limited trim, you get some nice two-tone leather seats that can heat your rear-end on cold days. You also get leather on the steering wheel and door panels and a keyless start ignition.

Inside the Series.Blue, in addition to all you get with the Limited trim, you also get some simulated carbon fiber trim bits along the dash. These are actually pretty cheap looking, too. Not because of the material necessarily, but because it’s split into two pieces with an unattractive and very noticeable gap between them. This was something that stood out to me right away and I don’t remember it standing out so much or being an issue in other models I’ve driven. It wasn’t just me either, as many people I gave a ride to throughout the week mentioned it. Like I stated earlier though, this is no luxury vehicle. On the other hand, touches like the dual-tone leather and alcantara seats and matching blue stitching around the cockpit were very nice. With the Series.Blue, you also get a red STI inspired engine start button, which is pretty cool and stands out in the blue and black interior. 

<a href="http://txgarage.com/2014/11/full-review-of-the-2015-subaru-brz-series-blue/2015-subaru-brz-series-blue-0038/" rel="attachment wp-att-11678"><img src="http://txgarage.com/images/2014/11/2015-Subaru-BRZ-Series-Blue-0038-400x300.jpg" alt="2015-Subaru-BRZ-Series-Blue-0038" width="400" height="300" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-11678 img-bythree" /></a><a href="http://txgarage.com/2014/11/full-review-of-the-2015-subaru-brz-series-blue/2015-subaru-brz-series-blue-0036/" rel="attachment wp-att-11676"><img src="http://txgarage.com/images/2014/11/2015-Subaru-BRZ-Series-Blue-0036-400x300.jpg" alt="2015-Subaru-BRZ-Series-Blue-0036" width="400" height="300" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-11676 img-bythree" /></a><a href="http://txgarage.com/2014/11/full-review-of-the-2015-subaru-brz-series-blue/2015-subaru-brz-series-blue-0039/" rel="attachment wp-att-11679"><img src="http://txgarage.com/images/2014/11/2015-Subaru-BRZ-Series-Blue-0039-400x300.jpg" alt="2015-Subaru-BRZ-Series-Blue-0039" width="400" height="300" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-11679 img-bythree" /></a>

Despite having a few gripes with the interior, looking at the outside of this car is something I’ve never had a gripe with. Although I’ve heard lots of journalist express either a dislike of the interior or a feeling of wanting more drama; I’ve always liked the styling direction that Toyota and Subaru have chosen. The exciting news here is that everything that makes this exterior great has been amplified with the Series.Blue. This package comes packed with an exclusive combination of STI functional aerodynamic body enhancements. These include the front-lip spoiler, side-skirts, and rear diffuser. While these bits add extra downforce, they also reduce the coefficient of drag from 0.28 to 0.29 – which is about this much (picture me holding my arms out). You also get some black-painted STI 17-inch wheels that look really good on this Crystal White car with black trim bits.

All BRZ models for 2015 now also feature larger stainless steel exhaust tips and a new shark fin roof antenna. The new exhaust tips look better, but sound better as well. Overall, I’m still pretty pleased with the looks of the BRZ and I hope that they’re offering some of these STI bits as dealer accessories as they really amplify the athleticism of this car.

Now that we’ve spent some time looking at the outside and inside of this car, it’s time to look under the hood. The 2015 BRZ gets the same 2.0-liter 4-cylinder Boxer engine that generates the same 200-horsepower and 151-lb-ft of torque. You can still opt for a 6-speed automatic transmission – which has some of the best feeling and shifting paddle shifters out for a vehicle in its price range – or even much over its price range. Of course, our tester was equipped with the 6-speed manual transmission, as all Series.Blue cars are. When it comes to shifting feel and preciseness, Toyota and Subaru have figured it out with this car. The gear shifting is one of the things that really make this such an enjoyable car. There are many small, fun, and sporty cars that are absolutely ruined by a floppy and lose gear shifter.

One of the other great characteristics about these cars is their low weight and ultra-low center of gravity. This allows the car to be nimble and agile. Although you only get 200-horses under the hood, the car still feels quick because of its low weight. I’ll still stick with the statement I made in my original review of the FR-S that this car really needs a variant with about 50, or so, more horsepower. The chassis can definitely handle it and it would just add to the fun.   

Many people still ask what distinguishes the BRZ from the FR-S and besides minor interior differences; the only other major difference is their suspension setup. The BRZ borrows its rear suspension architecture from the <a href="http://txgarage.com/2014/04/video-on-the-track-with-the-2015-subaru-wrx-sti/" title="On the track with the 2015 Subaru WRX STI" target="_blank">Subaru WRX STI</a>. This effectively uses high-tensile steel in the upper structure which contributes to its low center of gravity. The chassis tuning takes maximum advantage of this ultra-low center of gravity and high-strength body structure. This allows Subaru to tune the suspension for both agility and compliant ride quality. This really shows on the streets of Dallas and around the DFW area where you have many rough roads and some very nice, new, smooth roads. On the rough roads, this car is much more livable than something like the Nissan 370Z Nismo which we drove a few weeks back, but when you do get on smooth roads or a nice track, the car really comes to life and feels like a proper sports car.

<a href="http://txgarage.com/2014/11/full-review-of-the-2015-subaru-brz-series-blue/2015-subaru-brz-series-blue-0034/" rel="attachment wp-att-11674"><img src="http://txgarage.com/images/2014/11/2015-Subaru-BRZ-Series-Blue-0034-400x300.jpg" alt="2015-Subaru-BRZ-Series-Blue-0034" width="400" height="300" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-11674 img-bythree" /></a><a href="http://txgarage.com/2014/11/full-review-of-the-2015-subaru-brz-series-blue/2015-subaru-brz-series-blue-0032/" rel="attachment wp-att-11672"><img src="http://txgarage.com/images/2014/11/2015-Subaru-BRZ-Series-Blue-0032-400x300.jpg" alt="2015-Subaru-BRZ-Series-Blue-0032" width="400" height="300" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-11672 img-bythree" /></a><a href="http://txgarage.com/2014/11/full-review-of-the-2015-subaru-brz-series-blue/2015-subaru-brz-series-blue-0024/" rel="attachment wp-att-11664"><img src="http://txgarage.com/images/2014/11/2015-Subaru-BRZ-Series-Blue-0024-400x300.jpg" alt="2015-Subaru-BRZ-Series-Blue-0024" width="400" height="300" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-11664 img-bythree" /></a>

Speaking of the 370Z, you’re probably wondering exactly what’s out there that competes with the BRZ and FR-S. Definitely not the Nissan, at least not directly, as it costs almost twice as much and has a big V6 engine with much more power. You might look at the <a href="http://txgarage.com/2013/09/full-review-of-the-2013-hyundai-genesis-coupe-2-0t-r-spec/" title="Full Review of the 2013 Hyundai Genesis Coupe 2.0t R-Spec" target="_blank">Hyundai Genesis Coupe</a> and this would be a good comparison pitting the 2.0 Boxer vs the 2.0 turbo in the Genesis. The Hyundai would take the trophy if it came down to power only, but its larger size and much heavier body means you’re not having quite as much fun in the corners. Also, Hyundai still needs to do some work on their manual transmissions as it’s not even close to the feel of that in the BRZ. The <a href="http://txgarage.com/2012/06/mazda-mx5-special-edition-a-quick-drive-with-txgarage/" title="Mazda MX5 Special Edition a Quick Drive with txGarage" target="_blank">Mazda MX-5</a> is always a great benchmark although the BRZ does have rear-seats, even though for the most part they are unusable. I’m excited to see how the new MX-5 feels and drives, but for now, the BRZ is still just better in my opinion.

That might be about it as far as direct competition for this car goes. When you consider the base MSRP of just $25,695 or all the way up to our Series.Blue trim which topped the scales at just $30,285, this is one great sports car for not a whole lot of money. Of course, if you’re like me with a larger family, it doesn’t make sense to own a car like this. However, if I were in the market for a sports car today, it would be hard to look past the BRZ or the FR-S. As a matter of fact, this Series.Blue the way our tester was spec’d out, is exactly what I’d want. Unfortunately, as is the case with most limited production vehicles, all 1,000 vehicles have already sold out and you can’t even see it as a trim on Subaru’s website.

[gallery columns="5" ids="11681,11680,11679,11678,11677,11676,11675,11674,11673,11672,11671,11670,11669,11668,11667,11666,11665,11664,11663,11662,11661,11660,11659,11658,11657,11656,11655,11654,11653,11652,11651,11650,11649,11648,11647,11646,11645,11644,11643,11642,11641"]]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>11638</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2014-11-24 11:26:12</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2014-11-24 16:26:12</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>full-review-of-the-2015-subaru-brz-series-blue</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="2015"><![CDATA[2015]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="2015-brz"><![CDATA[2015 brz]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="blue"><![CDATA[blue]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="blue-series"><![CDATA[blue series]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="brz"><![CDATA[BRZ]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="brz"><![CDATA[BRZ]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="brz-sti"><![CDATA[brz sti]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="car-reviews"><![CDATA[Car Reviews]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="coupe"><![CDATA[coupe]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="fr-s"><![CDATA[fr-s]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="frs"><![CDATA[frs]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="series-blue"><![CDATA[series blue]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="sports-car"><![CDATA[sports car]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="sti"><![CDATA[sti]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="sti-brz"><![CDATA[sti brz]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="subaru"><![CDATA[subaru]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="subaru-2"><![CDATA[Subaru]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="subaru-brz"><![CDATA[subaru brz]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="top-review"><![CDATA[Top Review]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_knews_automated</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[0]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>postdata</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[2015|Subaru|BRZ]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>good-bad-list</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[<div class="cci-press-card__wrap">
  <div class="cci-press-card card--front"> 
    <header class="press-card__header"></header>
    <section class="press-card__content">
      <div class="journalist-name animated fadeInLeft" data-journalist-name="Adam Moore"></div>
      <span class="journalist-title">
        <a href="http://twitter.com/adamaoc">
          @adamaoc
        </a>
      </span>
    </section>
    <footer class="press-card__footer">
      <div class="article-link">
        Web Dev for DealerTrack Tech - Writer and auto reviewer with @txGarage - Co-founder of @BensHeart Foundation - Family man first - love tech, cars, and politics
Dallas, TX 
      </div>
    </footer>
  </div>
</div>]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_aioseop_title</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[Full Review of the 2015 Subaru BRZ Series.Blue]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_aioseop_description</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[txGarage - New. Reviews. Passion. - Texas Automotive Reviews : We’ve been lucky here at txGarage and have had many opportunities to get behind the wheel of this driver-focused sports car. We were in Las Vegas for the U.S. launch of the Scion FR-S, and since then, we’ve driven the FR-S and BRZ on many different occasions. This is by far one of my favorite vehicles on sale today, so my biggest questions are: what has Subaru done for 2015 to enhance the experience and distinguish itself from the FRS, and what is this Series.Blue stuff? The BRZ is coming in 3 trim levels starting with a Premium, then Limited, and finally the Series.Blue that we’re driving.  This limited production model will only net 1000 vehicles, 500 of which will come in a Crystal White Pearl paint color – like the one we’re driving - and 500 will be painted WR Blue Pearl. So let’s jump into some more details and see what this is coupe is all about.]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_ttscj_header_code</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[<style>
.post h1 {
  font-size: 27px;
}
.entry-content del { 
text-decoration: none;
font-size: 17px;
line-height: 26px;
}
.entry-content h2:first-child {
  text-align: center; 
  line-height: 1.8;
  font-size: 18px;
  letter-spacing: 1px;
  margin-bottom: 16px;
}
.img-bytwo {
  box-sizing: border-box;
width: 50% !important;
margin-bottom: 16px;
float: left;
padding-right: 1em;
padding-top: 1em;
padding-bottom: 1em;
}

.img-bythree {
  float: left;
  width: 33.33%;
  margin-bottom: 1em;
}

.entry-content .alignleft  {
  float: left;
}
.entry-content p {
font-size: 16px;
font-weight: 100;
letter-spacing: 1px;
line-height: 24px;
}
.entry-content  p:first-child {
font-size: 17px;
line-height: 26px;
}

body .entry-content p.firstp {
  font-size: 17px;
  line-height: 24px;
}

.entry-content .clear {
	clear: none;
}

/* === CCI Journalist Press Card === */
/* === CCI Journalist Press Card === */
.inner-gbl {
  overflow: hidden; 
}
.inner-gbl > h4 {
  display: none; 
}
.cci-press-card__wrap {
  position: relative;
  width: 260px;
  height: 410px;
  margin: 0 auto;
  -webkit-transform-style: preserve-3d;
  -moz-transform-style: preserve-3d;
  transform-style: preserve-3d;
  transition: transform 0.5s ease;
}
.card--front {
  z-index: 10;
} 

.padded {
  padding: 0 5px;
  font-size: 12px;
  text-align: center;
}
.cci-press-card {
  width: 260px; 
  height: 400px;
  margin: 0 auto;
  font-family: "Lucida Grande", sans-serif;
  background: #924b4e;
  border-radius: 8px;
  border-bottom: 3px solid #57060a;
  position: absolute;
  -webkit-backface-visibility: hidden;
  -moz-backface-visibility: hidden;
  backface-visibility: hidden;
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__header {
  height: 13px;
  padding: 20px;
  font-size: 20px;
  color: ghostwhite;
  line-height: 1;
  font-weight: 700;
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__header:before {
  content: "Author";
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__header:after {
  content: "Press Card";
  color: #652327;
  float: right;
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__content {
  height: 140px;
  padding: 20px;
  font-size: 20px;
  background: #444444 url('http://txgarage.com/images/2013/11/dallas-75-back.jpg') no-repeat;
  background-position-x: 0px;
  background-size: cover;
  transition: background-position-x 1s ease-out;
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__content .journalist-name:before {
  content: attr(data-journalist-name) "\A\A";
  color: ghostwhite;
  width: 100%;
  clear: both;
  display: block;
  font-weight: 700;
  text-shadow: 2px 2px 3px #333;
}
.cci-press-card .journalist-title a {
  display: block;
  font-size: 16px;
  color: ghostwhite;
  width: 100%;
  clear: both;
  text-decoration: none;
  text-shadow: 2px 2px 3px #333;
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__footer {
  padding: 0 20px; 
  color: white;
}
.press-card__footer h4 {
  font-weight: 100;
}
.press-card__footer h4 a {
  color: #fff;
  text-decoration: none;
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__footer .article-link {
  margin-bottom: 10px;
  padding-top: 10px;
  text-align: justify;
  color: #f1f1f1;
}
.rotate-3d {
  -webkit-transform: rotateY(180deg);
  -moz-transform: rotateY(180deg);
  transform: rotateY(180deg);
}
.z-up {
  z-index: 10;
}
.animated {
  -webkit-animation-fill-mode: both;
  -moz-animation-fill-mode: both;
  -ms-animation-fill-mode: both;
  -o-animation-fill-mode: both;
  animation-fill-mode: both;
  -webkit-animation-duration: 1s;
  -moz-animation-duration: 1s;
  -ms-animation-duration: 1s;
  -o-animation-duration: 1s;
  animation-duration: 1s;
}
@-webkit-keyframes fadeInLeft {
  0% {
    opacity: 0;
    -webkit-transform: translateX(-20px);
  }
  100% {
    opacity: 1;
    -webkit-transform: translateX(0);
  }
}
@-moz-keyframes fadeInLeft {
  0% {
    opacity: 0;
    -moz-transform: translateX(-20px);
  }
  100% {
    opacity: 1;
    -moz-transform: translateX(0);
  }
}
@-o-keyframes fadeInLeft {
  0% {
    opacity: 0;
    -o-transform: translateX(-20px);
  }
  100% {
    opacity: 1;
    -o-transform: translateX(0);
  }
}
@keyframes fadeInLeft {
  0% {
    opacity: 0;
    transform: translateX(-20px);
  }
  100% {
    opacity: 1;
    transform: translateX(0);
  }
}
.fadeInLeft {
  -webkit-animation-name: fadeInLeft;
  -moz-animation-name: fadeInLeft;
  -o-animation-name: fadeInLeft;
  animation-name: fadeInLeft;
}

@media screen and (max-width: 480px) {
 .inner-gbl { display: none; }
}
</style>
]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_thumbnail_id</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[11655]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_wpas_done_all</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_aioseop_keywords</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[2015, subaru, brz, 2015 brz, subaru brz, frs, fr-s, series blue, series.blue, blue series, blue, coupe, sports car, sti, sti brz, brz sti, luxury, scion, texas]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Quick Look at 2015 Ford F-350 King Ranch</title>
		<link>http://txgarage.com/2014/11/quick-look-at-2015-ford-f-350-king-ranch/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2014 18:58:12 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[JustinWegner]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://txgarage.com/?p=11686</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[[caption id="attachment_11687" align="alignnone" width="400"]<a href="http://txgarage.com/2014/11/quick-look-at-2015-ford-f-350-king-ranch/2015-ford-superduty-f350-kingranch-001/" rel="attachment wp-att-11687"><img src="http://txgarage.com/images/2014/11/2015-Ford-SuperDuty-F350-KingRanch-001-400x300.jpg" alt="The 2015 Ford Super Duty F-350 King Ranch" width="400" height="300" class="size-medium wp-image-11687" /></a> The 2015 Ford Super Duty F-350 King Ranch[/caption]<p class="firstp">The truth can hurt sometimes but it can also bring around some of the best outcomes. I think Ford is on it. I was never a fan of the 2000 model Ford Trucks this was more of a Chevrolet Decade for me, but I must say 2014 - 2015 has brought some seriously great looking Ford’s in the line-up. The one I am talking about specifically is the 2015 F-350 Lariat King Ranch Edition aka “Best of the Best”. </p>

The appearance has changed just enough on these trucks to make me notice a difference. I haven’t liked the older models because without the proper lift and tire size this truck can seem ‘squatty’. But with the upgraded suspension and a tweak in the body, it seems that they have hit the golden ration for me. And is almost overnight making me want a big Ford Truck - the F-150, F-250 or F-350. They’re all very strong and durable looking. Which when I get in the cab of a truck, I don’t feel that, to me it’s just not a truck. I want to know that the truck I am driving will be there when I call for power and luxury. 

Under the hood isn’t a joke either. Typically the bigger the engine, the better you feel about yourself. With this 6.7L Power Stroke Turbo Diesel Engine you feel the power, it’s clear as day when you tap the throttle. Traditionally, when I have been a part of certain discussions about the old 7.1L engine, guys have raved about how that is ‘THE’ engine. And although that might be the case this 6.7L will get you where you need to go, hauling what you need to haul (rated for 19,000 pounds!!!) , all the while doing it comfortably and safely. This 6.7L engine delivers horsepower of 440 at 2800 rpm, with ease. 

<a href="http://txgarage.com/2014/11/quick-look-at-2015-ford-f-350-king-ranch/2015-ford-superduty-f350-kingranch-008/" rel="attachment wp-att-11694"><img src="http://txgarage.com/images/2014/11/2015-Ford-SuperDuty-F350-KingRanch-008-400x300.jpg" alt="2015-Ford-SuperDuty-F350-KingRanch-008" width="400" height="300" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-11694" /></a><a href="http://txgarage.com/2014/11/quick-look-at-2015-ford-f-350-king-ranch/2015-ford-superduty-f350-kingranch-007/" rel="attachment wp-att-11693"><img src="http://txgarage.com/images/2014/11/2015-Ford-SuperDuty-F350-KingRanch-007-225x300.jpg" alt="2015-Ford-SuperDuty-F350-KingRanch-007" width="225" height="300" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-11693" /></a><a href="http://txgarage.com/2014/11/quick-look-at-2015-ford-f-350-king-ranch/2015-ford-superduty-f350-kingranch-005/" rel="attachment wp-att-11691"><img src="http://txgarage.com/images/2014/11/2015-Ford-SuperDuty-F350-KingRanch-005-400x300.jpg" alt="2015-Ford-SuperDuty-F350-KingRanch-005" width="400" height="300" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-11691" /></a>

Now let’s talk about this King Ranch Edition, and what that means for interior. Well it basically means Luxury. My exact quote when I first climbed up in the truck was, “Finally, Ford with this 2015 model has mastered the King Ranch Edition Interior.” The reason I said that was because I have been in some 2006 models (around there) that have been King Ranch Edition and the interior was nice and rustic looking but as far as comfortability, it wasn't a truck I was willing to spend hours on end in. I have been down on the King Ranch for some hunting; it’s a well known ranch around Texas for sure, and I think this interior fits the bill for one of the nicest truck interiors I have been in. I could see myself hauling it down to the deer lease and back, and not feel like my body took a beating when I return. That’s just part of the interior. With the touch screen dash displaying all your music right at your fingertips in an elegant order, it’s definitely something that could probably get really dirty when rolling around Ranches all over Texas. I worry about how long it would take for something to get so dirty that it starts to lose connection with the display. Since it displays your music, backup camera and other things, this might be problematic. But this isn’t just this truck, it’s all electronics and one of my pet peeves, so it’s something I feel I have to notate. I will say the dashes they started putting in, in 2011 and building upon since is starting to look very appealing and functional all at the same time. Which I love. Overall, this interior is so nice. As a graphic designer and front-end developer at times, I look at this interior as one that’s come the furthest, right next to the Toyota Tundras and Tacomas. 

This truck is going to come at a price for sure. This model costs right at $65,478. With this comes a bunch of options, that are nice but not necessary for a work truck. But I will say, coming from someone whos been in a lot of 350s all across South Central, and North Texas, this was one hell of a truck! 

[gallery columns="5" ids="11695,11694,11693,11692,11691,11690,11689,11688,11687"]]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>11686</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2014-11-28 13:58:12</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2014-11-28 18:58:12</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>quick-look-at-2015-ford-f-350-king-ranch</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="2015"><![CDATA[2015]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="2015-ford-f-350"><![CDATA[2015 ford f-350]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="car-reviews"><![CDATA[Car Reviews]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="f-series"><![CDATA[f series]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="f-350"><![CDATA[f-350]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="f-350-superduty"><![CDATA[F-350]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="f350"><![CDATA[f350]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="ford"><![CDATA[ford]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="ford-2"><![CDATA[Ford]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="king-ranch"><![CDATA[King Ranch]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="kingranch"><![CDATA[kingranch]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="quick-drive-2"><![CDATA[Quick Drive]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="super-duty"><![CDATA[super duty]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="superduty"><![CDATA[SuperDuty]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="superduty-2"><![CDATA[superduty]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_knews_automated</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[0]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_thumbnail_id</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[11687]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_aioseop_title</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[Quick Look at 2015 Ford F-350 King Ranch]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_aioseop_description</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[txGarage - News. Reviews. Passion. - Texas Truck Reviews - The truth can hurt sometimes but it can also bring around some of the best outcomes. I think Ford is on it. I was never a fan of the 2000 model Ford Trucks this was more of a Chevrolet Decade for me, but I must say 2014 - 2015 has brought some seriously great looking Ford’s in the line-up. The one I am talking about specifically is the 2015 F-350 Lariat King Ranch Edition aka “Best of the Best”. ]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_aioseop_keywords</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[2015, ford, f-350, f350, superduty, super duty, king ranch, kingranch, f series, 2015 ford f-350]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>good-bad-list</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[<div class="cci-press-card__wrap">
  <div class="cci-press-card card--front"> 
    <header class="press-card__header"></header>
    <section class="press-card__content">
      <div class="journalist-name animated fadeInLeft" data-journalist-name="Justin Wegner"></div>
      <span class="journalist-title">
        <a href="http://twitter.com/"></a>
      </span>
    </section>
    <footer class="press-card__footer">
      <div class="article-link">
        Justin is a Sr. Web Designer at Dealertrack Technologies with a true passion for family, anything outdoors and all things about vehicles. This gives him a great perspective on off-road vehicles although he's a big car enthusiast as well.
      </div>
    </footer>
  </div>
</div>]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_ttscj_header_code</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[<style>
.post h1 {
  font-size: 27px;
}
.entry-content del { 
text-decoration: none;
font-size: 17px;
line-height: 26px;
}
.entry-content h2:first-child {
  text-align: center; 
  line-height: 1.8;
  font-size: 18px;
  letter-spacing: 1px;
  margin-bottom: 16px;
}
.wp-image-11518, .wp-image-11516 {
width: 50% !important;
margin-bottom: 16px;
float: left;
}

.entry-content .alignleft  {
  float: left;
}
.entry-content p {
font-size: 16px;
font-weight: 100;
letter-spacing: 1px;
line-height: 24px;
}
.entry-content  p:first-child {
font-size: 17px;
line-height: 26px;
}

body .entry-content p.firstp {
  font-size: 17px;
  line-height: 24px;
}


/* === CCI Journalist Press Card === */
/* === CCI Journalist Press Card === */
.inner-gbl {
  overflow: hidden; 
}
.inner-gbl > h4 {
  display: none; 
}
.cci-press-card__wrap {
  position: relative;
  width: 260px;
  height: 410px;
  margin: 0 auto;
  -webkit-transform-style: preserve-3d;
  -moz-transform-style: preserve-3d;
  transform-style: preserve-3d;
  transition: transform 0.5s ease;
}
.card--front {
  z-index: 10;
} 

.padded {
  padding: 0 5px;
  font-size: 12px;
  text-align: center;
}
.cci-press-card {
  width: 260px; 
  height: 400px;
  margin: 0 auto;
  font-family: "Lucida Grande", sans-serif;
  background: #924b4e;
  border-radius: 8px;
  border-bottom: 3px solid #57060a;
  position: absolute;
  -webkit-backface-visibility: hidden;
  -moz-backface-visibility: hidden;
  backface-visibility: hidden;
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__header {
  height: 13px;
  padding: 20px;
  font-size: 20px;
  color: ghostwhite;
  line-height: 1;
  font-weight: 700;
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__header:before {
  content: "Author";
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__header:after {
  content: "Press Card";
  color: #652327;
  float: right;
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__content {
  height: 140px;
  padding: 20px;
  font-size: 20px;
  background: #444444 url('http://txgarage.com/images/2014/10/justin-wegner.jpg') no-repeat;
  background-position-x: 0px;
  background-size: cover;
  transition: background-position-x 1s ease-out;
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__content .journalist-name:before {
  content: attr(data-journalist-name) "\A\A";
  color: ghostwhite;
  width: 100%;
  clear: both;
  display: block;
  font-weight: 700;
  text-shadow: 2px 2px 3px #333;
}
.cci-press-card .journalist-title a {
  display: block;
  font-size: 16px;
  color: ghostwhite;
  width: 100%;
  clear: both;
  text-decoration: none;
  text-shadow: 2px 2px 3px #333;
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__footer {
  padding: 0 20px; 
  color: white;
}
.press-card__footer h4 {
  font-weight: 100;
}
.press-card__footer h4 a {
  color: #fff;
  text-decoration: none;
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__footer .article-link {
  margin-bottom: 10px;
  padding-top: 10px;
  text-align: justify;
  color: #f1f1f1;
}
.rotate-3d {
  -webkit-transform: rotateY(180deg);
  -moz-transform: rotateY(180deg);
  transform: rotateY(180deg);
}
.z-up {
  z-index: 10;
}
.animated {
  -webkit-animation-fill-mode: both;
  -moz-animation-fill-mode: both;
  -ms-animation-fill-mode: both;
  -o-animation-fill-mode: both;
  animation-fill-mode: both;
  -webkit-animation-duration: 1s;
  -moz-animation-duration: 1s;
  -ms-animation-duration: 1s;
  -o-animation-duration: 1s;
  animation-duration: 1s;
}
@-webkit-keyframes fadeInLeft {
  0% {
    opacity: 0;
    -webkit-transform: translateX(-20px);
  }
  100% {
    opacity: 1;
    -webkit-transform: translateX(0);
  }
}
@-moz-keyframes fadeInLeft {
  0% {
    opacity: 0;
    -moz-transform: translateX(-20px);
  }
  100% {
    opacity: 1;
    -moz-transform: translateX(0);
  }
}
@-o-keyframes fadeInLeft {
  0% {
    opacity: 0;
    -o-transform: translateX(-20px);
  }
  100% {
    opacity: 1;
    -o-transform: translateX(0);
  }
}
@keyframes fadeInLeft {
  0% {
    opacity: 0;
    transform: translateX(-20px);
  }
  100% {
    opacity: 1;
    transform: translateX(0);
  }
}
.fadeInLeft {
  -webkit-animation-name: fadeInLeft;
  -moz-animation-name: fadeInLeft;
  -o-animation-name: fadeInLeft;
  animation-name: fadeInLeft;
}

@media screen and (max-width: 480px) {
 .inner-gbl { display: none; }
}
</style>]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>postdata</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[2015|Ford|F-350]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_wpas_done_all</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>San Antonio man buys first all-new 2015 Ford F-150 Truck</title>
		<link>http://txgarage.com/2014/12/san-antonio-man-buys-first-all-new-2015-ford-f-150-truck/</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2014 16:13:41 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[News]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://txgarage.com/?p=11698</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[[caption id="attachment_11699" align="alignnone" width="400"]<a href="http://txgarage.com/2014/12/san-antonio-man-buys-first-all-new-2015-ford-f-150-truck/2015-f-150/" rel="attachment wp-att-11699"><img src="http://txgarage.com/images/2014/12/US_15F150_hero-400x300.jpg" alt="2015 Ford F-150 Truck of Texas" width="400" height="300" class="size-medium wp-image-11699" /></a> 2015 Ford F-150 Truck of Texas[/caption]<p class="firstp">Just in time for Thanksgiving, San Antonio resident Tim Kingsbury will be the first buyer in the U.S. to receive Ford’s smartest, toughest and most capable F-150 ever during a ceremony Wednesday. An avid hunter and retired high school football coach, Kingsbury is the father of current Texas Tech Red Raiders football coach, Kliff Kingsbury.</p>

Using a military-grade aluminum for strength, and weighing up to 700 pounds less than current models, the all-new F-150 is 5 percent to 29 percent more fuel efficient than current F-150 models, depending on engine and driveline configuration on the combined cycle (city and highway).

Don't forget that this truck was named <a href="http://txgarage.com/2014/10/2015-truck-of-texas-texas-truck-rodeo-with-the-2015-ford-f-150/" title="2015 Truck of Texas – Texas Truck Rodeo with the 2015 Ford F-150">Truck of Texas</a> by us and the Texas Auto Writers Association. 
<div style="clear: both;"></div>]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>11698</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2014-12-01 11:13:41</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2014-12-01 16:13:41</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>san-antonio-man-buys-first-all-new-2015-ford-f-150-truck</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="2015"><![CDATA[2015]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="f-150"><![CDATA[f-150]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="ford"><![CDATA[ford]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="news"><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="texas-auto-news"><![CDATA[texas auto news]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="truck-of-texas"><![CDATA[Truck of Texas]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_knews_automated</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[0]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_aioseop_description</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[Just in time for Thanksgiving, San Antonio resident Tim Kingsbury will be the first buyer in the U.S. to receive Ford’s smartest, toughest and most capable F-150 ever during a ceremony Wednesday. An avid hunter and retired high school football coach, Kingsbury is the father of current Texas Tech Red Raiders football coach, Kliff Kingsbury.]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_aioseop_title</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[San Antonio man buys first all-new 2015 Ford F-150 Truck]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_ttscj_header_code</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[<style>
.post h1 {
  font-size: 27px;
  line-height: 1.3;
}
.entry-content del { 
text-decoration: none;
font-size: 17px;
line-height: 26px;
}
.entry-content h2:first-child {
  text-align: center; 
  line-height: 1.8;
  font-size: 18px;
  letter-spacing: 1px;
  margin-bottom: 16px;
}

.img-bytwo {
  box-sizing: border-box;
  width: 50% !important;
  margin-bottom: 16px;
  float: left;
  padding-right: 1em;
  padding-top: 1em;
  padding-bottom: 1em;
}

.img-bythree {
  float: left;
  width: 33.33%;
  margin-bottom: 1em;
}
html .entry-content .wp-att-11628 {
display: block;
width: 100%;
}
html .entry-content .wp-att-11628 img {
float: none !important;
max-width: 100%;
width: 400px;
margin: 0 auto;
padding: 0;
display: block;
}
.entry-content .alignleft  {
  float: left;
}
.entry-content p {
font-size: 16px;
font-weight: 100;
letter-spacing: 1px;
line-height: 24px;
}
.entry-content  p:first-child {
font-size: 17px;
line-height: 26px;
}

body .entry-content p.firstp {
  font-size: 17px;
  line-height: 24px;
}


/* === CCI Journalist Press Card === */
/* === CCI Journalist Press Card === */
.inner-gbl {
  overflow: hidden; 
}
.inner-gbl > h4 {
  display: none; 
}
.cci-press-card__wrap {
  position: relative;
  width: 260px;
  height: 410px;
  margin: 0 auto;
  -webkit-transform-style: preserve-3d;
  -moz-transform-style: preserve-3d;
  transform-style: preserve-3d;
  transition: transform 0.5s ease;
}
.card--front {
  z-index: 10;
} 

.padded {
  padding: 0 5px;
  font-size: 12px;
  text-align: center;
}
.cci-press-card {
  width: 260px; 
  height: 400px;
  margin: 0 auto;
  font-family: "Lucida Grande", sans-serif;
  background: #924b4e;
  border-radius: 8px;
  border-bottom: 3px solid #57060a;
  position: absolute;
  -webkit-backface-visibility: hidden;
  -moz-backface-visibility: hidden;
  backface-visibility: hidden;
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__header {
  height: 13px;
  padding: 20px;
  font-size: 20px;
  color: ghostwhite;
  line-height: 1;
  font-weight: 700;
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__header:before {
  content: "Author";
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__header:after {
  content: "Press Card";
  color: #652327;
  float: right;
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__content {
  height: 140px;
  padding: 20px;
  font-size: 20px;
  background: #444444 url('http://txgarage.com/images/2014/10/justin-wegner.jpg') no-repeat;
  background-position-x: 0px;
  background-size: cover;
  transition: background-position-x 1s ease-out;
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__content .journalist-name:before {
  content: attr(data-journalist-name) "\A\A";
  color: ghostwhite;
  width: 100%;
  clear: both;
  display: block;
  font-weight: 700;
  text-shadow: 2px 2px 3px #333;
}
.cci-press-card .journalist-title a {
  display: block;
  font-size: 16px;
  color: ghostwhite;
  width: 100%;
  clear: both;
  text-decoration: none;
  text-shadow: 2px 2px 3px #333;
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__footer {
  padding: 0 20px; 
  color: white;
}
.press-card__footer h4 {
  font-weight: 100;
}
.press-card__footer h4 a {
  color: #fff;
  text-decoration: none;
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__footer .article-link {
  margin-bottom: 10px;
  padding-top: 10px;
  text-align: justify;
  color: #f1f1f1;
}
.rotate-3d {
  -webkit-transform: rotateY(180deg);
  -moz-transform: rotateY(180deg);
  transform: rotateY(180deg);
}
.z-up {
  z-index: 10;
}
.animated {
  -webkit-animation-fill-mode: both;
  -moz-animation-fill-mode: both;
  -ms-animation-fill-mode: both;
  -o-animation-fill-mode: both;
  animation-fill-mode: both;
  -webkit-animation-duration: 1s;
  -moz-animation-duration: 1s;
  -ms-animation-duration: 1s;
  -o-animation-duration: 1s;
  animation-duration: 1s;
}
@-webkit-keyframes fadeInLeft {
  0% {
    opacity: 0;
    -webkit-transform: translateX(-20px);
  }
  100% {
    opacity: 1;
    -webkit-transform: translateX(0);
  }
}
@-moz-keyframes fadeInLeft {
  0% {
    opacity: 0;
    -moz-transform: translateX(-20px);
  }
  100% {
    opacity: 1;
    -moz-transform: translateX(0);
  }
}
@-o-keyframes fadeInLeft {
  0% {
    opacity: 0;
    -o-transform: translateX(-20px);
  }
  100% {
    opacity: 1;
    -o-transform: translateX(0);
  }
}
@keyframes fadeInLeft {
  0% {
    opacity: 0;
    transform: translateX(-20px);
  }
  100% {
    opacity: 1;
    transform: translateX(0);
  }
}
.fadeInLeft {
  -webkit-animation-name: fadeInLeft;
  -moz-animation-name: fadeInLeft;
  -o-animation-name: fadeInLeft;
  animation-name: fadeInLeft;
}

@media screen and (max-width: 480px) {
 .inner-gbl { display: none; }
}
</style>]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_aioseop_keywords</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[2015, ford, f-150, fist sold, san antonio, 2015 ford f-150, texas auto news, news, texas]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_thumbnail_id</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[11699]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_wpas_done_all</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Full Review of the 2015 Ford Expedition King Ranch</title>
		<link>http://txgarage.com/2014/12/full-review-of-the-2015-ford-expedition-king-ranch/</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2014 12:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://txgarage.com/?p=11705</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[[caption id="attachment_11722" align="alignnone" width="400"]<a href="http://txgarage.com/2014/12/full-review-of-the-2015-ford-expedition-king-ranch/2015-ford-expedition-kingranch-0017/" rel="attachment wp-att-11722"><img src="http://txgarage.com/images/2014/12/2015-Ford-Expedition-KingRanch-0017-400x266.jpg" alt="The 2015 Ford Expedition King Ranch" width="400" height="266" class="size-medium wp-image-11722" /></a> The 2015 Ford Expedition King Ranch[/caption] <p class="firstp">Reviewing cars has its perks. Not just driving a different vehicle every week, but also having the opportunity to request a specific vehicle for a specific occasion. If you’ve been following for a while, you’ll know we usually try to take special vehicles out anytime we’re planning a road trip or a family getaway. For the past few years, I’ve been lucky enough to score some really great family vehicles to haul my wife and four kids around during these times. I specifically asked for the new Expedition this week as it’s Thanksgiving week and we’re traveling with the family. Thankfully, Ford was able to make it happen. My time with this big SUV was spent traveling with the family, giving me even more insight on how this vehicle would be to live with everyday for the average, larger, Texas family. The Expedition is the biggest SUV in the Ford lineup today since dropping the Excursion in 2005. This is the last traditional body-on-frame SUV in the Ford lineup being based off the F-150’s platform. The Explorer is now based on a car platform, the same as the Taurus, and although it’s still a great family vehicle, you’ll actually see more families looking at the Expedition for it’s extra size and capabilities.</p>
 
The first generation was introduced to the market as a 1997-year model. This 2015 refresh keeps it classified as a 3rd generation, but comes with some much-needed updates inside and out. Let’s check out what they’ve done inside this big SUV to make it more attractive to the modern SUV consumer.
 
Inside the Expedition, you get a similar layout to the outgoing models, but you’ll get a lot of updated materials throughout. You get standard seating for 8-passengers with an optional 7-passenger configuration. There are not many vehicles out today that hold up to 8-passengers and I was definitely able to take advantage of the extra room while carting the family around during our Thanksgiving break. If you don’t need all the room for people, you can also fold down the 3rd-row. In our King Ranch, this was done with a touch of a button, giving you even more cargo room. The 2nd-row split bench can also be folded for a maximum of 108.3 cubic feet of storage.  In comparison, the new Chevrolet Tahoe, standard length, has 94.7 cubic feet of storage.

<a href="http://txgarage.com/2014/12/full-review-of-the-2015-ford-expedition-king-ranch/15expedition-kingranch_ip_hr/" rel="attachment wp-att-11733"><img src="http://txgarage.com/images/2014/12/15Expedition-KingRanch_IP_HR-400x266.jpg" alt="15Expedition-KingRanch_IP_HR" width="400" height="266" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-11733 img-bytwo" /></a><a href="http://txgarage.com/2014/12/full-review-of-the-2015-ford-expedition-king-ranch/15expedition-kingranch_seats_hr/" rel="attachment wp-att-11734"><img src="http://txgarage.com/images/2014/12/15Expedition-KingRanch_seats_HR-400x266.jpg" alt="15Expedition-KingRanch_seats_HR" width="400" height="266" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-11734 img-bytwo" /></a>
 
Also added for the 2015 model year is Ford’s SYNC with MyFord Touch and an 8-inch touch-screen center display. The SYNC system is optional in the XLT trim, but comes standard with Limited, King Ranch, and Platinum models. You also get 2 LCDs on either side of the speedometer. These 4.2-inch displays show you all kinds of information from your fuel economy, radio settings, vehicle info, to navigation details. This is nothing new for most vehicles in the Ford lineup, but is a much-appreciated update for the Expedition.  
 
Our King Ranch trim provided us with a beautiful interior trimmed in Mesa Brown leather embossed with the famous Running W and features Kingsville stitching. You also get some really nice looking wood trim and an over feel of ruggedness and luxury throughout. The King Ranch interior transforms this family SUV into a full on luxury vehicle. 
 
Looking at the exterior, you’ll notice the 2015 has a new and more aggressive looking front end. This front end is made to convey a bolder look and distinguish this as the flagship of Ford’s SUV lineup. The grille and lower fascia come in a finish unique to each of the four models, including the all-new luxury Platinum trim. Also available are new projector headlamps and standard LED fog lamps to help enhance performance in an elegant, contemporary style. Our King Ranch model comes with exterior badges and two-tone paint rounding off its unique trim.
 
With all the added features to the 2015 Expedition, there’s one thing you can’t get that you could with the 2014. Under the hood, your only powertrain option is the 3.5-liter EcoBoost V6 engine; no longer can you get a V8. This engine has been proven in both the F-150 and Explorer as a premium engine delivering V8 performance and V6 fuel economy. It only makes sense that this would be the one powertrain offered. The EcoBoost engine pushes out 365-horsepower and a best-in-class 420-lb-ft. of torque. The 5.3-liter V8 available in the new Tahoe pushes 355-hp and 383-lb-ft. of torque in comparison.

<a href="http://txgarage.com/2014/12/full-review-of-the-2015-ford-expedition-king-ranch/2015-ford-expedition-kingranch-0013/" rel="attachment wp-att-11718"><img src="http://txgarage.com/images/2014/12/2015-Ford-Expedition-KingRanch-0013-400x266.jpg" alt="2015-Ford-Expedition-KingRanch-0013" width="400" height="266" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-11718 img-bythree" /></a><a href="http://txgarage.com/2014/12/full-review-of-the-2015-ford-expedition-king-ranch/2015-ford-expedition-kingranch-0019/" rel="attachment wp-att-11724"><img src="http://txgarage.com/images/2014/12/2015-Ford-Expedition-KingRanch-0019-400x266.jpg" alt="2015-Ford-Expedition-KingRanch-0019" width="400" height="266" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-11724 img-bythree" /></a><a href="http://txgarage.com/2014/12/full-review-of-the-2015-ford-expedition-king-ranch/2015-ford-expedition-kingranch-0018/" rel="attachment wp-att-11723"><img src="http://txgarage.com/images/2014/12/2015-Ford-Expedition-KingRanch-0018-400x266.jpg" alt="2015-Ford-Expedition-KingRanch-0018" width="400" height="266" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-11723 img-bythree" /></a>
 
This engine is hooked up with a 6-speed SelectShift automatic transmission and, when equipped with the towing package, has best-in-class max towing of 9,200-lbs. Although I didn’t have the opportunity to tow anything during my week reviewing this SUV, I have had the opportunity to tow with many different setups in the F-150 and it’s made effortless with this engine and Ford’s towing control systems. 
 
Whether you’re driving this vehicle round the big city or down backcountry roads, you’re going to feel right at home. The suspension is soft ridding your back of any harsh roads you may encounter. You still have good steering feel, though, allowing you to take corners or make highway maneuvers with the utmost confidence. When it’s time to make a pass, or get up and go for any reason, the EcoBoost is your best friend. You have plenty of power on tap to move this big, heavy vehicle down the road even when it’s loaded down. Of course, putting that foot down doesn’t help with fuel economy but the EcoBoost tries to help out there as well. The 4x2 vehicles were rated at 16-mpg city and 22-mpg highway. During our time with the Expedition, we found our average consumption closer to high 19’s, which is really good for this size of vehicle. In comparison, during our time with the Tahoe we average in the low 18’s.
 
So the drive is good, the interior is updated and much more luxurious, and you get some great looks, but how does all that translate to a better ride for the family? When you’re dealing with hauling around 4, or more, kids plus a significant other in the passenger seat, most smaller SUVs can feel a bit crowded. Even your good 3-row SUVs get pretty tight when packed to their max of 6 passengers. Having the extra room makes long road trip or every day tasks like getting in and out just that much easier. 
 
You also have a lot of great utility and technology with this new Expedition that helps keep the kids happy. For example, you get multiple USB adapters to keep all your gadgets charged. You also get a full 110v plug in the second row ready to power whatever electronics you want to throw at it. Our review vehicle didn’t have them, but you can also get a DVD entertainment system with screens built into the headrests.  
 
There is really only one main competitor left for the Expedition and that’s the vehicle I’ve constantly been mentioning during this review. The Chevrolet Tahoe/Suburban is really the only other vehicle out there with the size or seating capacity to match. The Tahoe is a great family SUV and is packed with luxury and technology just like this Expedition. You will be looking at spending a bit more money with the Chevrolet, though. The base price of a Tahoe is  $47,240 and the base Expedition is $43,585. If you’re looking at something equipped like our King Ranch you’re looking just over $57k on Ford’s side and just over $60k on Chevy’s. 
 
I’m often asked if I ever have a hard time giving vehicles back at the end of the week when it’s time to swap into the next ride. My answer is almost always no, as I’m eager to jump into the next new vehicle. With this 2015 Expedition, though, it wasn’t just me but my whole family was sad to see it go. This is definitely a vehicle we would aspire to that would be able to fit all the needs of our family. This is one vehicle that will really be missed in our household and I couldn’t recommend it enough for any family with the means to get one.


[gallery columns="5" ids="11706,11707,11708,11709,11710,11711,11712,11713,11714,11715,11716,11717,11718,11719,11720,11721,11722,11723,11724,11725,11726,11727,11728,11729,11730,11731"]]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>11705</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2014-12-15 07:30:00</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2014-12-15 12:30:00</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>full-review-of-the-2015-ford-expedition-king-ranch</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="2015"><![CDATA[2015]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="3-row"><![CDATA[3 row]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="7-passenger"><![CDATA[7 passenger]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="8-passenger"><![CDATA[8-passenger]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="car-reviews"><![CDATA[Car Reviews]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="ecoboost"><![CDATA[ecoboost]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="economy"><![CDATA[economy]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="engine"><![CDATA[engine]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="expedition"><![CDATA[Expedition]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="expedition-2"><![CDATA[expedition]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="f-series"><![CDATA[f series]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="ford"><![CDATA[ford]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="ford-2"><![CDATA[Ford]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="king-ranch"><![CDATA[King Ranch]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="mpg"><![CDATA[mpg]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="suv"><![CDATA[suv]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="tow"><![CDATA[tow]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="towing"><![CDATA[towing]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_knews_automated</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[0]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>good-bad-list</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[<div class="cci-press-card__wrap">
  <div class="cci-press-card card--front"> 
    <header class="press-card__header"></header>
    <section class="press-card__content">
      <div class="journalist-name animated fadeInLeft" data-journalist-name="Adam Moore"></div>
      <span class="journalist-title">
        <a href="http://twitter.com/adamaoc">
          @adamaoc
        </a>
      </span>
    </section>
    <footer class="press-card__footer">
      <div class="article-link">
        Web Dev for DealerTrack Tech - Writer and auto reviewer with @txGarage - Co-founder of @BensHeart Foundation - Family man first - love tech, cars, and politics
Dallas, TX 
      </div>
    </footer>
  </div>
</div>]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_aioseop_title</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[Full Review of the 2015 Ford Expedition King Ranch]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_ttscj_header_code</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[<style>
.post h1 {
  font-size: 27px;
}
.entry-content del { 
text-decoration: none;
font-size: 17px;
line-height: 26px;
}
.entry-content h2:first-child {
  text-align: center; 
  line-height: 1.8;
  font-size: 18px;
  letter-spacing: 1px;
  margin-bottom: 16px;
}
.img-bytwo {
  box-sizing: border-box;
width: 50% !important;
margin-bottom: 16px;
float: left;
padding-right: 1em;
padding-top: 1em;
padding-bottom: 1em;
}

.img-bythree {
  float: left;
  width: 33.33%;
  margin-bottom: 1em;
}

.entry-content .alignleft  {
  float: left;
}
.entry-content p {
font-size: 16px;
font-weight: 100;
letter-spacing: 1px;
line-height: 24px;
}
.entry-content  p:first-child {
font-size: 17px;
line-height: 26px;
}

body .entry-content p.firstp {
  font-size: 17px;
  line-height: 24px;
}

.entry-content .clear {
	clear: none;
}

/* === CCI Journalist Press Card === */
/* === CCI Journalist Press Card === */
.inner-gbl {
  overflow: hidden; 
}
.inner-gbl > h4 {
  display: none; 
}
.cci-press-card__wrap {
  position: relative;
  width: 260px;
  height: 410px;
  margin: 0 auto;
  -webkit-transform-style: preserve-3d;
  -moz-transform-style: preserve-3d;
  transform-style: preserve-3d;
  transition: transform 0.5s ease;
}
.card--front {
  z-index: 10;
} 

.padded {
  padding: 0 5px;
  font-size: 12px;
  text-align: center;
}
.cci-press-card {
  width: 260px; 
  height: 400px;
  margin: 0 auto;
  font-family: "Lucida Grande", sans-serif;
  background: #924b4e;
  border-radius: 8px;
  border-bottom: 3px solid #57060a;
  position: absolute;
  -webkit-backface-visibility: hidden;
  -moz-backface-visibility: hidden;
  backface-visibility: hidden;
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__header {
  height: 13px;
  padding: 20px;
  font-size: 20px;
  color: ghostwhite;
  line-height: 1;
  font-weight: 700;
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__header:before {
  content: "Author";
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__header:after {
  content: "Press Card";
  color: #652327;
  float: right;
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__content {
  height: 140px;
  padding: 20px;
  font-size: 20px;
  background: #444444 url('http://txgarage.com/images/2013/11/dallas-75-back.jpg') no-repeat;
  background-position-x: 0px;
  background-size: cover;
  transition: background-position-x 1s ease-out;
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__content .journalist-name:before {
  content: attr(data-journalist-name) "\A\A";
  color: ghostwhite;
  width: 100%;
  clear: both;
  display: block;
  font-weight: 700;
  text-shadow: 2px 2px 3px #333;
}
.cci-press-card .journalist-title a {
  display: block;
  font-size: 16px;
  color: ghostwhite;
  width: 100%;
  clear: both;
  text-decoration: none;
  text-shadow: 2px 2px 3px #333;
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__footer {
  padding: 0 20px; 
  color: white;
}
.press-card__footer h4 {
  font-weight: 100;
}
.press-card__footer h4 a {
  color: #fff;
  text-decoration: none;
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__footer .article-link {
  margin-bottom: 10px;
  padding-top: 10px;
  text-align: justify;
  color: #f1f1f1;
}
.rotate-3d {
  -webkit-transform: rotateY(180deg);
  -moz-transform: rotateY(180deg);
  transform: rotateY(180deg);
}
.z-up {
  z-index: 10;
}
.animated {
  -webkit-animation-fill-mode: both;
  -moz-animation-fill-mode: both;
  -ms-animation-fill-mode: both;
  -o-animation-fill-mode: both;
  animation-fill-mode: both;
  -webkit-animation-duration: 1s;
  -moz-animation-duration: 1s;
  -ms-animation-duration: 1s;
  -o-animation-duration: 1s;
  animation-duration: 1s;
}
@-webkit-keyframes fadeInLeft {
  0% {
    opacity: 0;
    -webkit-transform: translateX(-20px);
  }
  100% {
    opacity: 1;
    -webkit-transform: translateX(0);
  }
}
@-moz-keyframes fadeInLeft {
  0% {
    opacity: 0;
    -moz-transform: translateX(-20px);
  }
  100% {
    opacity: 1;
    -moz-transform: translateX(0);
  }
}
@-o-keyframes fadeInLeft {
  0% {
    opacity: 0;
    -o-transform: translateX(-20px);
  }
  100% {
    opacity: 1;
    -o-transform: translateX(0);
  }
}
@keyframes fadeInLeft {
  0% {
    opacity: 0;
    transform: translateX(-20px);
  }
  100% {
    opacity: 1;
    transform: translateX(0);
  }
}
.fadeInLeft {
  -webkit-animation-name: fadeInLeft;
  -moz-animation-name: fadeInLeft;
  -o-animation-name: fadeInLeft;
  animation-name: fadeInLeft;
}

@media screen and (max-width: 480px) {
 .inner-gbl { display: none; }
}
</style>
]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_thumbnail_id</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[11722]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_aioseop_keywords</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[2015, ford, expedition, suv, 8 passenger, 7 passenger, 3 row, king ranch, f series, towing, tow, engine, ecoboost, economy, mpg, ]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_aioseop_description</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[txGarage - News. Reviews. Passion. - Texas Automotive Reviews :: Reviewing cars has its perks. Not just driving a different vehicle every week, but also having the opportunity to request a specific vehicle for a specific occasion. If you’ve been following for a while, you’ll know we usually try to take special vehicles out anytime we’re planning a road trip or a family getaway. For the past few years, I’ve been lucky enough to score some really great family vehicles to haul my wife and four kids around during these times.]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_wpas_done_all</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Full Review of the 2015 Acura TLX</title>
		<link>http://txgarage.com/2014/12/full-review-of-the-2015-acura-tlx/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2014 13:46:28 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://txgarage.com/?p=11739</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>Tech. Luxury. Thrill.</h2>

[caption id="attachment_11748" align="alignnone" width="400"]<a href="http://txgarage.com/2014/12/full-review-of-the-2015-acura-tlx/2015-acura-tlx-009/" rel="attachment wp-att-11748"><img src="http://txgarage.com/images/2014/12/2015-Acura-TLX-009-400x267.jpg" alt="The 2015 Acura TLX Luxury Sedan" width="400" height="267" class="size-medium wp-image-11748" /></a> The 2015 Acura TLX Luxury Sedan[/caption]<p class="firstp">My first experience with the Acura brand was back when I was in high school. I bought a used '88 Acura Integra Special, which I was lucky enough to pick up from an auction for only $750. I drove that car for 3-years before I sold it for $900 back in 2001. Owning this car was my not just my first exposure to the Acura brand, but was also one of the cars that helped me gain a great respect and admiration for enthusiast cars. Ever since then, I’ve been following the Acura brand from its ups and downs and am always excited to get behind the wheel of a new one. Throughout this time, one of my favorite vehicles they’ve made was the TSX, a cool and sporty sedan. For the 2015 model year, though, the TL and TSX have been replaced with this new sedan, the Acura TLX.</p>
 
The TLX is made to bring more luxury to the model, while still keeping that Acura thrill many owners have grown to love. So the question for me is have they pulled out too much sportiness in favor of luxury and what does that mean for guys like me who really liked the TSX?

Our review car was a top of the line with a 3.5-liter V6 engine pushing 290-horsepower through a 9-speed automatic transmission. It also had Acura’s SH-AWD, their Super Handling All-Wheel Drive system. The first thing that came to my mind reading this stat was 290-hp out of a V6 sedan doesn’t seem like a formula for sportiness. Also, I know we’ve moved out of the power wars in favor of a how many gears can you shove in a transmission war, but a 9-speed transmission seems a bit excessive.
 
In reality, though, the power from this V6 is more than adequate for this sedan and during daily driving, you would never guess you’re rowing through 9-gears. You also have Acura’s Integrated Dynamics system (IDS) which are driving modes you can choose from ranging from Econ mode, Normal, Sport, and Sport +. Keeping the vehicle in Econ mode allows you to stretch every mpg by deadening your throttle response and putting the engine into a more economical mindset. Switching to Sport or Sport + enhances steering feel, sharpens throttle response, and tightens response levels for the SH-AWD system. Being in Sport+ mode really makes you forget about being in a luxury sedan making the TLX feel like a true sport-sedan giving tribute to its TSX heritage.

<a href="http://txgarage.com/2014/12/full-review-of-the-2015-acura-tlx/2015-acura-tlx-0023/" rel="attachment wp-att-11762"><img src="http://txgarage.com/images/2014/12/2015-Acura-TLX-0023-400x267.jpg" alt="2015-Acura-TLX-0023" width="400" height="267" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-11762" /></a><a href="http://txgarage.com/2014/12/full-review-of-the-2015-acura-tlx/2015-acura-tlx-004/" rel="attachment wp-att-11743"><img src="http://txgarage.com/images/2014/12/2015-Acura-TLX-004-400x267.jpg" alt="2015-Acura-TLX-004" width="400" height="267" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-11743" /></a><a href="http://txgarage.com/2014/12/full-review-of-the-2015-acura-tlx/2015-acura-tlx-003/" rel="attachment wp-att-11742"><img src="http://txgarage.com/images/2014/12/2015-Acura-TLX-003-400x267.jpg" alt="2015-Acura-TLX-003" width="400" height="267" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-11742" /></a>
 
I haven’t had a lot of experience with Acura’s all-wheel drive system as you really have to be in the right conditions to put it to the test. I happened to find myself in such conditions this week as we had some extremely heavy rain. I was on my way to pick up my son and the roads were very wet and very slick. I decided if I wanted to give the system a test, I needed to do so before getting my boy in the car with me. I was stopped at a stop sign ready to turn left onto the next road, so I flipped the IDS to Sport + and shifted the transmission to manual mode. I grabbed the paddle shifter and made sure I was starting in first gear and was ready to pull out with some enthusiasm. I slammed the gas pedal down to the floor and the car rocketed off the line with no problems or fuss at all. Pulling around the corner at speed, I could feel the rear of the car starting to slip and then almost immediately felt the SH-AWD system straighten me out. I banged through second, third, then fourth gear getting to speed without a problem. Coming up on a sharp right-hander, I firmly pushed the break down, again feeling the system sorting out ways to keep me from getting in trouble. Pulling around the right-hander, I could feel the car wanting to step out again. I put a little more thrust into the turn, but the backend sorted itself out again.

Overall, I left very impressed with how well the TLX was able to handle itself in the conditions I threw at it. It’s nice to be in a car that instills confidence into your drive no matter the conditions.

<a href="http://txgarage.com/2014/12/full-review-of-the-2015-acura-tlx/2015-acura-tlx-0016/" rel="attachment wp-att-11755"><img src="http://txgarage.com/images/2014/12/2015-Acura-TLX-0016-400x267.jpg" alt="2015-Acura-TLX-0016" width="400" height="267" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-11755 img-bytwo" /></a><a href="http://txgarage.com/2014/12/full-review-of-the-2015-acura-tlx/2015-acura-tlx-0012/" rel="attachment wp-att-11751"><img src="http://txgarage.com/images/2014/12/2015-Acura-TLX-0012-400x267.jpg" alt="2015-Acura-TLX-0012" width="400" height="267" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-11751 img-bytwo" /></a>

Even with its confidence building technology on the road, the real way to be blown away by this car is by sitting in it and driving it as a daily driver. The Ebony black leather seats in our TLX were by far the best seats in any Acura product I’ve sat in. The leather was nice, but the bolstering and padding was extremely comfortable for everyday driving. Of course the interior is packed full of technology for safety, comfort, and entertainment, but the one big thing that will stick out to you is the electronic gear selector. This is a trend going around now that there is no need to run a cable form a gear shifter to the transmission; it’s all electronically controlled now. <a href="http://txgarage.com/?s=chrysler" title="Chrysler News and Reviews on txGarage" target="_blank">Chrysler</a> has the rotary shifter, <a href="http://txgarage.com/?s=lincoln" title="Lincoln News and Reviews on txGarage" target="_blank">Lincoln</a> has push buttons up on the dash, <a href="http://txgarage.com/?s=jaguar" title="Jaguar News and Reviews on txGarage" target="_blank">Jaguar</a> has the knob that elevates from the console so it seems like this is definitely a trend in the luxury market these days. Acura has gone with the multi-button approach laying out the park button, a reverse switch that actually has to be pulled back on, a big circular drive button that lights up with a green halo, and the parking brake switch that can be pulled back to engage the parking brake and pushed down to release it.

This may take a little getting used to and if you’re like me and usually rest your hand on the gear shifter while driving, you’ll have to find something else to do with that had, but it’s a really cool feature of the interior making this car stand apart from the crowd.

There’s so much more to talk about with this car that I could go on for days, but I want to leave you knowing how much I was actually impressed with this car. I was worried going in that they may have messed up a car I grew to love and in turn they’ve made it that much better. The luxury car market is growing and having Lincoln making cool cars again, <a href="http://txgarage.com/?s=hyundai" title="Hyundai News and Reviews on txGarage" target="_blank">Hyundai</a> and <a href="http://txgarage.com/?s=kia" title="Kia News and Reviews on txGarage" target="_blank">Kia</a> throwing their hats in the ring, and all the big luxury brands bringing lower end models, you definitely have a lot to think about entering this market as a consumer. I think with this car, though, Acura has done a fantastic job and could easily see the younger, tech crowd jumping all over the TLX.
 
[gallery columns="5" ids="11740,11741,11742,11743,11744,11745,11746,11747,11748,11749,11750,11751,11752,11753,11754,11755,11756,11757,11758,11759,11760,11761,11762"]]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>11739</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2014-12-26 08:46:28</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2014-12-26 13:46:28</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>full-review-of-the-2015-acura-tlx</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="2015"><![CDATA[2015]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="2015-acura"><![CDATA[2015 acura]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="2015-acura-tlx"><![CDATA[2015 acura tlx]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="acura"><![CDATA[acura]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="acura-2"><![CDATA[Acura]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="acura-tlx"><![CDATA[acura tlx]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="awd"><![CDATA[awd]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="car-reviews"><![CDATA[Car Reviews]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="engine"><![CDATA[engine]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="luxury"><![CDATA[luxury]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="sport-sedan"><![CDATA[sport sedan]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="tech"><![CDATA[tech]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="tl"><![CDATA[tl]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="tlx"><![CDATA[TLX]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="tlx"><![CDATA[tlx]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="top-review"><![CDATA[Top Review]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="transmission"><![CDATA[transmission]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="tsx"><![CDATA[tsx]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_knews_automated</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[0]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_aioseop_title</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[Full Review of the 2015 Acura TLX - Tech. Luxury. Thrill.]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_thumbnail_id</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[11748]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>good-bad-list</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[<div class="cci-press-card__wrap">
  <div class="cci-press-card card--front"> 
    <header class="press-card__header"></header>
    <section class="press-card__content">
      <div class="journalist-name animated fadeInLeft" data-journalist-name="Adam Moore"></div>
      <span class="journalist-title">
        <a href="http://twitter.com/adamaoc">
          @adamaoc
        </a>
      </span>
    </section>
    <footer class="press-card__footer">
      <div class="article-link">
        Web Dev for DealerTrack Tech - Writer and auto reviewer with @txGarage - Co-founder of @BensHeart Foundation - Family man first - love tech, cars, and politics
Dallas, TX 
      </div>
    </footer>
  </div>
</div>]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_aioseop_description</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[News. Reviews. Passion. - Texas Automotive Reviews - My first experience with the Acura brand was back when I was in high school. I bought a used '88 Acura Integra Special, which I was lucky enough to pick up from an auction for only $750. I drove that car for 3-years before I sold it for $900 back in 2001. Owning this car was my not just my first exposure to the Acura brand, but was also one of the cars that helped me gain a great respect and admiration for enthusiast cars. Ever since then, I’ve been following the Acura brand from its ups and downs and am always excited to get behind the wheel of a new one. Throughout this time, one of my favorite vehicles they’ve made was the TSX, a cool and sporty sedan. For the 2015 model year, though, the TL and TSX have been replaced with this new sedan, the Acura TLX.]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_aioseop_keywords</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[acura, 2015 acura, tlx, tl, tsx, 2015 acura tlx, acura tlx, 2015, engine, transmission, awd, luxury, tech, sport sedan, dallas, texas, adam moore]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_ttscj_header_code</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[<style>
.post h1 {
  font-size: 27px;
}
.entry-content del { 
text-decoration: none;
font-size: 17px;
line-height: 26px;
}
.entry-content h2:first-child {
  text-align: center; 
  line-height: 1.8;
  font-size: 18px;
  letter-spacing: 1px;
  margin-bottom: 16px;
}
.img-bytwo {
  box-sizing: border-box;
width: 50% !important;
margin-bottom: 16px;
float: left;
padding-right: 1em;
padding-top: 1em;
padding-bottom: 1em;
}

.img-bythree {
  float: left;
  width: 33.33%;
  margin-bottom: 1em;
}

.entry-content .alignleft  {
  float: left;
}
.entry-content p {
font-size: 16px;
font-weight: 100;
letter-spacing: 1px;
line-height: 24px;
}
.entry-content  p:first-child {
font-size: 17px;
line-height: 26px;
}

body .entry-content p.firstp {
  font-size: 17px;
  line-height: 24px;
}

.entry-content .clear {
	clear: none;
}

/* === CCI Journalist Press Card === */
/* === CCI Journalist Press Card === */
.inner-gbl {
  overflow: hidden; 
}
.inner-gbl > h4 {
  display: none; 
}
.cci-press-card__wrap {
  position: relative;
  width: 260px;
  height: 410px;
  margin: 0 auto;
  -webkit-transform-style: preserve-3d;
  -moz-transform-style: preserve-3d;
  transform-style: preserve-3d;
  transition: transform 0.5s ease;
}
.card--front {
  z-index: 10;
} 

.padded {
  padding: 0 5px;
  font-size: 12px;
  text-align: center;
}
.cci-press-card {
  width: 260px; 
  height: 400px;
  margin: 0 auto;
  font-family: "Lucida Grande", sans-serif;
  background: #924b4e;
  border-radius: 8px;
  border-bottom: 3px solid #57060a;
  position: absolute;
  -webkit-backface-visibility: hidden;
  -moz-backface-visibility: hidden;
  backface-visibility: hidden;
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__header {
  height: 13px;
  padding: 20px;
  font-size: 20px;
  color: ghostwhite;
  line-height: 1;
  font-weight: 700;
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__header:before {
  content: "Author";
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__header:after {
  content: "Press Card";
  color: #652327;
  float: right;
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__content {
  height: 140px;
  padding: 20px;
  font-size: 20px;
  background: #444444 url('http://txgarage.com/images/2013/11/dallas-75-back.jpg') no-repeat;
  background-position-x: 0px;
  background-size: cover;
  transition: background-position-x 1s ease-out;
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__content .journalist-name:before {
  content: attr(data-journalist-name) "\A\A";
  color: ghostwhite;
  width: 100%;
  clear: both;
  display: block;
  font-weight: 700;
  text-shadow: 2px 2px 3px #333;
}
.cci-press-card .journalist-title a {
  display: block;
  font-size: 16px;
  color: ghostwhite;
  width: 100%;
  clear: both;
  text-decoration: none;
  text-shadow: 2px 2px 3px #333;
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__footer {
  padding: 0 20px; 
  color: white;
}
.press-card__footer h4 {
  font-weight: 100;
}
.press-card__footer h4 a {
  color: #fff;
  text-decoration: none;
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__footer .article-link {
  margin-bottom: 10px;
  padding-top: 10px;
  text-align: justify;
  color: #f1f1f1;
}
.rotate-3d {
  -webkit-transform: rotateY(180deg);
  -moz-transform: rotateY(180deg);
  transform: rotateY(180deg);
}
.z-up {
  z-index: 10;
}
.animated {
  -webkit-animation-fill-mode: both;
  -moz-animation-fill-mode: both;
  -ms-animation-fill-mode: both;
  -o-animation-fill-mode: both;
  animation-fill-mode: both;
  -webkit-animation-duration: 1s;
  -moz-animation-duration: 1s;
  -ms-animation-duration: 1s;
  -o-animation-duration: 1s;
  animation-duration: 1s;
}
@-webkit-keyframes fadeInLeft {
  0% {
    opacity: 0;
    -webkit-transform: translateX(-20px);
  }
  100% {
    opacity: 1;
    -webkit-transform: translateX(0);
  }
}
@-moz-keyframes fadeInLeft {
  0% {
    opacity: 0;
    -moz-transform: translateX(-20px);
  }
  100% {
    opacity: 1;
    -moz-transform: translateX(0);
  }
}
@-o-keyframes fadeInLeft {
  0% {
    opacity: 0;
    -o-transform: translateX(-20px);
  }
  100% {
    opacity: 1;
    -o-transform: translateX(0);
  }
}
@keyframes fadeInLeft {
  0% {
    opacity: 0;
    transform: translateX(-20px);
  }
  100% {
    opacity: 1;
    transform: translateX(0);
  }
}
.fadeInLeft {
  -webkit-animation-name: fadeInLeft;
  -moz-animation-name: fadeInLeft;
  -o-animation-name: fadeInLeft;
  animation-name: fadeInLeft;
}

@media screen and (max-width: 480px) {
 .inner-gbl { display: none; }
}
</style>
]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_wpas_done_all</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Looking at the 2015 Ford Transit Commercial Van</title>
		<link>http://txgarage.com/2014/12/looking-at-the-2015-ford-transit-commercial-van/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2014 14:01:23 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[JustinWegner]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://txgarage.com/?p=11769</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[[caption id="attachment_11787" align="alignnone" width="400"]<a href="http://txgarage.com/2014/12/looking-at-the-2015-ford-transit-commercial-van/2015-ford-transit-commercial-van-14/" rel="attachment wp-att-11787"><img src="http://txgarage.com/images/2014/12/2015-Ford-Transit-Commercial-Van-14-400x267.jpg" alt="The 2015 Ford Transit Commercial Van" width="400" height="267" class="size-medium wp-image-11787" /></a> The 2015 Ford Transit Commercial Van[/caption]<p class="firstp">People who know me or took a look at my hunting picture in my bio card, know that I am a hunting fanatic. If I could hunt and drive cars for a living, I WOULD! However, since this isn’t my reality {yet!}, I have to settle with dreaming. And for me that’s where this 2015 Ford Transit (Monster) Van left me...dreaming. Not in such a bad way but this power hauler made me really want to turn this beast into the ultimate hunter’s dream traveling machine. Let me explain why I feel this was the Van for me and hope you see all the perks to this basic yet versatile driving machine.</p>

<strong>Exterior:</strong> Let’s talk about the sheer monstrosity of an appearance that this thing has. The one we were provided was a 148-inch long wheelbase, which meant we could pretty much haul anything we could fit in there. This power hauler comes in 3 different wheel base and height options ranging from 246.7 cu. ft. all the way to 487.3 cu. ft. in the Long Wheel base with extended body. Ours was medium height and we were able to accommodate a 6ft 1in person comfortably standing. This Van came with your typical driver and passenger doors but the back doors vary depending on what wheelbase you get. For the shorter 130 in. wheelbase you get 180 degree swing-out doors and on the longer wheelbase you get 270 degree swing-out… this to me doesn’t make much sense and I am sure there is a good reason for it but since we didn’t have a 130 in. wheelbase to compare it to we, at txGarage, won’t know why. But that doesn’t really bother us because either way you look at this Van, it is a powerhouse and it’s up to handle the tasks at hand. 

<a href="http://txgarage.com/2014/12/looking-at-the-2015-ford-transit-commercial-van/2015-ford-transit-commercial-van-20/" rel="attachment wp-att-11793"><img src="http://txgarage.com/images/2014/12/2015-Ford-Transit-Commercial-Van-20-400x267.jpg" alt="2015-Ford-Transit-Commercial-Van-20" width="400" height="267" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-11793" /></a><a href="http://txgarage.com/2014/12/looking-at-the-2015-ford-transit-commercial-van/2015-ford-transit-commercial-van-33/" rel="attachment wp-att-11806"><img src="http://txgarage.com/images/2014/12/2015-Ford-Transit-Commercial-Van-33-400x267.jpg" alt="2015-Ford-Transit-Commercial-Van-33" width="400" height="267" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-11806" /></a><a href="http://txgarage.com/2014/12/looking-at-the-2015-ford-transit-commercial-van/2015-ford-transit-commercial-van-15/" rel="attachment wp-att-11788"><img src="http://txgarage.com/images/2014/12/2015-Ford-Transit-Commercial-Van-15-400x267.jpg" alt="2015-Ford-Transit-Commercial-Van-15" width="400" height="267" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-11788" /></a>

<strong>Under the Hood:</strong> Now we get to talk about efficiency under the hood that powers this beast. It was hard for me to believe we got as much power as we did from the 3.5L V6 EcoBoost engine. But it’s low-end power all the way to the torque available even at higher demands put this ride as one that I know could power my hunter’s dream traveling machine. The only other Van experiences I can compare this to are the old E-Series Vans, which turns out this engine is rated better than the old E-Series 6.8L V10  at fuel economy. Speaking of which; I was consistently averaging 17 MPG, both City and Highway because let’s face it, I wanted to feel how much power this thing had. I am sure that if you took it a little easier than I did or were more cost-conscious you would get what the EPA estimates, which is 14 City and 19 HWY. There are other fuel options available but we had the gas engine, which delivered more power than expected so I know this engine will hold up for the hard working. This big machine has a payload of 3,060, which should be more than enough for what I would use it for but if you needed more you can get an extra 1500 lbs with a dual rear axle. This Van came equipped with a towing package that can handle close to 9,000 lbs., so between the towing and payload this is the machine that could handle pretty much anything you asked of it.

<strong>Interior:</strong> As plain as it may sound when reading from Ford’s website, it’s actually a pretty beefy upgrade for the interior of any Van especially from the E-Series. When you climb in this cockpit you notice theres a HUGE windshield that allows you to almost see the ground beneath your feet (not really but really close). We got the base model that didn’t have the nice big display but nonetheless it was a decent experience getting my bluetooth hooked up. But if I were you, I’d get the one with upgraded display. This comes with typical SYNC just as Ford’s do but the bigger display allows for easier connectivity to your device and less headache overall. Not to mention the smaller display doesn’t offer much of a view when you’re trying to back this thing up using the backup camera. It is important to note, that it’s a little difficult backing this one up because it didn’t have any side windows to check your surroundings. Which is another small reason to get the upgraded display. But other than that this EcoBoost Van will surely suffice to fit your needs and everything your might ask of it to do in typical everyday use. 

<a href="http://txgarage.com/2014/12/looking-at-the-2015-ford-transit-commercial-van/2015-ford-transit-commercial-van-22/" rel="attachment wp-att-11795"><img src="http://txgarage.com/images/2014/12/2015-Ford-Transit-Commercial-Van-22-400x267.jpg" alt="2015-Ford-Transit-Commercial-Van-22" width="400" height="267" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-11795" /></a><a href="http://txgarage.com/2014/12/looking-at-the-2015-ford-transit-commercial-van/2015-ford-transit-commercial-van-23/" rel="attachment wp-att-11796"><img src="http://txgarage.com/images/2014/12/2015-Ford-Transit-Commercial-Van-23-400x267.jpg" alt="2015-Ford-Transit-Commercial-Van-23" width="400" height="267" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-11796" /></a><a href="http://txgarage.com/2014/12/looking-at-the-2015-ford-transit-commercial-van/2015-ford-transit-commercial-van-03/" rel="attachment wp-att-11776"><img src="http://txgarage.com/images/2014/12/2015-Ford-Transit-Commercial-Van-03-400x267.jpg" alt="2015-Ford-Transit-Commercial-Van-03" width="400" height="267" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-11776" /></a>

One picture that is on their website for a use of this van is a Welder. I will say most welders I know, will choose a flatbed pickup truck over this but once they see the safety features and think of security they might like this Van a little more. I can say after my time with it, it was up to the task. The exterior massiveness combined with the engine cost-consciousness along with all the things you’re capable of customizing on the interior, really makes this a vehicle that I would love to have as a vehicle I travel to and from hunting destinations comfortably. This is just what I would use this for but just know this Van is up to the challenge! 

[gallery columns="5" ids="11774,11775,11776,11777,11778,11779,11780,11781,11782,11783,11784,11785,11786,11787,11788,11789,11790,11791,11792,11793,11794,11795,11796,11797,11798,11799,11800,11801,11802,11803,11804,11805,11806,11807"]]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>11769</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2014-12-31 09:01:23</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2014-12-31 14:01:23</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>looking-at-the-2015-ford-transit-commercial-van</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="fordtx"><![CDATA[#fordtx]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="2015"><![CDATA[2015]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="2015-transit"><![CDATA[2015 transit]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="car-reviews"><![CDATA[Car Reviews]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="cargo-van"><![CDATA[cargo van]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="commercial"><![CDATA[commercial]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="ecoboost"><![CDATA[ecoboost]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="ford"><![CDATA[ford]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="ford-2"><![CDATA[Ford]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="ford-transit"><![CDATA[ford transit]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="hunting"><![CDATA[hunting]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="review"><![CDATA[review]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="transit"><![CDATA[transit]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="van"><![CDATA[van]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="work"><![CDATA[work]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_knews_automated</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[0]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>good-bad-list</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[<div class="cci-press-card__wrap">
  <div class="cci-press-card card--front"> 
    <header class="press-card__header"></header>
    <section class="press-card__content">
      <div class="journalist-name animated fadeInLeft" data-journalist-name="Justin Wegner"></div>
      <span class="journalist-title">
        <a href="http://twitter.com/"></a>
      </span>
    </section>
    <footer class="press-card__footer">
      <div class="article-link">
        Justin is a Sr. Web Designer at Dealertrack Technologies with a true passion for family, anything outdoors and all things about vehicles. This gives him a great perspective on off-road vehicles although he's a big car enthusiast as well.
      </div>
    </footer>
  </div>
</div>]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_aioseop_description</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[News. Reviews. Passion. - Texas Automotive Reviews :: People who know me or took a look at my hunting picture in my bio card, know that I am a hunting fanatic. If I could hunt and drive cars for a living, I WOULD! However, since this isn’t my reality {yet!}, I have to settle with dreaming. And for me that’s where this 2015 Ford Transit (Monster) Van left me...dreaming. Not in such a bad way but this power hauler made me really want to turn this beast into the ultimate hunter’s dream traveling machine. Let me explain why I feel this was the Van for me and hope you see all the perks to this basic yet versatile driving machine.]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_aioseop_keywords</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[2015, ford, transit, commercial, van, ford transit, 2015 transit, cargo van, ecoboost, work, review, hunting]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_ttscj_header_code</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[<style>
.post h1 {
  font-size: 27px;
}
.entry-content del { 
text-decoration: none;
font-size: 17px;
line-height: 26px;
}
.entry-content h2:first-child {
  text-align: center; 
  line-height: 1.8;
  font-size: 18px;
  letter-spacing: 1px;
  margin-bottom: 16px;
}
.wp-image-11518, .wp-image-11516 {
width: 50% !important;
margin-bottom: 16px;
float: left;
}

.entry-content .alignleft  {
  float: left;
}
.entry-content p {
font-size: 16px;
font-weight: 100;
letter-spacing: 1px;
line-height: 24px;
}
.entry-content  p:first-child {
font-size: 17px;
line-height: 26px;
}

body .entry-content p.firstp {
  font-size: 17px;
  line-height: 24px;
}


/* === CCI Journalist Press Card === */
/* === CCI Journalist Press Card === */
.inner-gbl {
  overflow: hidden; 
}
.inner-gbl > h4 {
  display: none; 
}
.cci-press-card__wrap {
  position: relative;
  width: 260px;
  height: 410px;
  margin: 0 auto;
  -webkit-transform-style: preserve-3d;
  -moz-transform-style: preserve-3d;
  transform-style: preserve-3d;
  transition: transform 0.5s ease;
}
.card--front {
  z-index: 10;
} 

.padded {
  padding: 0 5px;
  font-size: 12px;
  text-align: center;
}
.cci-press-card {
  width: 260px; 
  height: 400px;
  margin: 0 auto;
  font-family: "Lucida Grande", sans-serif;
  background: #924b4e;
  border-radius: 8px;
  border-bottom: 3px solid #57060a;
  position: absolute;
  -webkit-backface-visibility: hidden;
  -moz-backface-visibility: hidden;
  backface-visibility: hidden;
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__header {
  height: 13px;
  padding: 20px;
  font-size: 20px;
  color: ghostwhite;
  line-height: 1;
  font-weight: 700;
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__header:before {
  content: "Author";
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__header:after {
  content: "Press Card";
  color: #652327;
  float: right;
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__content {
  height: 140px;
  padding: 20px;
  font-size: 20px;
  background: #444444 url('http://txgarage.com/images/2014/10/justin-wegner.jpg') no-repeat;
  background-position-x: 0px;
  background-size: cover;
  transition: background-position-x 1s ease-out;
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__content .journalist-name:before {
  content: attr(data-journalist-name) "\A\A";
  color: ghostwhite;
  width: 100%;
  clear: both;
  display: block;
  font-weight: 700;
  text-shadow: 2px 2px 3px #333;
}
.cci-press-card .journalist-title a {
  display: block;
  font-size: 16px;
  color: ghostwhite;
  width: 100%;
  clear: both;
  text-decoration: none;
  text-shadow: 2px 2px 3px #333;
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__footer {
  padding: 0 20px; 
  color: white;
}
.press-card__footer h4 {
  font-weight: 100;
}
.press-card__footer h4 a {
  color: #fff;
  text-decoration: none;
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__footer .article-link {
  margin-bottom: 10px;
  padding-top: 10px;
  text-align: justify;
  color: #f1f1f1;
}
.rotate-3d {
  -webkit-transform: rotateY(180deg);
  -moz-transform: rotateY(180deg);
  transform: rotateY(180deg);
}
.z-up {
  z-index: 10;
}
.animated {
  -webkit-animation-fill-mode: both;
  -moz-animation-fill-mode: both;
  -ms-animation-fill-mode: both;
  -o-animation-fill-mode: both;
  animation-fill-mode: both;
  -webkit-animation-duration: 1s;
  -moz-animation-duration: 1s;
  -ms-animation-duration: 1s;
  -o-animation-duration: 1s;
  animation-duration: 1s;
}
@-webkit-keyframes fadeInLeft {
  0% {
    opacity: 0;
    -webkit-transform: translateX(-20px);
  }
  100% {
    opacity: 1;
    -webkit-transform: translateX(0);
  }
}
@-moz-keyframes fadeInLeft {
  0% {
    opacity: 0;
    -moz-transform: translateX(-20px);
  }
  100% {
    opacity: 1;
    -moz-transform: translateX(0);
  }
}
@-o-keyframes fadeInLeft {
  0% {
    opacity: 0;
    -o-transform: translateX(-20px);
  }
  100% {
    opacity: 1;
    -o-transform: translateX(0);
  }
}
@keyframes fadeInLeft {
  0% {
    opacity: 0;
    transform: translateX(-20px);
  }
  100% {
    opacity: 1;
    transform: translateX(0);
  }
}
.fadeInLeft {
  -webkit-animation-name: fadeInLeft;
  -moz-animation-name: fadeInLeft;
  -o-animation-name: fadeInLeft;
  animation-name: fadeInLeft;
}

@media screen and (max-width: 480px) {
 .inner-gbl { display: none; }
}
</style>]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_thumbnail_id</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[11787]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_aioseop_title</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[Looking at the 2015 Ford Transit Commercial Van]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_wpas_done_all</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Hyundai to debut Blue Link Smartwatch App with voice recognition at 2015 CES</title>
		<link>http://txgarage.com/2015/01/hyundai-to-debut-blue-link-smartwatch-app-with-voice-recognition-at-2015-ces/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2015 14:28:35 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[News]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://txgarage.com/?p=11811</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[[caption id="attachment_11829" align="alignnone" width="400"]<a href="http://txgarage.com/2015/01/hyundai-to-debut-blue-link-smartwatch-app-with-voice-recognition-at-2015-ces/blue-link-smartwatch-18/" rel="attachment wp-att-11829"><img src="http://txgarage.com/images/2015/01/42539_Blue_Link_Smartwatch-400x263.jpg" alt="Hyundai&#039;s new Blue Link Smartwatch App" width="400" height="263" class="size-medium wp-image-11829" /></a> Hyundai's new Blue Link Smartwatch App[/caption]<p class="firstp">Jan. 2, 2015 – Smartwatch sales are skyrocketing and starting early in 2015 Hyundai owners will be able to connect with their cars using these wearable devices and the Hyundai Blue Link® smartwatch app. Hyundai will debut and demonstrate the Blue Link smartwatch app at Pepcom’s Digital Experience and at the Consumer Electronics Show (CES®). Pepcom’s Digital Experience takes place before CES on Jan. 5 and Hyundai’s exhibit (North Hall, booth #2818) at CES will be open Jan. 6-9, 2015. Hyundai’s cloud-based Blue Link platform allows features like remote start and service information to be quickly accessed through devices like smartwatches and smartphones. Hyundai partnered with Station Digital Media to develop the Blue Link smartwatch app.</p>

“This new app expands Hyundai’s exploration into how wearable technology and Blue Link fit into a customer’s lifestyle,” said Barry Ratzlaff, executive director, customer connect and service business development, Hyundai Motor America. “Connecting to your car through a smartwatch and voice recognition was previously something seen only in science fiction movies. Now, we can provide this capability to owners of Hyundai vehicles equipped with Blue Link.”

The app is easy to use. The wearer simply taps an icon or uses voice commands to execute remote functions. The Blue Link smartwatch app allows Hyundai owners to remote start, lock and unlock doors as well as find their car in a crowded parking lot. Pushing the microphone icon on the watch activates the voice function, where the driver can execute commands such as “Start my car,” “Lock my car” or “Find my car.”

<a href="http://txgarage.com/2015/01/hyundai-to-debut-blue-link-smartwatch-app-with-voice-recognition-at-2015-ces/blue-link-smartwatch-7/" rel="attachment wp-att-11818"><img src="http://txgarage.com/images/2015/01/42528_Blue_Link_Smartwatch-400x263.jpg" alt="Blue Link Smartwatch" width="400" height="263" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-11818" /></a><a href="http://txgarage.com/2015/01/hyundai-to-debut-blue-link-smartwatch-app-with-voice-recognition-at-2015-ces/blue-link-smartwatch-4/" rel="attachment wp-att-11815"><img src="http://txgarage.com/images/2015/01/42257_Blue_Link_Smartwatch1-400x263.jpg" alt="Blue Link Smartwatch" width="400" height="263" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-11815" /></a><a href="http://txgarage.com/2015/01/hyundai-to-debut-blue-link-smartwatch-app-with-voice-recognition-at-2015-ces/blue-link-smartwatch-17/" rel="attachment wp-att-11828"><img src="http://txgarage.com/images/2015/01/42538_Blue_Link_Smartwatch-400x263.jpg" alt="Blue Link Smartwatch" width="400" height="263" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-11828" /></a>

Next Generation Blue Link System to Launch on 2016 Elantra GT and Veloster 

The Blue Link smartwatch app works with first and second generation Blue Link equipped Hyundai models.

<strong>Blue Link smartwatch features</strong>

The Blue Link smartwatch app must be paired via Bluetooth to an owner’s smartphone that contains the Blue Link mobile app. Remote functions can then be executed from almost anywhere in the U.S. as long as the user’s smartphone has a Bluetooth and cellular or Internet connection. Hyundai representatives will be demonstrating the Blue Link smartwatch app on Samsung, Motorola, Sony and LG smartwatches. Android Wear users can download the app from Google Play for free starting in the first quarter of 2015.

The Blue Link smartwatch app works with first and next generation Blue Link equipped Hyundai models. The first generation Blue Link system rolled out on the 2012 Sonata and expanded across the lineup through 2013. Next generation Blue Link equipped models include the 2015 Genesis, Sonata and Azera. The smartwatch app provides all Blue Link users, including first generation owners, with even more freedom of choice when interacting with their Hyundai.

<strong>Blue Link Smartwatch features (all voice activated):</strong>

<ul class="articleul">
	<li>Remote Engine Start</li>
	<li>Remote Engine Stop</li>
	<li>Remote Door Lock / Unlock</li>
	<li>Remote Flash Lights / Honk Horn</li>
	<li>Car Finder</li>
	<li>Call Roadside</li>
	<li>Call Blue Link</li>
</ul>

<strong>Next Generation Blue Link and the 2015 Elantra GT and Veloster</strong>

The next generation Blue Link system featuring a destination search powered by Google™ continues to add new capabilities and is being applied to additional Hyundai vehicles. Recently introduced features such as maintenance alerts and the Hyundai Assurance Car Care in-vehicle app will debut on the 2016 Hyundai Elantra GT and Hyundai Veloster in 2015.

[gallery columns="5" ids="11831,11830,11829,11828,11827,11826,11825,11824,11823,11822,11821,11820,11819,11818,11817,11816,11815,11814,11813"]
]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>11811</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2015-01-02 09:28:35</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2015-01-02 14:28:35</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>hyundai-to-debut-blue-link-smartwatch-app-with-voice-recognition-at-2015-ces</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="2015"><![CDATA[2015]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="android"><![CDATA[android]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="apple"><![CDATA[apple]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="blue-link"><![CDATA[blue link]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="bluelink"><![CDATA[bluelink]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="ces"><![CDATA[ces]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="consumer-electronic-show"><![CDATA[consumer electronic show]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="elantra"><![CDATA[elantra]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="future-cars"><![CDATA[Future Cars]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="hyundai"><![CDATA[Hyundai]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="hyundai"><![CDATA[Hyundai]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="hyundai-news"><![CDATA[hyundai news]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="news"><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="news"><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="smart-watch"><![CDATA[smart watch]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="smartwatch"><![CDATA[smartwatch]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="texas-automotive-news"><![CDATA[texas automotive news]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="texas-car-news"><![CDATA[texas car news]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="veloster"><![CDATA[Veloster]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="voice-commands"><![CDATA[voice commands]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_knews_automated</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[0]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_aioseop_title</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[Hyundai to debut Blue Link Smartwatch App with voice recognition at 2015 CES]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_aioseop_description</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[News. Reviews. Passion - Texas Automotive News - Jan. 2, 2015 – Smartwatch sales are skyrocketing and starting early in 2015 Hyundai owners will be able to connect with their cars using these wearable devices and the Hyundai Blue Link® smartwatch app. Hyundai will debut and demonstrate the Blue Link smartwatch app at Pepcom’s Digital Experience and at the Consumer Electronics Show (CES®). Pepcom’s Digital Experience takes place before CES on Jan. 5 and Hyundai’s exhibit (North Hall, booth #2818) at CES will be open Jan. 6-9, 2015. Hyundai’s cloud-based Blue Link platform allows features like remote start and service information to be quickly accessed through devices like smartwatches and smartphones. Hyundai partnered with Station Digital Media to develop the Blue Link smartwatch app.]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_aioseop_opengraph_settings</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:13:{s:32:"aioseop_opengraph_settings_title";s:76:"Hyundai to debut Blue Link Smartwatch App with voice recognition at 2015 CES";s:31:"aioseop_opengraph_settings_desc";s:783:"News. Reviews. Passion - Jan. 2, 2015 – Smartwatch sales are skyrocketing and starting early in 2015 Hyundai owners will be able to connect with their cars using these wearable devices and the Hyundai Blue Link® smartwatch app. Hyundai will debut and demonstrate the Blue Link smartwatch app at Pepcom’s Digital Experience and at the Consumer Electronics Show (CES®). Pepcom’s Digital Experience takes place before CES on Jan. 5 and Hyundai’s exhibit (North Hall, booth #2818) at CES will be open Jan. 6-9, 2015. Hyundai’s cloud-based Blue Link platform allows features like remote start and service information to be quickly accessed through devices like smartwatches and smartphones. Hyundai partnered with Station Digital Media to develop the Blue Link smartwatch app.";s:32:"aioseop_opengraph_settings_image";s:73:"http://txgarage.com/images/2015/01/42539_Blue_Link_Smartwatch-400x263.jpg";s:36:"aioseop_opengraph_settings_customimg";s:73:"http://txgarage.com/images/2015/01/42539_Blue_Link_Smartwatch-400x263.jpg";s:37:"aioseop_opengraph_settings_imagewidth";s:0:"";s:38:"aioseop_opengraph_settings_imageheight";s:0:"";s:32:"aioseop_opengraph_settings_video";s:0:"";s:37:"aioseop_opengraph_settings_videowidth";s:0:"";s:38:"aioseop_opengraph_settings_videoheight";s:0:"";s:35:"aioseop_opengraph_settings_category";s:7:"article";s:34:"aioseop_opengraph_settings_section";s:15:"Automotive News";s:30:"aioseop_opengraph_settings_tag";s:200:"hyundai, bluelink, blue link, news, hyundai news, texas automotive news, texas car news, elantra, veloster, 2015, ces, consumer electronic show, smartwatch, smart watch, android, apple, voice commands";s:34:"aioseop_opengraph_settings_setcard";s:19:"summary_large_image";}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_aioseop_keywords</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[hyundai, bluelink, blue link, news, hyundai news, texas automotive news, texas car news, elantra, veloster, 2015, ces, consumer electronic show, smartwatch, smart watch, android, apple, voice commands]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_thumbnail_id</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[11829]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_ttscj_header_code</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[<style>
.post h1 {
  font-size: 27px;
  line-height: 1.3;
}

.articleul {
list-style: initial;
font-size: 16px;
margin-left: 26px;
margin-bottom: 16px;
font-weight: 100;
letter-spacing: 1px;
line-height: 24px;
}
.entry-content del { 
text-decoration: none;
font-size: 17px;
line-height: 26px;
}
.entry-content h2:first-child {
  text-align: center; 
  line-height: 1.8;
  font-size: 18px;
  letter-spacing: 1px;
  margin-bottom: 16px;
}

.img-bytwo {
  box-sizing: border-box;
  width: 50% !important;
  margin-bottom: 16px;
  float: left;
  padding-right: 1em;
  padding-top: 1em;
  padding-bottom: 1em;
}

.img-bythree {
  float: left;
  width: 33.33%;
  margin-bottom: 1em;
}
html .entry-content .wp-att-11628 {
display: block;
width: 100%;
}
html .entry-content .wp-att-11628 img {
float: none !important;
max-width: 100%;
width: 400px;
margin: 0 auto;
padding: 0;
display: block;
}
.entry-content .alignleft  {
  float: left;
}
.entry-content p {
font-size: 16px;
font-weight: 100;
letter-spacing: 1px;
line-height: 24px;
}
.entry-content  p:first-child {
font-size: 17px;
line-height: 26px;
}

body .entry-content p.firstp {
  font-size: 17px;
  line-height: 24px;
}


</style>]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_wpas_done_all</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>2015 Progressive International Motorcycle Show</title>
		<link>http://txgarage.com/2015/01/2015-progressive-international-motorcycle-show/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2015 00:29:45 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[David_Boldt]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://txgarage.com/?p=11839</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2 class="second-title">Goin’ With The Flo…</h2>

[caption id="attachment_11840" align="alignnone" width="400"]<a href="http://txgarage.com/2015/01/2015-progressive-international-motorcycle-show/indian-scout-2015/" rel="attachment wp-att-11840"><img src="http://txgarage.com/images/2015/01/Indian-Scout-2015-400x267.jpg" alt="Indian Scout 2015" width="400" height="267" class="size-medium wp-image-11840" /></a> Indian Scout 2015[/caption]<p class="firstp">While the rest of the small world known as ‘automotive media’ was packing its collective bag for the Detroit show, I was comfortably ensconced within the warm confines of Washington, DC’s convention center. There, most of what we regard as the North American motorcycle market was on display at the Progressive International Motorcycle Show, irrespective of both D.C.’s January weather and Washington’s historic indifference to motorized fun.</p>

To call it fun, of course, is to shortchange the importance of the motorcycle segment. Whether you consider a bike, motorcycle or scooter for its implied efficiency, regard their (typically) bold designs as a great form of self-expression, or simply want to see what we used to call the one-percenters (before that term was a socioeconomic distinction) might be up to, know there is a lot going on within the motorcycle industry. After an economic downturn that affected the bike biz as much as any other (American Suzuki simply cancelled the 2010 model year!), both customers and new bikes are returning to showrooms. 

<a href="http://txgarage.com/2015/01/2015-progressive-international-motorcycle-show/progressive-motorcycle-flo/" class="centerimg" rel="attachment wp-att-11841"><img src="http://txgarage.com/images/2015/01/Progressive-Motorcycle-Flo-280x300.jpg" alt="Progressive Motorcycle Flo" width="280" height="300" class="" /></a>

The Progressive International Motorcycle Show is a calendar of approximately a dozen stops across the U.S., starting in San Mateo, CA and concluding in Chicago on the second weekend of February. The Washington stop was the tour’s fourth. Next show on the Progressive calendar is in Dallas, running from January 23rd thru 25th. Additional details on that show, a listing of exhibitors and other shows on the schedule can be found at www.motorcycleshows.com. 

On the downside of the Progressive Motorcycle Show is the promoter’s reliance on what we’ll call stunt drama; on the upside is no scheduled appearances (yet) of Erik Estrada. For small miracles we give thanks…and go with the Flo.]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>11839</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2015-01-19 19:29:45</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2015-01-20 00:29:45</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>2015-progressive-international-motorcycle-show</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="auto-show"><![CDATA[auto show]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="flow"><![CDATA[flow]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="motorcycle-show"><![CDATA[motorcycle show]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="news"><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="progressive"><![CDATA[progressive]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="progressive-insurance"><![CDATA[progressive insurance]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="progressive-international-motorcycle-show"><![CDATA[Progressive International Motorcycle Show]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_knews_automated</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[0]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>good-bad-list</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[<div class="cci-press-card__wrap">
  <div class="cci-press-card card--front"> 
    <header class="press-card__header"></header>
    <section class="press-card__content">
      <div class="journalist-name animated fadeInLeft" data-journalist-name="David Boldt"></div>
      <span class="journalist-title">
        <a href="http://carbuzzard.com/#txgarage">
          http://carbuzzard.com/
        </a>
      </span>
    </section>
    <footer class="press-card__footer">
      <div class="article-link">
        Boldt, a long-time contributor to AutoTrader.com, KBB.com and – more recently – CarBuzzard.com, brings some twelve years of retail experience to the discussion, followed by another eighteen years of automotive journalism and public relations. 
      </div>
    </footer>
  </div>
</div>]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_aioseop_title</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[2015 Progressive International Motorcycle Show: Goin’ With The Flo…]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_aioseop_opengraph_settings</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:12:{s:32:"aioseop_opengraph_settings_title";s:0:"";s:31:"aioseop_opengraph_settings_desc";s:0:"";s:36:"aioseop_opengraph_settings_customimg";s:0:"";s:37:"aioseop_opengraph_settings_imagewidth";s:0:"";s:38:"aioseop_opengraph_settings_imageheight";s:0:"";s:32:"aioseop_opengraph_settings_video";s:0:"";s:37:"aioseop_opengraph_settings_videowidth";s:0:"";s:38:"aioseop_opengraph_settings_videoheight";s:0:"";s:35:"aioseop_opengraph_settings_category";s:7:"article";s:34:"aioseop_opengraph_settings_section";s:0:"";s:30:"aioseop_opengraph_settings_tag";s:0:"";s:34:"aioseop_opengraph_settings_setcard";s:7:"summary";}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_ttscj_header_code</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[<style>
.centerimg {
display: block;
text-align: center;
}
.second-title {
  text-align: center; 
  line-height: 1.8;
  font-size: 18px;
  letter-spacing: 1px;
}

.entry-content p {
font-size: 14px;
font-weight: 100;
letter-spacing: 1px;
line-height: 19px;
}
body .entry-content p.firstp {
  font-size: 16px;
  line-height: 24px;
}


/* === CCI Journalist Press Card === */
/* === CCI Journalist Press Card === */
.inner-gbl {
  overflow: hidden; 
}
.inner-gbl > h4 {
  display: none; 
}
.cci-press-card__wrap {
  position: relative;
  width: 260px;
  height: 410px;
  margin: 0 auto;
  -webkit-transform-style: preserve-3d;
  -moz-transform-style: preserve-3d;
  transform-style: preserve-3d;
  transition: transform 0.5s ease;
}
.card--front {
  z-index: 10;
} 

.padded {
  padding: 0 5px;
  font-size: 12px;
  text-align: center;
}
.cci-press-card {
  width: 260px; 
  height: 400px;
  margin: 0 auto;
  font-family: "Lucida Grande", sans-serif;
  background: #924b4e;
  border-radius: 8px;
  border-bottom: 3px solid #57060a;
  position: absolute;
  -webkit-backface-visibility: hidden;
  -moz-backface-visibility: hidden;
  backface-visibility: hidden;
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__header {
  height: 13px;
  padding: 20px;
  font-size: 20px;
  color: ghostwhite;
  line-height: 1;
  font-weight: 700;
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__header:before {
  content: "Author";
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__header:after {
  content: "Press Card";
  color: #652327;
  float: right;
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__content {
  height: 140px;
  padding: 20px;
  font-size: 20px;
  background: #ffffff url('http://txgarage.com/images/authors/david-boldt-author-img.jpg') no-repeat;
  background-position-x: 0px;
  background-size: cover;
  transition: background-position-x 1s ease-out;
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__content .journalist-name:before {
  content: attr(data-journalist-name) "\A\A";
  color: ghostwhite;
  width: 100%;
  clear: both;
  display: block;
  font-weight: 700;
  text-shadow: 2px 2px 3px #333;
}
.cci-press-card .journalist-title a {
  display: block;
  font-size: 16px;
  color: ghostwhite;
  width: 100%;
  clear: both;
  text-decoration: none;
  text-shadow: 2px 2px 3px #333;
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__footer {
  padding: 0 20px; 
  color: white;
}
.press-card__footer h4 {
  font-weight: 100;
}
.press-card__footer h4 a {
  color: #fff;
  text-decoration: none;
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__footer .article-link {
  margin-bottom: 10px;
  padding-top: 10px;
  text-align: justify;
  color: #f1f1f1;
}
.rotate-3d {
  -webkit-transform: rotateY(180deg);
  -moz-transform: rotateY(180deg);
  transform: rotateY(180deg);
}
.z-up {
  z-index: 10;
}
.animated {
  -webkit-animation-fill-mode: both;
  -moz-animation-fill-mode: both;
  -ms-animation-fill-mode: both;
  -o-animation-fill-mode: both;
  animation-fill-mode: both;
  -webkit-animation-duration: 1s;
  -moz-animation-duration: 1s;
  -ms-animation-duration: 1s;
  -o-animation-duration: 1s;
  animation-duration: 1s;
}
@-webkit-keyframes fadeInLeft {
  0% {
    opacity: 0;
    -webkit-transform: translateX(-20px);
  }
  100% {
    opacity: 1;
    -webkit-transform: translateX(0);
  }
}
@-moz-keyframes fadeInLeft {
  0% {
    opacity: 0;
    -moz-transform: translateX(-20px);
  }
  100% {
    opacity: 1;
    -moz-transform: translateX(0);
  }
}
@-o-keyframes fadeInLeft {
  0% {
    opacity: 0;
    -o-transform: translateX(-20px);
  }
  100% {
    opacity: 1;
    -o-transform: translateX(0);
  }
}
@keyframes fadeInLeft {
  0% {
    opacity: 0;
    transform: translateX(-20px);
  }
  100% {
    opacity: 1;
    transform: translateX(0);
  }
}
.fadeInLeft {
  -webkit-animation-name: fadeInLeft;
  -moz-animation-name: fadeInLeft;
  -o-animation-name: fadeInLeft;
  animation-name: fadeInLeft;
}

@media screen and (max-width: 480px) {
 .inner-gbl { display: none; }
}
</style>]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_thumbnail_id</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[11841]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_wpas_done_all</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_aioseop_description</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[Texas Automotive News :: While the rest of the small world known as ‘automotive media’ was packing its collective bag for the Detroit show, I was comfortably ensconced within the warm confines of Washington, DC’s convention center. There, most of what we regard as the North American motorcycle market was on display at the Progressive International Motorcycle Show, irrespective of both D.C.’s January weather and Washington’s historic indifference to motorized fun.]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_aioseop_keywords</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[progressive insurance, progressive, motorcycle show, auto show, Progressive International Motorcycle Show, flow, ]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>A few days with a 2015 Honda Civic EX-LNAV</title>
		<link>http://txgarage.com/2015/01/a-few-days-with-a-2015-honda-civic-ex-lnav/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2015 12:30:42 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[JustinWegner]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://txgarage.com/?p=11846</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[So Honda has really been pushing safety and that’s very apparent judging by their latest modifications to the Honda Civic. They are on their 9th generation and have only made slight tweaks to the car over the years so it’s apparent this car is popular; it just may not be for me and here’s a different way for txGarage to lay that out. 

<a href="http://txgarage.com/2015/01/a-few-days-with-a-2015-honda-civic-ex-lnav/2015-honda-civic-sedan-0022/" rel="attachment wp-att-11869"><img src="http://txgarage.com/images/2015/01/2015-Honda-Civic-Sedan-0022-400x267.jpg" alt="2015-Honda-Civic-Sedan-0022" width="400" height="267" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-11869 img-by-three" /></a><a href="http://txgarage.com/2015/01/a-few-days-with-a-2015-honda-civic-ex-lnav/2015-honda-civic-sedan-0015/" rel="attachment wp-att-11862"><img src="http://txgarage.com/images/2015/01/2015-Honda-Civic-Sedan-0015-400x267.jpg" alt="2015-Honda-Civic-Sedan-0015" width="400" height="267" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-11862 img-by-three" /></a><a href="http://txgarage.com/2015/01/a-few-days-with-a-2015-honda-civic-ex-lnav/2015-honda-civic-sedan-0018/" rel="attachment wp-att-11865"><img src="http://txgarage.com/images/2015/01/2015-Honda-Civic-Sedan-0018-400x267.jpg" alt="2015-Honda-Civic-Sedan-0018" width="400" height="267" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-11865 img-by-three" /></a>

<strong>Liked Features:</strong>

<ul>
<li>The 7 inch Audio Display - This was a two fold interest for me. The display was intuitive enough, easy to navigate while driving, and not a huge distraction. One really cool feature was the triple view setting for the back up camera, so you could really use every inch of space while in tight spaces. Use the Panorama, more directional and the one that looks directly down on the bumper.</li>
<li>The steering column and buttons - I loved the steering wheel and button layout. I think it was all very intuitive to use and not a distraction while driving. That was most important to me. </li>
<li>The side mirror display - online they show just a brief 3 second video of this and I actually found myself turning on the camera to check my lanes as I was needing to change lanes in Dallas traffic. There would be moments where I would just turn it on to see the view because the camera was that great in quality. I wish the backup cameras were this good...</li>
</ul>

<strong>Disliked Features:</strong>

<ul>
<li>The Amount of Displays - One thing that is very important in a vehicle and I think Honda knows is, simplicity. Less is more… there were 4 displays for information to keep up with. The Speedometer, which has been this honda thing for a while, the tachometer, another info display to the right of the speedometer, then the radio display. To me this is just 1 or 2 too many displays. They should cut the info display out and combine that with the tachometer. There is still enough space to make those work together harmoniously together in that area. Rather than splitting it in 2 above. </li>
<li>Seating - The seats were just down right uncomfortable. Just couldn’t find a setting I was happy with. Main problem with having some sort of lumbar adjustment would have been nice. the seats in person, feel nothing like you think they would after looking online at automobiles.honda.com</li>
<li>Gas Mileage - Last but not least. Probably the reason most would turn to a Civic, is the gas mileage. I will go on record as saying I like to test out sport modes and all that but more importantly I LOVE great gas mileage vehicles. Especially because I drive 80 miles to work in a day. So to me I value great MPGs. But I am more than disappointed at what I got. I averaged between 23 City and 29 HWY!!! I know; it’s ridiculous. They rate this VTEC 4 Cylinder at 30 City and 39 HWY. Safe to say they were just a little off. I had one trip where there wasn’t traffic and I MILKED, and I mean milked it, to get 34 MPG on the highway.</li>
</ul>

So that’s just my quick review after having a few days with the 2015 Honda Civic EX-L. If someone were to ask me, would I purchase one? I honestly wouldn’t. However, that being said, this is one of the safest cars on the market, and it’s loaded with some features that are pretty cool. Just not enough to make me really want one.

[gallery columns="5" ids="11870,11869,11868,11867,11866,11865,11864,11863,11862,11861,11860,11859,11858,11857,11856,11855,11854,11853,11852,11851,11850,11849,11848"]]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>11846</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2015-01-23 07:30:42</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2015-01-23 12:30:42</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>a-few-days-with-a-2015-honda-civic-ex-lnav</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="2015"><![CDATA[2015]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="car-reviews"><![CDATA[Car Reviews]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="civic"><![CDATA[civic]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="civic-honda-2"><![CDATA[Civic]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="driven"><![CDATA[driven]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="fuel-economy"><![CDATA[fuel economy]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="honda"><![CDATA[honda]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="honda-2"><![CDATA[Honda]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="mpg"><![CDATA[mpg]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="quick-drive-2"><![CDATA[Quick Drive]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="quick-drive"><![CDATA[quick drive]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="review"><![CDATA[review]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="safety"><![CDATA[safety]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="sedan"><![CDATA[sedan]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_knews_automated</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[0]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>good-bad-list</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[<div class="cci-press-card__wrap">
  <div class="cci-press-card card--front"> 
    <header class="press-card__header"></header>
    <section class="press-card__content">
      <div class="journalist-name animated fadeInLeft" data-journalist-name="Justin Wegner"></div>
      <span class="journalist-title">
        <a href="http://twitter.com/"></a>
      </span>
    </section>
    <footer class="press-card__footer">
      <div class="article-link">
        Justin is a Sr. Web Designer at Dealertrack Technologies with a true passion for family, anything outdoors and all things about vehicles. This gives him a great perspective on off-road vehicles although he's a big car enthusiast as well.
      </div>
    </footer>
  </div>
</div>]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_thumbnail_id</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[11860]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_aioseop_description</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[News. Reviews. Passion. - Texas Automotive Reviews :: So Honda has really been pushing safety and that’s very apparent judging by their latest modifications to the Honda Civic. They are on their 9th generation and have only made slight tweaks to the car over the years so it’s apparent this car is popular; it just may not be for me and here’s a different way for txGarage to lay that out. 
]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_aioseop_title</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[A few days with a 2015 Honda Civic EX-LNAV]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_aioseop_opengraph_settings</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:13:{s:32:"aioseop_opengraph_settings_title";s:59:"A few days with a 2015 Honda Civic EX-LNAV by Justin Wegner";s:31:"aioseop_opengraph_settings_desc";s:398:"News. Reviews. Passion. - Texas Automotive Reviews :: So Honda has really been pushing safety and that’s very apparent judging by their latest modifications to the Honda Civic. They are on their 9th generation and have only made slight tweaks to the car over the years so it’s apparent this car is popular; it just may not be for me and here’s a different way for txGarage to lay that out. 
";s:32:"aioseop_opengraph_settings_image";s:67:"http://txgarage.com/images/2015/01/2015-Honda-Civic-Sedan-00161.jpg";s:36:"aioseop_opengraph_settings_customimg";s:67:"http://txgarage.com/images/2015/01/2015-Honda-Civic-Sedan-00161.jpg";s:37:"aioseop_opengraph_settings_imagewidth";s:0:"";s:38:"aioseop_opengraph_settings_imageheight";s:0:"";s:32:"aioseop_opengraph_settings_video";s:0:"";s:37:"aioseop_opengraph_settings_videowidth";s:0:"";s:38:"aioseop_opengraph_settings_videoheight";s:0:"";s:35:"aioseop_opengraph_settings_category";s:7:"article";s:34:"aioseop_opengraph_settings_section";s:0:"";s:30:"aioseop_opengraph_settings_tag";s:103:"2015, honda, civic, sedan, mpg, fuel economy, review, quick drive, driven, safety, texas, Justin Wegner";s:34:"aioseop_opengraph_settings_setcard";s:19:"summary_large_image";}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_ttscj_header_code</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[<style>
.post h1 {
  font-size: 27px;
}

.entry-content .img-by-three {
width: 33.33%;
float: left;
box-sizing: border-box;
padding: 1em;
}
.entry-content del { 
text-decoration: none;
font-size: 17px;
line-height: 26px;
}
.entry-content h2:first-child {
  text-align: center; 
  line-height: 1.8;
  font-size: 18px;
  letter-spacing: 1px;
  margin-bottom: 16px;
}

.entry-content .alignleft  {
  float: left;
}
.entry-content p, .entry-content li, .entry-content ul {
font-size: 16px;
font-weight: 100;
letter-spacing: 1px;
line-height: 24px;
}
.entry-content ul {
list-style: initial;
margin-left: 40px;
margin-bottom: 16px;
}
.entry-content ul li {
margin-bottom: 13px;
}
.entry-content  p:first-child {
font-size: 17px;
line-height: 26px;
}

body .entry-content p.firstp {
  font-size: 17px;
  line-height: 24px;
}


/* === CCI Journalist Press Card === */
/* === CCI Journalist Press Card === */
.inner-gbl {
  overflow: hidden; 
}
.inner-gbl > h4 {
  display: none; 
}
.cci-press-card__wrap {
  position: relative;
  width: 260px;
  height: 410px;
  margin: 0 auto;
  -webkit-transform-style: preserve-3d;
  -moz-transform-style: preserve-3d;
  transform-style: preserve-3d;
  transition: transform 0.5s ease;
}
.card--front {
  z-index: 10;
} 

.padded {
  padding: 0 5px;
  font-size: 12px;
  text-align: center;
}
.cci-press-card {
  width: 260px; 
  height: 400px;
  margin: 0 auto;
  font-family: "Lucida Grande", sans-serif;
  background: #924b4e;
  border-radius: 8px;
  border-bottom: 3px solid #57060a;
  position: absolute;
  -webkit-backface-visibility: hidden;
  -moz-backface-visibility: hidden;
  backface-visibility: hidden;
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__header {
  height: 13px;
  padding: 20px;
  font-size: 20px;
  color: ghostwhite;
  line-height: 1;
  font-weight: 700;
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__header:before {
  content: "Author";
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__header:after {
  content: "Press Card";
  color: #652327;
  float: right;
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__content {
  height: 140px;
  padding: 20px;
  font-size: 20px;
  background: #444444 url('http://txgarage.com/images/2014/10/justin-wegner.jpg') no-repeat;
  background-position-x: 0px;
  background-size: cover;
  transition: background-position-x 1s ease-out;
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__content .journalist-name:before {
  content: attr(data-journalist-name) "\A\A";
  color: ghostwhite;
  width: 100%;
  clear: both;
  display: block;
  font-weight: 700;
  text-shadow: 2px 2px 3px #333;
}
.cci-press-card .journalist-title a {
  display: block;
  font-size: 16px;
  color: ghostwhite;
  width: 100%;
  clear: both;
  text-decoration: none;
  text-shadow: 2px 2px 3px #333;
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__footer {
  padding: 0 20px; 
  color: white;
}
.press-card__footer h4 {
  font-weight: 100;
}
.press-card__footer h4 a {
  color: #fff;
  text-decoration: none;
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__footer .article-link {
  margin-bottom: 10px;
  padding-top: 10px;
  text-align: justify;
  color: #f1f1f1;
}
.rotate-3d {
  -webkit-transform: rotateY(180deg);
  -moz-transform: rotateY(180deg);
  transform: rotateY(180deg);
}
.z-up {
  z-index: 10;
}
.animated {
  -webkit-animation-fill-mode: both;
  -moz-animation-fill-mode: both;
  -ms-animation-fill-mode: both;
  -o-animation-fill-mode: both;
  animation-fill-mode: both;
  -webkit-animation-duration: 1s;
  -moz-animation-duration: 1s;
  -ms-animation-duration: 1s;
  -o-animation-duration: 1s;
  animation-duration: 1s;
}
@-webkit-keyframes fadeInLeft {
  0% {
    opacity: 0;
    -webkit-transform: translateX(-20px);
  }
  100% {
    opacity: 1;
    -webkit-transform: translateX(0);
  }
}
@-moz-keyframes fadeInLeft {
  0% {
    opacity: 0;
    -moz-transform: translateX(-20px);
  }
  100% {
    opacity: 1;
    -moz-transform: translateX(0);
  }
}
@-o-keyframes fadeInLeft {
  0% {
    opacity: 0;
    -o-transform: translateX(-20px);
  }
  100% {
    opacity: 1;
    -o-transform: translateX(0);
  }
}
@keyframes fadeInLeft {
  0% {
    opacity: 0;
    transform: translateX(-20px);
  }
  100% {
    opacity: 1;
    transform: translateX(0);
  }
}
.fadeInLeft {
  -webkit-animation-name: fadeInLeft;
  -moz-animation-name: fadeInLeft;
  -o-animation-name: fadeInLeft;
  animation-name: fadeInLeft;
}

@media screen and (max-width: 480px) {
 .inner-gbl { display: none; }
}
</style>]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_aioseop_keywords</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[2015, honda, civic, sedan, mpg, fuel economy, review, quick drive, driven, safety, texas, Justin Wegner]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_wpas_done_all</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Our week with the Hyundai Sonata Sport 2.0T</title>
		<link>http://txgarage.com/2015/02/our-week-with-the-hyundai-sonata-sport-2-0t/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2015 01:39:36 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[JustinWegner]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://txgarage.com/?p=11877</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[[caption id="attachment_11875" align="alignnone" width="400"]<a href="http://txgarage.com/2015/02/our-week-with-the-hyundai-sonata-sport-2-0t/sonata-top-shot/" rel="attachment wp-att-11875"><img src="http://txgarage.com/images/2015/01/sonata-top-shot-400x229.jpg" alt="2015 Hyundai Sonata Sport 2.0t" width="400" height="229" class="size-medium wp-image-11875" /></a> 2015 Hyundai Sonata Sport 2.0t[/caption]<p class="firstp">From the sleek contours to the Sport 2.0 Turbo set up, this Hyundai Sonata literally made me want this car as my everyday driver. This urban sunset colored, full-sized sedan had enough power to tout that “sport” title with ease. My everyday driver, as many readers know, is a full-sized truck but here lately we’ve been in the lineup for driving full-sized sedans and this Sonata was no slouch. As a matter a fact it’s made it’s mark, here’s a little why I think this Sedan can be that car that a Dad (such as myself) can drive with confidence.</p>

First off, lets talk looks. I personally haven’t been a huge fan wild colors on cars, with the exception of sports cars or roadsters. This sonata, came covered with a color they call Urban Sunset with a nice little vibrant sport badge on the trunk, that I must say fit nicely. As you stand facing this fantastic vehicle, right away your eyes are drawn to the nice flowing lines on the hood that swoop effortlessly right down the hood, drawing your eyes to the...wait for it...Hyundai logo. I know, when I first think of Hyundai, at least 5 - 7 years ago, there wasn’t much you could tell me that I would get excited about with these cars. But they’re doing something right as of late. Those lines continue elegantly through the sides and to the trunk. Nestled within the flowing elegant lines are some striking LED daytime running lights at the front as well as LED taillight on each side of the spacious trunk. As you’re at the trunk, you’ll notice the contours flow nicely from the top and taper perfectly with the quad holed muffler. Just a really nice look all the way around and ride nicely on the 18 Alloy wheels.

<a href="http://txgarage.com/2015/02/our-week-with-the-hyundai-sonata-sport-2-0t/2015-hyundai-sonata-sport-0032/" rel="attachment wp-att-11911"><img src="http://txgarage.com/images/2015/02/2015-Hyundai-Sonata-Sport-0032-400x225.jpg" alt="2015-Hyundai-Sonata-Sport-0032" width="400" height="225" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-11911" /></a><a href="http://txgarage.com/2015/02/our-week-with-the-hyundai-sonata-sport-2-0t/2015-hyundai-sonata-sport-0030/" rel="attachment wp-att-11909"><img src="http://txgarage.com/images/2015/02/2015-Hyundai-Sonata-Sport-0030-400x225.jpg" alt="2015-Hyundai-Sonata-Sport-0030" width="400" height="225" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-11909" /></a><a href="http://txgarage.com/2015/02/our-week-with-the-hyundai-sonata-sport-2-0t/2015-hyundai-sonata-sport-0020/" rel="attachment wp-att-11899"><img src="http://txgarage.com/images/2015/02/2015-Hyundai-Sonata-Sport-0020-400x225.jpg" alt="2015-Hyundai-Sonata-Sport-0020" width="400" height="225" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-11899" /></a>

Now let’s take a peek at some of the specs behind the badge and under the hood. The Hyundai Sonata comes with a few options for power but what we had was the Sport 2.0T which comes ready to pump out 245 hp @ 6,000 rpm. Producing 260 lbs of torque between 1,350 and 4,000 rpms. So for a full sized sedan, and I can attest, this machine comes with more than enough power. I might add, it’s the kind of power that you will still get decent gas mileage. Speaking of which this model was rated at 23 mpg city and 32 mpg highway. That’s about what we got when we drove this but overall we averaged between 25 - 27 mpg. The 6-speed automatic transmission comes on all models of the Sonata except the Eco model comes equipped with the 7-speed. 

<a href="http://txgarage.com/2015/02/our-week-with-the-hyundai-sonata-sport-2-0t/2015-hyundai-sonata-sport-006/" rel="attachment wp-att-11885"><img src="http://txgarage.com/images/2015/02/2015-Hyundai-Sonata-Sport-006-400x225.jpg" alt="2015-Hyundai-Sonata-Sport-006" width="400" height="225" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-11885" /></a><a href="http://txgarage.com/2015/02/our-week-with-the-hyundai-sonata-sport-2-0t/2015-hyundai-sonata-sport-0039/" rel="attachment wp-att-11918"><img src="http://txgarage.com/images/2015/02/2015-Hyundai-Sonata-Sport-0039-400x225.jpg" alt="2015-Hyundai-Sonata-Sport-0039" width="400" height="225" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-11918" /></a><a href="http://txgarage.com/2015/02/our-week-with-the-hyundai-sonata-sport-2-0t/2015-hyundai-sonata-sport-0042/" rel="attachment wp-att-11921"><img src="http://txgarage.com/images/2015/02/2015-Hyundai-Sonata-Sport-0042-400x225.jpg" alt="2015-Hyundai-Sonata-Sport-0042" width="400" height="225" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-11921" /></a>

For the interior, there’s one word that comes to mind and that’s, comfortable. The next is, spacious. anytime you get comfortable and spacious together describing the interior of any vehicle, especially sedans, you know you’ve found a vehicle worth paying for. With plenty of legroom up front and in the back, you’re riding in style with not only luxurious black leather-orange trimmed seats but Hyundai claims this spacious room is “Class-Leading”. I completely agree with this claim. To get nit-picky (as I usually do) I have to say there were some small things on the interior that I liked and some that I didn’t. I feel like Hyundai has one of the best dash controls on the steering wheel that I have used. Like their use of the toggle button as well as the integration with the hands-free bluetooth system. One small thing that I just couldn't seem to get used to was the clock. They have it in a display all on its own between the radio and temperature controls. Every time I was looking for the clock display I went to the radio and kept forgetting that it was hidden below it. I would much rather see the clock display joined with the radio. 

So as far as sticker price for this Sport 2.0T this one will ring you up right around $29,500. At that price, you’re actually getting quite a bit of features with interior and driving modes that I feel are more than worth it. As far as other cars in it’s class, I still wouldn’t pass this car up as a reliable option for my family and I. 

[gallery columns="5" ids="11925,11924,11923,11922,11921,11920,11919,11918,11917,11916,11915,11914,11913,11912,11911,11910,11909,11908,11907,11906,11905,11904,11903,11902,11901,11900,11899,11898,11897,11896,11895,11894,11893,11892,11891,11890,11889,11888,11887,11886,11885,11884,11883,11882,11881,11880,11875"]]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>11877</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2015-02-05 20:39:36</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2015-02-06 01:39:36</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>our-week-with-the-hyundai-sonata-sport-2-0t</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="2-0t"><![CDATA[2.0t]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="2015"><![CDATA[2015]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="car-reviews"><![CDATA[Car Reviews]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="design"><![CDATA[design]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="eco"><![CDATA[eco]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="hyundai"><![CDATA[Hyundai]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="hyundai"><![CDATA[Hyundai]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="sonata"><![CDATA[sonata]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="sonata-hyundai"><![CDATA[Sonata]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="sonata-sport"><![CDATA[sonata sport]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="sport"><![CDATA[sport]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="sport-sedan"><![CDATA[sport sedan]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="turbo"><![CDATA[turbo]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_knews_automated</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[0]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>good-bad-list</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[<div class="cci-press-card__wrap">
  <div class="cci-press-card card--front"> 
    <header class="press-card__header"></header>
    <section class="press-card__content">
      <div class="journalist-name animated fadeInLeft" data-journalist-name="Justin Wegner"></div>
      <span class="journalist-title">
        <a href="http://twitter.com/"></a>
      </span>
    </section>
    <footer class="press-card__footer">
      <div class="article-link">
        Justin is a Sr. Web Designer at Dealertrack Technologies with a true passion for family, anything outdoors and all things about vehicles. This gives him a great perspective on off-road vehicles although he's a big car enthusiast as well.
      </div>
    </footer>
  </div>
</div>]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_aioseop_keywords</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[Hyundai, Sonata, 2015, sport, sport sedan, sonata sport, 2.0t, turbo, eco, design]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_wpas_done_all</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_aioseop_opengraph_settings</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:12:{s:32:"aioseop_opengraph_settings_title";s:0:"";s:31:"aioseop_opengraph_settings_desc";s:0:"";s:36:"aioseop_opengraph_settings_customimg";s:0:"";s:37:"aioseop_opengraph_settings_imagewidth";s:0:"";s:38:"aioseop_opengraph_settings_imageheight";s:0:"";s:32:"aioseop_opengraph_settings_video";s:0:"";s:37:"aioseop_opengraph_settings_videowidth";s:0:"";s:38:"aioseop_opengraph_settings_videoheight";s:0:"";s:35:"aioseop_opengraph_settings_category";s:7:"article";s:34:"aioseop_opengraph_settings_section";s:0:"";s:30:"aioseop_opengraph_settings_tag";s:0:"";s:34:"aioseop_opengraph_settings_setcard";s:7:"summary";}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_ttscj_header_code</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[<style>
.post h1 {
  font-size: 27px;
}

.entry-content .img-by-three {
width: 33.33%;
float: left;
box-sizing: border-box;
padding: 1em;
}
.entry-content del { 
text-decoration: none;
font-size: 17px;
line-height: 26px;
}
.entry-content h2:first-child {
  text-align: center; 
  line-height: 1.8;
  font-size: 18px;
  letter-spacing: 1px;
  margin-bottom: 16px;
}

.entry-content .alignleft  {
  float: left;
}
.entry-content p, .entry-content li, .entry-content ul {
font-size: 16px;
font-weight: 100;
letter-spacing: 1px;
line-height: 24px;
}
.entry-content ul {
list-style: initial;
margin-left: 40px;
margin-bottom: 16px;
}
.entry-content ul li {
margin-bottom: 13px;
}
.entry-content  p:first-child {
font-size: 17px;
line-height: 26px;
}

body .entry-content p.firstp {
  font-size: 17px;
  line-height: 24px;
}


/* === CCI Journalist Press Card === */
/* === CCI Journalist Press Card === */
.inner-gbl {
  overflow: hidden; 
}
.inner-gbl > h4 {
  display: none; 
}
.cci-press-card__wrap {
  position: relative;
  width: 260px;
  height: 410px;
  margin: 0 auto;
  -webkit-transform-style: preserve-3d;
  -moz-transform-style: preserve-3d;
  transform-style: preserve-3d;
  transition: transform 0.5s ease;
}
.card--front {
  z-index: 10;
} 

.padded {
  padding: 0 5px;
  font-size: 12px;
  text-align: center;
}
.cci-press-card {
  width: 260px; 
  height: 400px;
  margin: 0 auto;
  font-family: "Lucida Grande", sans-serif;
  background: #924b4e;
  border-radius: 8px;
  border-bottom: 3px solid #57060a;
  position: absolute;
  -webkit-backface-visibility: hidden;
  -moz-backface-visibility: hidden;
  backface-visibility: hidden;
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__header {
  height: 13px;
  padding: 20px;
  font-size: 20px;
  color: ghostwhite;
  line-height: 1;
  font-weight: 700;
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__header:before {
  content: "Author";
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__header:after {
  content: "Press Card";
  color: #652327;
  float: right;
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__content {
  height: 140px;
  padding: 20px;
  font-size: 20px;
  background: #444444 url('http://txgarage.com/images/2014/10/justin-wegner.jpg') no-repeat;
  background-position-x: 0px;
  background-size: cover;
  transition: background-position-x 1s ease-out;
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__content .journalist-name:before {
  content: attr(data-journalist-name) "\A\A";
  color: ghostwhite;
  width: 100%;
  clear: both;
  display: block;
  font-weight: 700;
  text-shadow: 2px 2px 3px #333;
}
.cci-press-card .journalist-title a {
  display: block;
  font-size: 16px;
  color: ghostwhite;
  width: 100%;
  clear: both;
  text-decoration: none;
  text-shadow: 2px 2px 3px #333;
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__footer {
  padding: 0 20px; 
  color: white;
}
.press-card__footer h4 {
  font-weight: 100;
}
.press-card__footer h4 a {
  color: #fff;
  text-decoration: none;
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__footer .article-link {
  margin-bottom: 10px;
  padding-top: 10px;
  text-align: justify;
  color: #f1f1f1;
}
.rotate-3d {
  -webkit-transform: rotateY(180deg);
  -moz-transform: rotateY(180deg);
  transform: rotateY(180deg);
}
.z-up {
  z-index: 10;
}
.animated {
  -webkit-animation-fill-mode: both;
  -moz-animation-fill-mode: both;
  -ms-animation-fill-mode: both;
  -o-animation-fill-mode: both;
  animation-fill-mode: both;
  -webkit-animation-duration: 1s;
  -moz-animation-duration: 1s;
  -ms-animation-duration: 1s;
  -o-animation-duration: 1s;
  animation-duration: 1s;
}
@-webkit-keyframes fadeInLeft {
  0% {
    opacity: 0;
    -webkit-transform: translateX(-20px);
  }
  100% {
    opacity: 1;
    -webkit-transform: translateX(0);
  }
}
@-moz-keyframes fadeInLeft {
  0% {
    opacity: 0;
    -moz-transform: translateX(-20px);
  }
  100% {
    opacity: 1;
    -moz-transform: translateX(0);
  }
}
@-o-keyframes fadeInLeft {
  0% {
    opacity: 0;
    -o-transform: translateX(-20px);
  }
  100% {
    opacity: 1;
    -o-transform: translateX(0);
  }
}
@keyframes fadeInLeft {
  0% {
    opacity: 0;
    transform: translateX(-20px);
  }
  100% {
    opacity: 1;
    transform: translateX(0);
  }
}
.fadeInLeft {
  -webkit-animation-name: fadeInLeft;
  -moz-animation-name: fadeInLeft;
  -o-animation-name: fadeInLeft;
  animation-name: fadeInLeft;
}

@media screen and (max-width: 480px) {
 .inner-gbl { display: none; }
}
</style>]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_aioseop_description</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[News. Reviews. Passion. - Texas Automotive Reviews -- From the sleek contours to the Sport 2.0 Turbo set up, this Hyundai Sonata literally made me want this car as my everyday driver. This urban sunset colored, full-sized sedan had enough power to tout that “sport” title with ease. My everyday driver, as many readers know, is a full-sized truck but here lately we’ve been in the lineup for driving full-sized sedans and this Sonata was no slouch. As a matter a fact it’s made it’s mark, here’s a little why I think this Sedan can be that car that a Dad (such as myself) can drive with confidence.]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_thumbnail_id</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[11875]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Mercedes-Benz Announces Pricing on All-New 2016 Mercedes-AMG GT S</title>
		<link>http://txgarage.com/2015/02/mercedes-benz-announces-pricing-on-all-new-2016-mercedes-amg-gt-s/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2015 14:13:29 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[News]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://txgarage.com/?p=11928</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[[caption id="attachment_11930" align="alignnone" width="400"]<a href="http://txgarage.com/2015/02/mercedes-benz-announces-pricing-on-all-new-2016-mercedes-amg-gt-s/2016-mercedes-amg-gt-s-2/" rel="attachment wp-att-11930"><img src="http://txgarage.com/images/2015/02/14C875_330-400x266.jpg" alt="2016 Mercedes-AMG GT S" width="400" height="266" class="size-medium wp-image-11930" /></a> 2016 Mercedes-AMG GT S[/caption]<p class="firstp">With the new Mercedes-AMG GT model range, the Mercedes-AMG sports car brand is moving into a new segment. As the second sports car developed entirely in-house by Mercedes-AMG, the GT has everything you would expect from an authentic Mercedes-AMG, from the characteristic styling, thoroughbred motorsport technology to the optimum weight distribution.</p>

<div style="clear: both; padding-top: 1em;"></div>

Starting at an MSRP of $129,900, the Mercedes-AMG GT S features a long list of standard features, including Nappa Leather, Keyless-GO, COMAND, Collision Prevention Assist PLUS, Parktronic, 8 Airbags, 19" Front / 20" Rear wheels, AMG Adaptive Suspension, LED Headlamps, Power heated/memory AMG Performance Seats, Rearview Camera, Red Brake Calipers, AMG 3-Stage ESP, and a Burmester Surround Sound System. The GT S is powered by a 4.0 bi-turbo V8 engine that features an output of 503 hp and 479 lb-ft of torque, delivering an impressive 0-60 mph time of 3.7 seconds. The U.S. market launch of the GT S is scheduled for April 2015.

The base GT variant goes on sale in the U.S. in Spring 2016 with 456 hp and 443 lb-ft of torque and a 0-60 time of 3.9 seconds. More information on pricing and equipment levels for both the Mercedes-AMG GT S and GT will be available closer to their respective launch dates.

[gallery ids="11930,11929"]]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>11928</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2015-02-06 09:13:29</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2015-02-06 14:13:29</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>mercedes-benz-announces-pricing-on-all-new-2016-mercedes-amg-gt-s</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="2016"><![CDATA[2016]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="amg"><![CDATA[AMG]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="amg-gt"><![CDATA[amg gt]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="gt-s"><![CDATA[gt s]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="mb"><![CDATA[mb]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="mercedes"><![CDATA[Mercedes]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="mercedes-benz"><![CDATA[mercedes-benz]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="mercedes-benz-2"><![CDATA[Mercedes-Benz]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="news"><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="news"><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="pricing"><![CDATA[pricing]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_knews_automated</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[0]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_thumbnail_id</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[11930]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_aioseop_title</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[Mercedes-Benz Announces Pricing on All-New 2016 Mercedes-AMG GT S]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_aioseop_description</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[New. Reviews. Passion. Texas Automotive News - With the new Mercedes-AMG GT model range, the Mercedes-AMG sports car brand is moving into a new segment. As the second sports car developed entirely in-house by Mercedes-AMG, the GT has everything you would expect from an authentic Mercedes-AMG, from the characteristic styling, thoroughbred motorsport technology to the optimum weight distribution.]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_aioseop_keywords</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[2016, mercedes, mb, mercedes-benz, gt s, amg, amg gt, pricing, news, ]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_aioseop_opengraph_settings</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:12:{s:32:"aioseop_opengraph_settings_title";s:0:"";s:31:"aioseop_opengraph_settings_desc";s:0:"";s:36:"aioseop_opengraph_settings_customimg";s:0:"";s:37:"aioseop_opengraph_settings_imagewidth";s:0:"";s:38:"aioseop_opengraph_settings_imageheight";s:0:"";s:32:"aioseop_opengraph_settings_video";s:0:"";s:37:"aioseop_opengraph_settings_videowidth";s:0:"";s:38:"aioseop_opengraph_settings_videoheight";s:0:"";s:35:"aioseop_opengraph_settings_category";s:7:"article";s:34:"aioseop_opengraph_settings_section";s:0:"";s:30:"aioseop_opengraph_settings_tag";s:0:"";s:34:"aioseop_opengraph_settings_setcard";s:7:"summary";}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_ttscj_header_code</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[<style>
.post h1 {
  font-size: 27px;
  line-height: 1.3;
}

.articleul {
list-style: initial;
font-size: 16px;
margin-left: 26px;
margin-bottom: 16px;
font-weight: 100;
letter-spacing: 1px;
line-height: 24px;
}
.entry-content del { 
text-decoration: none;
font-size: 17px;
line-height: 26px;
}
.entry-content h2:first-child {
  text-align: center; 
  line-height: 1.8;
  font-size: 18px;
  letter-spacing: 1px;
  margin-bottom: 16px;
}

.img-bytwo {
  box-sizing: border-box;
  width: 50% !important;
  margin-bottom: 16px;
  float: left;
  padding-right: 1em;
  padding-top: 1em;
  padding-bottom: 1em;
}

.img-bythree {
  float: left;
  width: 33.33%;
  margin-bottom: 1em;
}
html .entry-content .wp-att-11628 {
display: block;
width: 100%;
}
html .entry-content .wp-att-11628 img {
float: none !important;
max-width: 100%;
width: 400px;
margin: 0 auto;
padding: 0;
display: block;
}
.entry-content .alignleft  {
  float: left;
}
.entry-content p {
font-size: 16px;
font-weight: 100;
letter-spacing: 1px;
line-height: 24px;
}
.entry-content  p:first-child {
font-size: 17px;
line-height: 26px;
}

body .entry-content p.firstp {
  font-size: 17px;
  line-height: 24px;
}


</style>]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_wpas_done_all</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Full Review of the 2015 Kia K900</title>
		<link>http://txgarage.com/2015/02/full-review-of-the-2015-kia-k900/</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2015 12:20:42 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://txgarage.com/?p=11935</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>Luxury in an unexpected suit</h2>

[caption id="attachment_11937" align="alignnone" width="400"]<a href="http://txgarage.com/2015/02/full-review-of-the-2015-kia-k900/2015-kia-k900-002/" rel="attachment wp-att-11937"><img src="http://txgarage.com/images/2015/02/2015-Kia-K900-002-400x300.jpg" alt="2015 Kia K900" width="400" height="300" class="size-medium wp-image-11937" /></a> 2015 Kia K900[/caption]<p class="firstp">Back in 2011, Hyundai did something that most people just didn’t understand at the time. They brought a vehicle from overseas that would seemingly go right up against the likes of BMW, Mercedes, Lexus, and Audi all while maintaining a cost savings people would expect from a brand like Hyundai. Just because it would be significantly cheaper than the big name brands didn't mean it wasn't still going to be the most expensive vehicle they would sell. Most people can’t see spending in the lower to upper $60’s for a Hyundai. It just so happens that New Years of 2011, we were able to get our hands on one of the first Equus to hit the showroom floor. It obviously had its flaws, but in the end the car was an incredible bang for its buck. Fast forward to New Years of 2015 and we find ourselves once again driving a car that goes against conventional wisdom. The Equus had more success here in the U.S. market than anyone expected, so now it was Kia’s turn to show out; in comes the K900.</p>

Like the Equus, the K900 is a car some people don’t understand. This is a Kia with rear-wheel-drive, a 5.0-liter V8 engine pushing 420-horsepower, and a base sticker price in the mid $50k range. Why would someone pay that kind of money for a Kia?

Let’s start out with its looks. Unlike the Hyundai, which doesn’t really share any design-cues with the rest of the lineup, the K900 fits perfectly alongside the Optima and Cadenza. Seeing this car driving down the road, there is no mistaking the fact that it’s a Kia, which you could tell was something Hyundai wasn’t prepared to do. In my opinion, this was a bold move for Kia, but their design language is so nice that it just fits. I’ve often said that the Optima is one of the best looking sedans in its class, so moving that look into a bigger, more luxurious platform just makes sense. 

Up front is the standard, large grille that has been chromed out. You get some beautiful LED headlights that look more like jewelry than anything else. They are quite functional, though, using new Dynamic Bending Light technology that helps illuminate what you need to see even if it’s around a corner. Looking down the hood, you’ll see four distinctive lines all pointing toward the dominate Kia badge resting proudly on top. These lines give the vehicle a sporty and lean look; a hard feat to pull off in such a large car. The side mirrors have LED turn signals built in that almost make a ‘V’ shape following the same lines as you see on the hood. 

<a href="http://txgarage.com/2015/02/full-review-of-the-2015-kia-k900/2015-kia-k900-003/" rel="attachment wp-att-11938"><img src="http://txgarage.com/images/2015/02/2015-Kia-K900-003-400x300.jpg" alt="2015-Kia-K900-003" width="400" height="300" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-11938" /></a><a href="http://txgarage.com/2015/02/full-review-of-the-2015-kia-k900/2015-kia-k900-004/" rel="attachment wp-att-11939"><img src="http://txgarage.com/images/2015/02/2015-Kia-K900-004-400x300.jpg" alt="2015-Kia-K900-004" width="400" height="300" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-11939" /></a><a href="http://txgarage.com/2015/02/full-review-of-the-2015-kia-k900/2015-kia-k900-006/" rel="attachment wp-att-11941"><img src="http://txgarage.com/images/2015/02/2015-Kia-K900-006-400x300.jpg" alt="2015-Kia-K900-006" width="400" height="300" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-11941" /></a>

When you see this car from its side is when you start to realize its true size. This car is 200.6-inches from nose to tail. In comparison, a BMW 7-Series is about 5-inches longer. The other thing you’ll notice while looking down the side of the car is the one design gripe I would have with the K900. Kia has fit a Buick-like side vent behind the front wheels. I really think it just looks awkward in proportions to this car, but I’ve never really been a fan of fake vents either. That being said, many other vehicles in Kia’s lineup have similar vents in similar places. Around back, you also get a clean and upscale look with LED taillights and predominate, dual-chrome exhaust tips. 

All of this is nice and good, but where the K900 really needs to shine is where you’ll be spending most of your time. Looking inside the car, you would almost forget that this is a Kia, except for the proud badge right in the center of the steering wheel. The cabin is extremely spacious no matter where you enter or sit in this car. Everything is wrapped in beautiful leather and accented with real wood. Our test vehicle had a black on black interior that was nice and had a more old-school luxury look and feel. Kia also offers a black and white interior with white leather seats and more black accents around the cabin. In my opinion, this is the better looking interior to go with as it gives a much more modern interpretation of luxury. 

The amount of luxurious features and technology packed into this car are seemingly endless. You get all of the features you would come to expect from almost any vehicle these day like heated and cooled seats, bluetooth wireless, voice activated infotainment system, steering wheel mounted controls, and push button start with smart key entry. You also get so much more including park assist, front and rear parking sensors, surround view monitor showing 360-view around the car, blind-spot detection, rear-cross alert system, advanced smart cruise control, lane departure warning, driver select mode, color heads-up display, power open and close trunk, and so much more. 

<a href="http://txgarage.com/2015/02/full-review-of-the-2015-kia-k900/7637_2015_k900/" rel="attachment wp-att-11943"><img src="http://txgarage.com/images/2015/02/7637_2015_K900-400x265.jpg" alt="7637_2015_K900" width="400" height="265" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-11943" /></a><a href="http://txgarage.com/2015/02/full-review-of-the-2015-kia-k900/7634_2015_k900/" rel="attachment wp-att-11942"><img src="http://txgarage.com/images/2015/02/7634_2015_K900-400x234.jpg" alt="7634_2015_K900" width="400" height="234" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-11942" /></a><a href="http://txgarage.com/2015/02/full-review-of-the-2015-kia-k900/7764_2015_k900/" rel="attachment wp-att-11948"><img src="http://txgarage.com/images/2015/02/7764_2015_K900-400x265.jpg" alt="7764_2015_K900" width="400" height="265" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-11948" /></a>

One of the predominant features of the interior is the Lexicon Discrete Logic7 surround sound system, a 900-watt audio system with 17-speakers and an external amplifier and subwoofer. This is a great system with really good quality sound, but it’s also connected to the 9.2-inch display with UVO eServices, Kia’s infotainment and onboard app system. There are a lot of great systems out there these days including those found in Ford, Chrysler, and Toyota vehicles, but I would definitely rank these UVO systems up there with the top brands. Connecting bluetooth was done with ease as you pair your phone to the vehicle. Making voice commands was pretty smooth and I didn’t have to repeat myself for the car to understand what I was trying to accomplish. 

Another great part about the interior of this car is the rear seats. Yes, the rear seat passengers are not second class in this car. The center armrest has many controls for adjusting the climate in the rear seats. They also have heated and cooled options and can recline with a touch of a button. This car is often used as chauffeured vehicle in Korea, so it makes sense to focus luxury in the rear seats as well.

It’s all about luxury, but not just visible luxury. One thing that can’t be ignored with a large luxury sedan is the way it drives and the way it’s powered. As I mentioned earlier, the K900 comes with a 5.0-liter V8 engine delivering 420-hp and 376-lb. ft. of torque. That’s a lot of power, but it’s needed to push around this heavy car. It feels good too, to be able to put your foot down and blow away other vehicles on the road. It definitely has the power on tap when you need it.

If there was one big gripe I have with this car, it would be with the steering feel. This big, heavy luxury sedan has a very light and floaty steering feel. This is okay for smooth, luxury driving, but I prefer a heavier feel with more direct and faster inputs. It’s not that I want this to be a sports car, it’s clearly not, but having that feel and sense of weight through the steering makes you feel more in control and planted especially when driving at highway speeds. The K900 at times almost felt dangerous to drive because you never really knew what the steering what going to do. Putting the steering into sport-mode does help tighten up the feel but it’s still something I’d like to see Kia address and at this point it’s all about the software. 

At the end of my week, I felt torn on what I really thought about this car. It was incredible to drive giving you a real sense of luxury, performance, and overall comfort. Putting it up against anything else on the market that could compete in size, technology, style, or luxury would mean spending $20-30k more. I even like the styling and the overall feel of the car more than its Hyundai sibling. When it comes down to it though, would this be a car I would buy if I was in the market? I would say yes. Don’t discount this car because of the badge on the hood. The K900 is a great vehicle and I’m excited to see how well it does for the Kia brand. 


[gallery columns="5" ids="11961,11960,11959,11958,11957,11956,11955,11954,11953,11952,11951,11950,11949,11948,11947,11946,11945,11944,11943,11942,11941,11940,11939,11938,11937,11936"]
[gallery columns="5" ids="11964,11965,11966,11967,11968,11969,11970,11971,11972,11973,11974,11975,11976,11977,11978,11979,11980,11981,11982,11983,11984,11985,11987,11988,11989,11990,11991,11992,11993,11994,11995"]]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>11935</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2015-02-09 07:20:42</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2015-02-09 12:20:42</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>full-review-of-the-2015-kia-k900</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="2015"><![CDATA[2015]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="car-reviews"><![CDATA[Car Reviews]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="engine"><![CDATA[engine]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="horsepower"><![CDATA[horsepower]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="hp"><![CDATA[hp]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="k900"><![CDATA[K900]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="k900"><![CDATA[K900]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="kia"><![CDATA[kia]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="kia-2"><![CDATA[Kia]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="kia-k900"><![CDATA[Kia K900]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="luxury"><![CDATA[luxury]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="review"><![CDATA[review]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="sedan"><![CDATA[sedan]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_knews_automated</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[0]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_thumbnail_id</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[11937]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>good-bad-list</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[<div class="cci-press-card__wrap">
  <div class="cci-press-card card--front"> 
    <header class="press-card__header"></header>
    <section class="press-card__content">
      <div class="journalist-name animated fadeInLeft" data-journalist-name="Adam Moore"></div>
      <span class="journalist-title">
        <a href="http://twitter.com/adamaoc">
          @adamaoc
        </a>
      </span>
    </section>
    <footer class="press-card__footer">
      <div class="article-link">
        Web Dev for DealerTrack Tech - Writer and auto reviewer with @txGarage - Co-founder of @BensHeart Foundation - Family man first - love tech, cars, and politics
Dallas, TX 
      </div>
    </footer>
  </div>
</div>]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_aioseop_description</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[New. Reviews. Passion. - Texas Automotive Reviews :: Like the Equus, the K900 is a car some people don’t understand. This is a Kia with rear-wheel-drive, a 5.0-liter V8 engine pushing 420-horsepower, and a base sticker price in the mid $50k range. Why would someone pay that kind of money for a Kia?
]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_aioseop_keywords</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[Kia, 2015, K900, Kia K900, luxury, sedan, engine, hp, horsepower, review, ]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_aioseop_opengraph_settings</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:12:{s:32:"aioseop_opengraph_settings_title";s:0:"";s:31:"aioseop_opengraph_settings_desc";s:0:"";s:36:"aioseop_opengraph_settings_customimg";s:0:"";s:37:"aioseop_opengraph_settings_imagewidth";s:0:"";s:38:"aioseop_opengraph_settings_imageheight";s:0:"";s:32:"aioseop_opengraph_settings_video";s:0:"";s:37:"aioseop_opengraph_settings_videowidth";s:0:"";s:38:"aioseop_opengraph_settings_videoheight";s:0:"";s:35:"aioseop_opengraph_settings_category";s:7:"article";s:34:"aioseop_opengraph_settings_section";s:0:"";s:30:"aioseop_opengraph_settings_tag";s:0:"";s:34:"aioseop_opengraph_settings_setcard";s:7:"summary";}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_ttscj_header_code</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[<style>
.post h1 {
  font-size: 27px;
}
.entry-content del { 
text-decoration: none;
font-size: 17px;
line-height: 26px;
}
.entry-content h2:first-child {
  text-align: center; 
  line-height: 1.8;
  font-size: 18px;
  letter-spacing: 1px;
  margin-bottom: 16px;
}
.img-bytwo {
  box-sizing: border-box;
width: 50% !important;
margin-bottom: 16px;
float: left;
padding-right: 1em;
padding-top: 1em;
padding-bottom: 1em;
}

.img-bythree {
  float: left;
  width: 33.33%;
  margin-bottom: 1em;
}

.entry-content .alignleft  {
  float: left;
}
.entry-content p {
font-size: 16px;
font-weight: 100;
letter-spacing: 1px;
line-height: 24px;
}
.entry-content  p:first-child {
font-size: 17px;
line-height: 26px;
}

body .entry-content p.firstp {
  font-size: 17px;
  line-height: 24px;
}

.entry-content .clear {
	clear: none;
}

/* === CCI Journalist Press Card === */
/* === CCI Journalist Press Card === */
.inner-gbl {
  overflow: hidden; 
}
.inner-gbl > h4 {
  display: none; 
}
.cci-press-card__wrap {
  position: relative;
  width: 260px;
  height: 410px;
  margin: 0 auto;
  -webkit-transform-style: preserve-3d;
  -moz-transform-style: preserve-3d;
  transform-style: preserve-3d;
  transition: transform 0.5s ease;
}
.card--front {
  z-index: 10;
} 

.padded {
  padding: 0 5px;
  font-size: 12px;
  text-align: center;
}
.cci-press-card {
  width: 260px; 
  height: 400px;
  margin: 0 auto;
  font-family: "Lucida Grande", sans-serif;
  background: #924b4e;
  border-radius: 8px;
  border-bottom: 3px solid #57060a;
  position: absolute;
  -webkit-backface-visibility: hidden;
  -moz-backface-visibility: hidden;
  backface-visibility: hidden;
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__header {
  height: 13px;
  padding: 20px;
  font-size: 20px;
  color: ghostwhite;
  line-height: 1;
  font-weight: 700;
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__header:before {
  content: "Author";
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__header:after {
  content: "Press Card";
  color: #652327;
  float: right;
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__content {
  height: 140px;
  padding: 20px;
  font-size: 20px;
  background: #444444 url('http://txgarage.com/images/2013/11/dallas-75-back.jpg') no-repeat;
  background-position-x: 0px;
  background-size: cover;
  transition: background-position-x 1s ease-out;
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__content .journalist-name:before {
  content: attr(data-journalist-name) "\A\A";
  color: ghostwhite;
  width: 100%;
  clear: both;
  display: block;
  font-weight: 700;
  text-shadow: 2px 2px 3px #333;
}
.cci-press-card .journalist-title a {
  display: block;
  font-size: 16px;
  color: ghostwhite;
  width: 100%;
  clear: both;
  text-decoration: none;
  text-shadow: 2px 2px 3px #333;
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__footer {
  padding: 0 20px; 
  color: white;
}
.press-card__footer h4 {
  font-weight: 100;
}
.press-card__footer h4 a {
  color: #fff;
  text-decoration: none;
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__footer .article-link {
  margin-bottom: 10px;
  padding-top: 10px;
  text-align: justify;
  color: #f1f1f1;
}
.rotate-3d {
  -webkit-transform: rotateY(180deg);
  -moz-transform: rotateY(180deg);
  transform: rotateY(180deg);
}
.z-up {
  z-index: 10;
}
.animated {
  -webkit-animation-fill-mode: both;
  -moz-animation-fill-mode: both;
  -ms-animation-fill-mode: both;
  -o-animation-fill-mode: both;
  animation-fill-mode: both;
  -webkit-animation-duration: 1s;
  -moz-animation-duration: 1s;
  -ms-animation-duration: 1s;
  -o-animation-duration: 1s;
  animation-duration: 1s;
}
@-webkit-keyframes fadeInLeft {
  0% {
    opacity: 0;
    -webkit-transform: translateX(-20px);
  }
  100% {
    opacity: 1;
    -webkit-transform: translateX(0);
  }
}
@-moz-keyframes fadeInLeft {
  0% {
    opacity: 0;
    -moz-transform: translateX(-20px);
  }
  100% {
    opacity: 1;
    -moz-transform: translateX(0);
  }
}
@-o-keyframes fadeInLeft {
  0% {
    opacity: 0;
    -o-transform: translateX(-20px);
  }
  100% {
    opacity: 1;
    -o-transform: translateX(0);
  }
}
@keyframes fadeInLeft {
  0% {
    opacity: 0;
    transform: translateX(-20px);
  }
  100% {
    opacity: 1;
    transform: translateX(0);
  }
}
.fadeInLeft {
  -webkit-animation-name: fadeInLeft;
  -moz-animation-name: fadeInLeft;
  -o-animation-name: fadeInLeft;
  animation-name: fadeInLeft;
}

@media screen and (max-width: 480px) {
 .inner-gbl { display: none; }
}
</style>
]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_aioseop_title</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[Full Review of the 2015 Kia K900]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_wpas_done_all</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>2015 GMC Canyon 4WD SLE Crew Cab Long Box Reviewed</title>
		<link>http://txgarage.com/2015/02/2015-gmc-canyon-4wd-sle-crew-long-box-reviewed/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2015 11:00:20 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://txgarage.com/?p=12000</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[[caption id="attachment_12003" align="alignnone" width="400"]<a href="http://txgarage.com/2015/02/2015-gmc-canyon-4wd-sle-crew-long-box-reviewed/2015-gmc-canyon-txgarage-002/" rel="attachment wp-att-12003"><img src="http://txgarage.com/images/2015/02/2015-GMC-Canyon-txGarage-002-400x300.jpg" alt="The 2015 GMC Canyon by txGarage" width="400" height="300" class="size-medium wp-image-12003" /></a> The 2015 GMC Canyon by txGarage[/caption]<p class="firstp">I’ve been excited for a while about these new trucks coming out of GM. I’ve always been a  fan of the smaller truck market and like seeing what manufacturers assume we want from a small truck. Looking at the field available just a few years ago, though, was pretty depressing. Your default choice was basically a Toyota Tacoma, which is a great truck, but has been in need of some major updates for some time. Now that the all-new Colorado and Canyon are out, it seems like the small truck market is picking up once again with Toyota recently showing a newly updated Tacoma (stay tuned for more) and even Hyundai throwing a concept truck against the wall, which excites me. We’ve had the chance to drive the Colorado both as a test vehicle and also during our Truck Rodeo event where we were able to take it off road, but this is my first time in the Canyon and I already have high hopes.</p>

The <a href="http://txgarage.com/2014/10/the-small-truck-loaded-with-technologyandstuff-2015-chevy-colorado/" title="The small truck loaded with #TechnologyAndStuff – 2015 Chevy Colorado" target="_blank">Colorado was a great small truck</a> that checked a lot of the right boxes, but there’s something about this Canyon. So what sets this truck apart from its Colorado cousin? Easy, refinement inside and out. Looking at the the full lineup from GMC, you’ll notice a very distinct design style. From the beautifully styled and jeweled headlights to the bold grille and beefy fenders, this new Canyon fits right in. I even had people mistake it for the full-size Sierra. I was pretty surprised just how much I liked the exterior styling of this truck as I found myself looking back at it in the parking lot like I would a fancy sports car. 

<a href="http://txgarage.com/2015/02/2015-gmc-canyon-4wd-sle-crew-long-box-reviewed/2015-gmc-canyon-txgarage-001/" rel="attachment wp-att-12002" class="hero-center"><img src="http://txgarage.com/images/2015/02/2015-GMC-Canyon-txGarage-001.jpg" alt="2015-GMC-Canyon-txGarage-001" class="size-medium wp-image-12002" /></a>

Looking inside the truck, it’s pretty similar to the Colorado with a little more refinement. The black leather seats were nice and very comfortable. The whole cabin is covered in black leather and soft-touch plastics with wood trim in the doors and silver plastic surrounding the center stack. Overall, the interior isn’t the most premium out there, but it’s a lot better than you’ll get in pretty much any other truck of this size. It’s also put together really well and the color scheme screams luxury. 

Under the hood, you have the option of a 2.5-liter 4-cylinder engine or the one our tester was equipped with, the 3.6-liter V6. The V6 offers up 305-horsepower and has a best-in-class tow rating of 7,000-pounds. If you’re looking to tow, this is definitely the option you want to choose. The 4-banger pushes 200-hp and is available with a 6-speed manual transmission. There are talks of a small diesel being offered in the near future which should give you the best of both worlds; fuel efficiency and towing power. 

The V6 equipped with 4-wheel-drive and a 6-speed automatic transmission was rated at 17-mpg city and 24-mpg highway. During our week with the truck, we averaged just over 21-mpg which is respectable. Take off the 4WD and you can bump those numbers up to 18-mpg city and 26-mpg highway. The most efficient setup is the 4-cylinder matched up with a manual transmission getting you up to 19-mpg city and 26-mpg highway. In my opinion, though, for a truck to live with everyday, give me the V6 and more power.

Another great thing about this new Canyon is the focus on bringing technology to these small trucks. In the past, these trucks were really second class citizens and you didn’t have the option to get all the best tech, but that’s changed now. Our tester was equipped with IntelliLInk, GMC’s infotainment and connectivity system. This controls your audio, phone, bluetooth, and navigation plus many other apps. All of this is displayed on a new 8-inch touchscreen. Although the screen inputs could be a bit laggy, connecting bluetooth to this system worked well and the navigation screen was clear and easy to use. This truck isn’t just about the infotainment, though. You also get a standard rearview camera, a multitude of USB and power outlets in the front and rear, and you can get heated and cooled seats. 

Overall, this is easily my favorite compact truck on the market today. I like the refined looks of the Canyon over the Colorado and I like the extra technology and comfort you get from these trucks over the current Tacoma. If it was up to me, I’d have a crew-cab with the short box, the V6, and a SLT trim. Of course, we have yet to talk about the price. Our tester was the 4WD SLE Crew-Cab Long Box with the all-terrain package. With these boxes checked, our tester had an MSRP of $38,915. Comparing that to a similarly spec’d Tacoma you’d be looking at about $5,000 less, but you are getting more technology and refinement in the GMC. The real competition is moving up to a full size truck. You can get a full size truck with a nice interior, technology, and comfort for around $45-50k and if you buy it at the right time of the year, you can get heavy incentives, but this truck should really appeal to a different customer. Much like myself, if a full size truck just feels too big sometimes and you’re looking for something that matches your style, the Canyon really starts to make sense. Of course, if GMC really wanted to make me happy, they’d throw a cover over the bed and some 3-rd row seats to give us a modern Blazer/Jimmy (use different names) that could compete with with the best from Jeep and Toyota. 

[gallery columns="5" ids="12004,12005,12006,12007,12008,12009,12010,12011,12012,12013,12014,12015,12016,12017,12018,12019,12020,12021,12022,12023,12024,12025,12026,12027,12003,12002"]]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>12000</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2015-02-26 06:00:20</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2015-02-26 11:00:20</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>2015-gmc-canyon-4wd-sle-crew-long-box-reviewed</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="2015"><![CDATA[2015]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="4wd"><![CDATA[4WD]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="4x4"><![CDATA[4x4]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="blazer"><![CDATA[blazer]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="canyon"><![CDATA[canyon]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="canyon"><![CDATA[Canyon]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="car-reviews"><![CDATA[Car Reviews]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="compact-truck"><![CDATA[compact truck]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="crew-cab"><![CDATA[crew cab]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="engine"><![CDATA[engine]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="gmc"><![CDATA[gmc]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="gmc-2"><![CDATA[GMC]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="jimmy"><![CDATA[jimmy]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="mpg"><![CDATA[mpg]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="small-truck"><![CDATA[small truck]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="truck"><![CDATA[truck]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_knews_automated</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[0]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>good-bad-list</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[<div class="cci-press-card__wrap">
  <div class="cci-press-card card--front"> 
    <header class="press-card__header"></header>
    <section class="press-card__content">
      <div class="journalist-name animated fadeInLeft" data-journalist-name="Adam Moore"></div>
      <span class="journalist-title">
        <a href="http://twitter.com/adamaoc">
          @adamaoc
        </a>
      </span>
    </section>
    <footer class="press-card__footer">
      <div class="article-link">
        Web Dev for DealerTrack Tech - Writer and auto reviewer with @txGarage - Co-founder of @BensHeart Foundation - Family man first - love tech, cars, and politics
Dallas, TX 
      </div>
    </footer>
  </div>
</div>]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_aioseop_description</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[News. Reviews. Passion. - Texas Automotive Reviews -- I’ve been excited for a while about these new trucks coming out of GM. I’ve always been a  fan of the smaller truck market and like seeing what manufacturers assume we want from a small truck. Looking at the field available just a few years ago, though, was pretty depressing. Your default choice was basically a Toyota Tacoma, which is a great truck, but has been in need of some major updates for some time. Now that the all-new Colorado and Canyon are out, it seems like the small truck market is picking up once again with Toyota recently showing a newly updated Tacoma (stay tuned for more) and even Hyundai throwing a concept truck against the wall, which excites me. We’ve had the chance to drive the Colorado both as a test vehicle and also during our Truck Rodeo event where we were able to take it off road, but this is my first time in the Canyon and I already have high hopes.]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_aioseop_title</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[2015 GMC Canyon 4WD SLE Crew Cab Long Box Reviewed]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_aioseop_keywords</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[2015, GMC, Canyon, 4wd, 4x4, truck, compact truck, small truck, crew cab, engine, mpg, blazer, jimmy]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_aioseop_opengraph_settings</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:12:{s:32:"aioseop_opengraph_settings_title";s:0:"";s:31:"aioseop_opengraph_settings_desc";s:0:"";s:36:"aioseop_opengraph_settings_customimg";s:0:"";s:37:"aioseop_opengraph_settings_imagewidth";s:0:"";s:38:"aioseop_opengraph_settings_imageheight";s:0:"";s:32:"aioseop_opengraph_settings_video";s:0:"";s:37:"aioseop_opengraph_settings_videowidth";s:0:"";s:38:"aioseop_opengraph_settings_videoheight";s:0:"";s:35:"aioseop_opengraph_settings_category";s:7:"article";s:34:"aioseop_opengraph_settings_section";s:0:"";s:30:"aioseop_opengraph_settings_tag";s:0:"";s:34:"aioseop_opengraph_settings_setcard";s:7:"summary";}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_ttscj_header_code</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[<style>
.post h1 {
  font-size: 27px;
}
.entry-content del { 
text-decoration: none;
font-size: 17px;
line-height: 26px;
}
.entry-content h2:first-child {
  text-align: center; 
  line-height: 1.8;
  font-size: 18px;
  letter-spacing: 1px;
  margin-bottom: 16px;
}

.hero-center {
width: 90%;
display: block;
overflow: hidden;
height: 450px;
margin: 0 auto;
}
.hero-center img {
width: 100% !important;
}
.img-bytwo {
  box-sizing: border-box;
width: 50% !important;
margin-bottom: 16px;
float: left;
padding-right: 1em;
padding-top: 1em;
padding-bottom: 1em;
}

.img-bythree {
  float: left;
  width: 33.33%;
  margin-bottom: 1em;
}

.entry-content .alignleft  {
  float: left;
}
.entry-content p {
font-size: 16px;
font-weight: 100;
letter-spacing: 1px;
line-height: 24px;
}
.entry-content  p:first-child {
font-size: 17px;
line-height: 26px;
}

body .entry-content p.firstp {
  font-size: 17px;
  line-height: 24px;
}

.entry-content .clear {
	clear: none;
}

/* === CCI Journalist Press Card === */
/* === CCI Journalist Press Card === */
.inner-gbl {
  overflow: hidden; 
}
.inner-gbl > h4 {
  display: none; 
}
.cci-press-card__wrap {
  position: relative;
  width: 260px;
  height: 410px;
  margin: 0 auto;
  -webkit-transform-style: preserve-3d;
  -moz-transform-style: preserve-3d;
  transform-style: preserve-3d;
  transition: transform 0.5s ease;
}
.card--front {
  z-index: 10;
} 

.padded {
  padding: 0 5px;
  font-size: 12px;
  text-align: center;
}
.cci-press-card {
  width: 260px; 
  height: 400px;
  margin: 0 auto;
  font-family: "Lucida Grande", sans-serif;
  background: #924b4e;
  border-radius: 8px;
  border-bottom: 3px solid #57060a;
  position: absolute;
  -webkit-backface-visibility: hidden;
  -moz-backface-visibility: hidden;
  backface-visibility: hidden;
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__header {
  height: 13px;
  padding: 20px;
  font-size: 20px;
  color: ghostwhite;
  line-height: 1;
  font-weight: 700;
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__header:before {
  content: "Author";
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__header:after {
  content: "Press Card";
  color: #652327;
  float: right;
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__content {
  height: 140px;
  padding: 20px;
  font-size: 20px;
  background: #444444 url('http://txgarage.com/images/2013/11/dallas-75-back.jpg') no-repeat;
  background-position-x: 0px;
  background-size: cover;
  transition: background-position-x 1s ease-out;
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__content .journalist-name:before {
  content: attr(data-journalist-name) "AA";
  color: ghostwhite;
  width: 100%;
  clear: both;
  display: block;
  font-weight: 700;
  text-shadow: 2px 2px 3px #333;
}
.cci-press-card .journalist-title a {
  display: block;
  font-size: 16px;
  color: ghostwhite;
  width: 100%;
  clear: both;
  text-decoration: none;
  text-shadow: 2px 2px 3px #333;
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__footer {
  padding: 0 20px; 
  color: white;
}
.press-card__footer h4 {
  font-weight: 100;
}
.press-card__footer h4 a {
  color: #fff;
  text-decoration: none;
}
.cci-press-card .press-card__footer .article-link {
  margin-bottom: 10px;
  padding-top: 10px;
  text-align: justify;
  color: #f1f1f1;
}
.rotate-3d {
  -webkit-transform: rotateY(180deg);
  -moz-transform: rotateY(180deg);
  transform: rotateY(180deg);
}
.z-up {
  z-index: 10;
}
.animated {
  -webkit-animation-fill-mode: both;
  -moz-animation-fill-mode: both;
  -ms-animation-fill-mode: both;
  -o-animation-fill-mode: both;
  animation-fill-mode: both;
  -webkit-animation-duration: 1s;
  -moz-animation-duration: 1s;
  -ms-animation-duration: 1s;
  -o-animation-duration: 1s;
  animation-duration: 1s;
}
@-webkit-keyframes fadeInLeft {
  0% {
    opacity: 0;
    -webkit-transform: translateX(-20px);
  }
  100% {
    opacity: 1;
    -webkit-transform: translateX(0);
  }
}
@-moz-keyframes fadeInLeft {
  0% {
    opacity: 0;
    -moz-transform: translateX(-20px);
  }
  100% {
    opacity: 1;
    -moz-transform: translateX(0);
  }
}
@-o-keyframes fadeInLeft {
  0% {
    opacity: 0;
    -o-transform: translateX(-20px);
  }
  100% {
    opacity: 1;
    -o-transform: translateX(0);
  }
}
@keyframes fadeInLeft {
  0% {
    opacity: 0;
    transform: translateX(-20px);
  }
  100% {
    opacity: 1;
    transform: translateX(0);
  }
}
.fadeInLeft {
  -webkit-animation-name: fadeInLeft;
  -moz-animation-name: fadeInLeft;
  -o-animation-name: fadeInLeft;
  animation-name: fadeInLeft;
}

@media screen and (max-width: 480px) {
 .inner-gbl { display: none; }
.hero-center {
width: 95%;
display: block;
overflow: hidden;
height: 250px;
}
}
</style>
]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_thumbnail_id</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[12003]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_wpas_done_all</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
</channel>
</rss>
